- [explosions]
- [blaster fire]
How much longer until
we're in hyperspace, Tech?
That depends on when Echo plans
on getting the drive back online.
I'm working on it!
- [explosion]
- [creature squawks]
I don't think Ruby
likes this very much.
You named that thing?
What's with these guys?
- Well, we did steal from them.
- [Ruby hisses]
Technically, the Rhokai
stole the lizard first.
We are merely intercepting it.
They don't see it that way.
[Ruby squawks]
[Wrecker screaming] It's
loose! It's loose! [Grunts]
Get it off! Get it
off. Get it off!
Stay calm. You're scaring her.
Get it off. Get it
off. Get it off!
[Ruby squeals]
Hyperdrive's online.
- [Ruby hisses]
- Got her.
[Ruby growls]
- That is one strange-looking lizard.
- [Ruby hissing]
What's your client want it for?
Maybe it's a pet. Maybe he wants to turn
it into a stew. Don't know, don't care.
As long as you get paid.
Now you're catching on.
And guess what? That
means you get paid too.
Bring the lizard in the back.
[Ruby squeals]
[Omega] Hunter?
What are you two up to?
The mission's over. Can we go?
Again?
It's a tradition.
It makes the kid happy.
Uh-huh.
The kid.
[sighs] Don't take long.
[Wrecker laughs]
All right, fellas,
here's your cut.
- [cage rattling]
- [Ruby snorting]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You said the job paid
three times this.
For me, not for you.
And just how is this a mutually
beneficial arrangement?
You're breathing, aren't you?
Rather generous considering
the debt you owe me.
What debt?
Docking fees, port charges,
gear, fuel, rations,
and 20 cartons of Mantell Mix.
Best part of the mission.
Mm-hmm.
That'll be 14 credits
for the Mantell Mix.
- [Omega] Mmm.
- Uh, yeah... uh, put it on Cid's tab.
Hey, you're in my seat. Move it!
Oh, he's ignoring you.
You hearing me? I said move it.
Now, I like you boys, but I'm
not running a charity here.
You need a big score
for us to be square.
Like what?
Like retrieving that tactical
droid, but you bungled that op.
I suggest you figure something
out before you see my ugly side.
That's not her ugly side?
What was that, goggles?
- [blaster fires]
- [crash]
[blaster fires]
[aliens screaming]
[big alien] Move! Out of my way!
Hey, what's going on in here?
Who are you?
Rex?
Oh, great. Another clone.
Just what I needed.
Well, don't get comfy.
I'm done taking in strays.
This ain't a clone
clubhouse, ya know.
Unbelievable. Thinkin'
they own the place.
Captain.
[Rex] It's been a while, boys.
Where have you been, Rex?
Hmm.
That's a long story.
And when the war ended,
I guess you could say I've
been... keeping a low profile.
Very low. Imperial files have
you listed as killed in action.
Being dead in the Empire's
eyes has its advantages.
Well, how'd you track us down?
Trace and Rafa Martez.
They said a squad of rogue
clones helped them on Corellia.
They told me I
could find you here.
And that you were
traveling with a kid.
Who is she?
Omega. She's a clone like us.
Well, look who it is. [Laughs]
Come here, Rex. [Laughs]
[grunts] Yeah. Good to
see you too, Wrecker.
I thought you didn't
like the regs.
[Wrecker] This one we like.
Omega, this is Rex.
I've met many clones in my
time, but never one like you.
You're a generation one.
Now how'd you know that?
From the lines on your face.
[Rex chuckles]
Yeah, I guess I've been around.
You got that right.
[groans]
Tech, I need one of
those med patches.
[Tech] You used the last one.
What's wrong?
Nothing. It's just a headache.
Which are becoming
more frequent.
Is that so?
If you're concerned about the
so-called inhibitor chips, don't be.
Our deviant nature appears to
have impeded their functionality.
Except in Crosshair.
You're telling me you
haven't removed your chips?
No, not yet.
Rex?
Those chips make you a threat to
everyone around you. Even her.
You're all ticking time bombs.
Take it easy, Captain.
What's in your head is more
dangerous than you can imagine.
I've seen what happens
when the chip activates,
and I don't want to bury
any more of our brothers.
Trust me. It is not
something you can control.
I couldn't.
It's a risk you do
not want to take.
How do you suggest
we get them out?
Good question. I'll be in touch.
[Gonky honking]
[groans]
[groans] I don't like this plan.
We agreed to meet Rex on
Bracca. That's what we're doing.
He wants to cut open my head.
All of our heads actually.
Not mine. I don't have
an inhibitor chip.
Why not? Now, that's not fair.
How's the chip scanner coming?
Since Rex's chip was removed, I
am able to establish a baseline
by comparing his
brain scan to ours.
Allowing for the detection
of any cellular anomaly.
He means, "It's
almost finished."
Do we really have to do this?
If Rex is sure, we
should trust him.
[console beeps]
[Omega] What is this place?
[Hunter] A starship graveyard.
- [console whistles]
- I'm picking up Rex's beacon.
Right on time.
How's a junk planet
gonna help us?
[Rex] Follow me.
Bracca may not be much to look at,
but it has exactly what we need.
I had my inhibitor chip taken out
on a Jedi cruiser just like that.
That's where we're heading.
[Wrecker] Then why'd we
land all the way over here?
[Hunter] Everyone down.
[Rex] That's why.
[Tech] It's the Scrapper Guild.
[Rex] They control
this entire planet.
We need to keep out of
sight from their patrols.
Let's move.
Fives tried to warn me about the chips,
but I didn't understand at the time.
[Echo] It's still
hard to believe now.
[Rex] How did you boys
find out about them?
[Echo] Omega.
[Rex] The kid?
[rumbling]
[metal groaning]
[Omega] Whoa.
It's much bigger up close.
[Rex] This is an original Venator-class
ship from the first batch off the line.
[Wrecker] First off the line,
huh? Just like you, Rex.
[laughs]
[Tech] What is it?
[Hunter] Stay above
the waterline.
[metal rumbling, groaning]
[Rex] The last time I was aboard
one of these it didn't end so well.
[Echo] If the inhibitor chip
isn't something you can control,
how'd you get yours out?
[Rex] I had help.
[water splashes]
The medical bay's
at the other end.
Wrecker, grab that cable.
[Wrecker] This? W-Why? W-W-What
are you gonna do with it?
- [Rex] Nicely done.
- [Omega grunts]
[Echo] You're up, Wrecker.
[Wrecker] Uh...
Yeah, my head doesn't hurt anymore.
I'm fine. You guys go without me.
You can do it. Just keep
your eyes on the cable.
[Wrecker groans]
[grunts, exhales]
Whoa!
That was close.
- [Wrecker screams, grunts]
- [Rex] Wrecker!
[Wrecker] Whoa, whoa! [Grunts]
[grunting]
[Rex] Are you all right?
[Wrecker] No! Smells
awful down here!
[gags]
- What's that?
- [Hunter] Wrecker, start climbing.
- [Wrecker] Why?
- Hurry!
- [dianoga roars]
- [Wrecker grunts, shouts]
- Wrecker!
- [Hunter] Grab the cable. Get him up.
[Wrecker grunts]
[dianoga screams]
[Wrecker] Faster! Pull faster!
- [dianoga roars]
- [Wrecker shouts]
[Hunter, Rex grunting]
[Wrecker] Whoa, whoa!
[dianoga roars]
[dianoga growls]
[Rex] Wrecker!
[water bubbles]
- [Wrecker grunts]
- Pull!
[Hunter, Rex grunting]
- [Wrecker shouts]
- [dianoga roars]
[Wrecker] Whoa!
- [dianoga growls, screams]
- [Wrecker] Whoa, whoa... [shouts]
[strains, coughs]
- [breathing heavily] What was... that?
- [Hunter, Rex strain]
[Wrecker coughs]
[Rex breathing heavily]
Makes you miss battling
clankers, doesn't it?
[groans] Yeah.
[rat squeaks]
- [door groans]
- [rat squeaks]
[rats chatter]
[rat squeaks, chatters]
This will do nicely.
[Tech] I would no longer call this
medical bay a sterile environment.
Do you prefer to use
the facility on Kamino?
[Tech] This will do nicely.
I'll calibrate the surgical pod.
- [screen beeps]
- [electricity pulsating]
Time to get scanned, Wrecker.
Let's get this over with.
[groans]
[device beeps]
[scanner beeping]
- [device whines]
- [Wrecker groans]
Hunter, just because the surgery
worked on Rex, doesn't mean it's safe.
This is dangerous.
It's more dangerous to leave
their inhibitor chips in.
We have to do this.
It's worth the risk.
And what if
something goes wrong?
I'll be left here with no one.
We're not going anywhere, Omega.
You're stuck with
us for the long run.
Got it?
[scanner beeping]
[Tech] I think I
found something.
Ninety degrees from his
right orbital floor,
below the parietal and
temporal intersection...
Get that away from me.
[groaning]
Something's not right.
We need to speed this up.
[pod hums]
[machinery whirs, clanks]
[Rex] You boys got lucky.
Very few clones were immune
to the effects of Order 66.
It's rare.
When the regs attacked the Jedi on
Kaller, we didn't understand why.
[groaning continues]
[Hunter] We couldn't save the general,
but at least we helped the Padawan escape.
Relax, this won't hurt a bit.
[grunts]
[Tech grunts, gasps]
Wrecker.
You're in direct
violation of Order 66.
[bellows]
Wrecker?
He'll destroy the equipment if
we don't get him out of here.
[Wrecker] You're all traitors.
We'll draw him out.
Omega, stay with Tech.
[Wrecker coughs]
[sighs, grunts]
[shouts, grunts]
- [metal clanks]
- [Wrecker grunts]
- [Hunter shouts]
[blaster fires]
[Hunter shouts]
[both grunting]
[shouts]
[grunts] Come on,
Wrecker. Snap out of it.
[both grunting]
[Hunter groans]
All clones in violation of
Order 66 shall be terminated.
[Hunter choking]
[blaster fires]
Huh? [Growls]
[Omega panting]
[Omega breathing heavily]
- [Wrecker grunts]
- [gasps]
[electricity crackling]
[breathing heavily]
[Wrecker roars]
[exhales]
[rat squeaks, chatters]
[footsteps approach]
[Wrecker grunts]
This isn't you, Wrecker.
It's the inhibitor chip.
Conspiring with traitors
makes you guilty of treason.
Please, stop. I don't
want to hurt you.
[Wrecker grunts]
But, Wrecker, I'm your friend.
Good soldiers follow orders.
- [blaster fires]
- [groans]
Is it supposed to
take this long?
I'm not sure. I've never
been on this end of it.
[console hums]
[Tech] The procedure's complete.
Wrecker.
Wrecker!
He should be awake by now.
- [console hums]
- He is alive,
but his vitals have
not stabilized.
We won't know more until
he regains consciousness.
This could be a while.
Why don't you take Omega
topside and get some air?
[Omega] No.
I'm staying until he wakes up.
[Wrecker grunts]
Hey, kid. Why...
Why the long face?
He's awake!
Oh. You made it.
- Welcome back.
- [Wrecker chuckles, groans]
One chip down. Three
to go. Who's next?
[machinery whirs]
[Wrecker grunts]
Listen, Omega.
About what happened...
I... I tried to control it.
I tried as hard as I could.
I just couldn't make it stop.
I know, Wrecker. It's okay.
But still... I... I'm sorry.
[gasps]
The mission's over.
We can't break tradition.
Thanks, kid.
[chuckles]
[Omega] Mmm.
[person speaks on
comm, indistinct]
Copy that. I'll meet you at the
rendezvous by the next rotation.
I figured you weren't out
of the fight just yet.
I spent my life defending
the Republic. Can't stop now.
The Republic's gone, Rex.
Ah, not all of it. We're here.
Others are out there too.
Your squad's skills would
be a tremendous asset.
Things aren't like before.
Our priorities have shifted.
So I've noticed.
Omega needs us, and I have to
do what's best for my squad.
Which is what?
I'm still figuring that out.
I guess we all are.
When you sort things out,
let me know where you land.
Tell the boys I'll
see them around.
[Hunter] Stay out of trouble.
Funny. I was gonna
say the same to you.
Well...
Take care, trooper.
[Hunter] Captain.
If you're ever in a bind,
you know how to reach us.
[scrapper] Intruders confirmed on
the Jedi Cruiser. Notify the Empire.