Cid better pay us
extra for that mission.
[Wrecker] Eh. It wasn't so bad.
She failed to mention the drop zone
would be swarming with Gundarks.
It is not the first time she
has left out key details.
- [chattering]
- [electronic music playing loudly]
When did this place
get so popular?
And who are they?
Not our problem. Let's find Cid.
[masked guard] Where do
you think you're going?
[blows landing]
[grunts]
It's rude to barge into
one's office unannounced.
This isn't your office.
[scoffs] Guess again.
- Ruby?
- She's my prized pet.
What are you doing with her?
I paid. Cid delivered.
And where is Cid?
Cid's out.
This parlor and Ord Mantell
are now my territory.
But if you're looking for
work, I might have use for you.
We'll think about it.
You do that.
We're getting off Ord Mantell.
Tech, prep the ship. The rest
of us will gather supplies.
But what about Cid?
What did he mean when
he said she was "out"?
Given his tone,
it is a plausible assumption that Cid
was either forced out or taken out.
Well, we have to find
her and help her.
[Cid clears throat]
Nice to see one of you cares.
Inside. Now.
So you boys met Roland.
He's a former client and the
son of crime boss Isa Durand.
Roland's trying to make a name for
himself by joining up with the Pykes.
What's he doing on Ord Mantell?
This port's connected to
multiple hyperspace routes,
ideal for smuggling.
My parlor's right in the
middle of the action.
Roland saw the value
in it and took it.
But we are taking it back.
- We?
- If I lose, you lose.
Don't forget how good I've
been at keeping secrets.
I believe she's threatening us.
You're quick.
When we needed help, we
came to Cid, remember?
Now she needs help.
We can't just walk away.
You tell 'em, Tiny.
[sighs]
So, what's your plan?
My sources tell me that a
buyer is meeting Roland tonight
to acquire a shipment of spice
he's storing in my back office.
You want to disrupt his supply
chain by stealing the shipment
and thereby sabotaging the deal.
Very good, Goggles.
When the Pykes come to collect,
Roland won't be able to pay,
and he'll be their problem.
Start climbing, tough guys.
[Hunter] Where are we?
Ord Mantell's old
mining tunnels.
These rails run
underneath the city.
It's how we're sneaking into
my parlor to steal the spice.
[Wrecker] Well, why don't we
just walk in there and take it?
We can handle those guards.
No one can know we're involved.
Roland is one thing,
but the Pykes aren't an
enemy you want to make.
We'll use these carts to
transport the crates of spice.
[Tech] They're not in the best shape,
but I can get the motors operational.
No. Motors are too loud.
This is a stealth mission. You
boys are good at that, right?
Tiny, Goggles, you're with me.
[carts creaking,
rattling quietly]
[brakes squeaking]
Now, listen up.
When we pass through those
doors, not a peep out of anyone.
We don't want to wake the hive.
[Echo] The what?
The caverns have a slight
infestation problem.
[Wrecker chuckles] We're
not afraid of a few bugs.
Well, it won't be a problem if
everyone keeps their traps shut.
Big guy, get the door.
[screeching in distance]
- [wings flapping]
- [Wrecker] Wha...
[whispering] What was
that? Oh. [Grunts]
[gasps]
What did I say?
[Wrecker scoffs]
It was an accident.
- [rumbling]
- [screeching]
[rumbling, screeching continue]
[rumbling, screeching stop]
[Hunter] Keep moving.
[Cid] We're here.
[Wrecker muttering, panting]
This ladder leads into my
back office. Up you go.
[Tech] Without eyes on the office,
how do we know Roland is not inside?
I've got that covered.
[beeping]
[chiming quietly]
[electronic music playing]
[grunts, squeals]
[sniffing]
[chewing]
[Ruby squeals]
Ruby?
Don't just stand
there. Find her!
[Ruby squeals]
- [comm beeps]
- All clear.
[Echo] Ugh. And I thought
Wrecker was a slob.
[Cid on comm] Can the commentary.
Roland won't be gone for long.
[Tech] Six crates
of spice confirmed.
[Wrecker] Here. Hand it over.
Where is she?
We looked everywhere.
Can't find her.
Keep looking.
[shushes] Keep that thing quiet.
[stammers] Give it more mix.
[groans]
[Ruby screeches]
Now you've done it.
[screeching continues]
Okay. New plan!
You coward!
[squeals]
[Roland] There you are.
[Ruby panting]
Good girl.
After them.
Out of time, boys.
- Get the last two crates.
- [Echo] I'll seal the door.
Don't worry. We'll catch
those two and kill them.
Yes, we will.
From now on, you
need to stay close.
[Ruby purring]
The spice.
It's gone!
[Cid] That's secure
enough. Let's go.
Found them!
[Wrecker] We've got incoming!
- I said no blaster fire.
- [Wrecker] Tell that to them!
[masked guard] Huh?
[screaming]
[grunts]
[masked guards scream]
If those laser brains woke
the hive, we're all dead.
[screeching]
What's that sound?
Cid, I don't like this.
[rumbling]
Power up the engines!
[Wrecker] We've got more coming!
[screeching]
[screams]
[screeches]
[Tech] They're avoiding the
light. Use your torches.
[screeches]
Not the spice!
- [Echo] Forget the spice. Let's go!
- Wrecker, seal them in.
[sighs] Whew! [Groans]
Well, at least we got
rid of the spice, right?
I didn't anticipate Cid
to be so bold or foolish.
It... It was all her idea.
- We swear.
- Yeah, it was a distraction.
We weren't gonna
hurt Ruby. Honest.
Tell me where Cid took my spice!
We don't know. She didn't say.
Get them out of here.
[Pyke] Where is our payment?
[Roland] The
shipment was stolen.
You'll get your money,
but I need more time.
[Pyke] We did not
come to hear excuses.
If you cannot deliver as promised,
you are of no further use to us.
I said you'll get your money.
I suggest you go back
to Oba Diah and wait.
[Pyke] You are out of
your depth, Durand.
Either you correct
this grave mistake,
or you and your entire family will
experience what pain truly feels like.
Are you sure your parlor's safe?
Bolo and Ketch said the Pykes
already came for Roland.
I told you they don't take
kindly to unpaid debts.
See? My plan worked
like a charm.
Even better than expected.
That's her. She's
the one you want.
[Pyke] It has come to my attention that
you have stolen our shipment of spice.
Return it to us, and we will
consider this issue resolved.
Not sure what he's been telling
you, but we don't have any spice.
[Pyke] Kill them all.
Wait. We don't have the spice
on us, but we know where it is.
[Pyke] My patience
is wearing very thin.
If you know where the spice is,
then you should have no
problem retrieving it.
Until you do, the
child stays here.
Not happening.
[Pyke] You misunderstand.
This is not a negotiation.
If I may…
You all don't realize
who you're dealing with.
If you don't lower your blasters,
we're all gonna wish we were dead.
Let me handle this.
We can't leave Omega with them.
We don't have a choice, but
we know where the spice is.
We'll return it, and
the kid will be fine.
The ptero-creatures we encountered
in the cavern are Irlings.
They are nocturnal insects with visual
sensitivity to thermal registers.
Our best chance is to
strike before nightfall.
Muscles and I will rappel down into
the cavern and locate the crates.
I got the kid into this
mess, and I'll get her out.
[Wrecker groans] You've
gotta be kidding me.
And this time, don't drop it.
- [cracks]
- [gasps]
- [exhales]
- [screeches]
[whispering] Found one.
I'll secure it.
Start looking for
the other crates.
Quietly.
Don't try it. They'll kill you.
If your friends don't return
the spice, we're both dead.
That's what happens when you
meddle in other people's business.
Us?
You're the one who took
Cid's parlor from her.
You take what you want.
That's the Durand way.
It's a tactic my
mother has perfected.
So, she's a criminal too?
Ugh. You make it
sound so undignified.
[chuckles]
If she saw me now…
[whimpers]
[purring]
[sighs]
Ruby doesn't take a
liking to many people.
Don't worry, Ruby.
We'll get out of this.
Crates three and
four are aboard.
It's almost night.
Those things are gonna wake up.
I am preparing for
that possibility.
[Wrecker grunts]
Last crate… [exhales
heavily] …in hand.
Rest later.
Final crate secure.
Bring us up.
Quit squirming.
[cable groaning]
[Wrecker] Oh.
[whispering] Maybe
they didn't hear it.
I don't think we're that lucky.
Yeah, me neither.
[rumbling]
[Wrecker screaming on
comm] Get us out of here!
Wrecker. What's going on?
[Cid] Irlings. Lots of 'em!
[Wrecker] Help!
Help me! Help me!
Watch out for the spice.
[Wrecker screaming]
Tech.
This should distract them.
Incoming!
[screaming continues]
[screeching]
See, Muscles? That
wasn't so bad.
[Wrecker muttering] Yeah,
I'm okay. I'm okay. Phew!
[Pyke] Since the spice has been returned,
the matter between us is resolved.
- But not with you.
- [Ruby squeals]
Don't!
He made a mistake. That's all.
She's right.
Kill him and you'll be
starting a war with Isa Durand.
Do you want that heat right now?
Call this a bad
deal and walk away.
[Pyke] We do not
accept bad deals.
[screams]
Our business is finished.
It would not be wise for
our paths to cross again.
Are you okay?
It's a small price to pay.
[Ruby whimpers, pants]
I'll be going now.
Come on, boys.
First round's on me.
[scoffs] You owe us
way more than that.
Don't push your luck.
Why did you stick up for
him after what he did?
I don't know.
Ruby likes him.
Maybe he's not all bad.