[computer beeps]
[sighs] Well, this is a first.
[Echo] Inspecting every corner of
the ship finally tired her out.
Yeah, she's curious.
I'll give her that.
[sighs] Hunter, she's a child.
What are we gonna do with her?
[Tech] We are coming
up on Saleucami.
[squawking]
[growling]
[squawks]
[birds chirping]
Hmm?
What's with her?
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
Whoa.
What is this?
[Tech] That would be dirt.
[gasps] It's amazing.
[laughs]
[Hunter] Come on.
Let's get moving.
[squawking]
Whoa.
Huh?
[chuckles]
So this friend of yours, what's
he doing all the way out here?
Hiding. That's
what deserters do.
Staying off the radar's not our specialty,
but he's been doing it for years.
And you trust a deserter?
Why not? We're
all deserters now.
What are we looking at?
A booby trap.
Single trip wire.
[chuckles] That's cute.
Whoa! [Screams]
Easy, Wrecker!
Was that me?
[Suu] What do we have here?
More clones who
have lost their way.
It's been a while, fellas.
I see a few new faces.
Echo and Omega, Cut and Suu.
Pleased to meet you.
Ma'am.
Where's Crosshair?
It's complicated.
Sounds familiar.
Rex told us about the clone
troopers turning against the Jedi.
You talked to Rex? When?
Well, he passed
through yesterday.
Where'd he go?
Didn't ask.
He was going on about
some behavioral implant.
He must mean the inhibitor chip.
The what?
Inhibitor chips.
The Kaminoans implanted them in the
clones to modify their behavior.
Tech, you said the regs were programmed
but you never mentioned a chip.
How else did you
think it worked?
Mom, Dad!
There's a ship outside!
Shaeeah, Jek! Remember me?
- Uncle Wrecker!
Who are you?
Omega.
We never see kids around here.
Come with us.
[squawking]
Mm... what's the
purpose of this?
To have fun. Here, you try.
Huh?
You're supposed to catch it.
Oh.
All right, out with it.
What's with the girl?
She's a defective
clone, like we are.
Not exactly.
What do you mean?
The Kaminoans don't
create without a purpose.
You all have one,
so what's hers?
It doesn't matter.
She's just a kid.
Mm. Battling droids was easy
compared to raising a child.
[chuckling]
You have no idea
what you're in for.
We didn't have a choice.
Kamino wasn't safe anymore.
Well, neither is Saleucami.
Rex warned us of the
storm that's coming.
Clone troopers have
already started showing up.
I'm heading into town to book
us a transport off-world.
We can take you
where you need to go.
Nah, you're wanted
men. It's too risky.
I have to do what's
best for them.
[Shaeeah laughing]
I caught it!
[droid beeps, whistles]
[chattering]
Troops should be pulling their forces,
not securing a post. The war is over.
[chuckles] Well, it
doesn't feel that way.
[PA: Indistinct]
They started seizing
ships about a week ago.
Military ships?
All ships.
They're tagging them
inside that impound lot.
The stall's up ahead.
Let's book the shuttle
before we're spotted.
So, where will you and
your family go next?
I suppose find a remote piece
of land on a distant planet.
That's all we really need.
That's the key to
not being found?
You wanna know how to disappear?
Put being a soldier behind you
and make a new life for yourself.
What do you want?
I need to book passage on
the next shuttle out of here.
Those credits won't do you
any good without a chain code.
New galactic policy.
My what?
[sighs] Your chain code.
[PA: Admiral] your
individual chain code,
every citizen can exchange their
invalid currency for Imperial credits,
thanks to the generosity
of the new Galactic Empire.
The war is over.
With peace comes opportunity
and prosperity for all.
[male passenger grunting]
I booked passage
on this transport.
No planetary travel
without a chain code.
But I have to get on this ship.
Stand down, citizen.
Get in line, get your chain
code, and don't make any trouble.
It's not just ships.
They're registering people too.
[sighs] Getting off-planet's
gonna be harder than I thought.
[animal squawks]
Nice one.
I'll get it.
It's past the fence.
We'll get it later.
Jek!
Come inside. We have
to finish packing.
But it's still early.
Inside, now.
Where's Omega?
She was right behind me.
[Shaeeah] Omega!
Got it!
[Shaeeah] Omega, don't move!
[growling]
[beeping]
Hmm. It appears all public transport
is now restricted without chain codes.
Which Cut can't sign up for.
He'll be arrested when they
discover he's a deserter.
The next shuttle
leaves in a few hours.
Codes or no codes,
we need to be on it.
[Shaeeah] Mom!
Mom, it's Omega!
She went out past the fence!
[creature growling]
[hisses]
[growling continues]
[whimpers]
[growls, winces]
[growling]
What were you doing out there?
Do you realize you
could've been killed?
Easy. She's not a soldier.
Are you hurt? Now,
let's take a look here.
I'm sorry. I was
trying to get the ball.
I didn't know.
You're safe. That's
all that matters.
Come on.
Hey, kid. You all right?
She'll be fine.
All in all, I would say that
could've gone much worse.
Tech, you think you could
forge some chain codes?
I only learned of them
moments ago, but yes.
Do it. We're getting Cut, Suu
and the kids on that shuttle.
[sniffles]
[sighs]
Need another set
of eyes out here?
Almost forgot how good
of a shot you are.
I owe you one.
Children will always find ways
of getting into trouble, Hunter.
It's what they do.
Protecting them is what we do.
Where's Omega?
She wanted to stay on the ship.
I've been thinking
about what you said.
And you're right,
she's not a soldier.
Just give her some time.
When you leave Saleucami, I
want Omega to go with you.
You two can give her
something that we can't.
Is that what you really want?
It's what she needs.
It's ironic. Clones wanted
names instead of numbers,
yet now people are signing
up to be given numbers.
It's ingenious.
You could create a database to
identify anyone in the galaxy.
Glad you're impressed,
but where are we going to find the data
for these chain codes? And the disks?
Already thought of that.
Clones now control
the spaceport.
There we can tap into their
network and replicate the codes.
Then what?
Hunter said they're tagging ships
inside their impound facility.
That is our way in.
You're suggesting we call the
authorities and have them seize our ship?
That is exactly
what I am saying.
I guess if they think it's
abandoned, that just might work.
You did what?
Tech!
This was the simplest solution.
Getting our ship impounded
is not my idea of a solution.
We'll meet you at the
spaceport with the chain codes.
I have this under control.
[Hunter] There's one big
problem. Omega's on the ship.
I think it's a good plan, Tech.
So much for simple.
[clone trooper 1] Clamp it
down and add it to the list.
We'll run its signature later.
What kind of ship
is this anyway?
[clone trooper 2] Looks like a
modified Omicron-class attack shuttle.
[clone trooper 1] It's a mess.
No wonder it was abandoned.
So far so good.
Now how can I help?
[Echo] You've had enough action
for today. We'll handle this.
[Tech] Go to the security kiosk.
Scomp in, copy the data and grab
the blank disks for me to program.
[Echo] Roger that.
[droid beeping]
I don't see any disks, Tech.
They'll be locked in
a safe compartment.
Ah. Found 'em.
Excellent.
Tech, we're in the spaceport.
What is your status?
In progress. The encryption
shouldn't be a problem.
Mom, I don't like this.
Everything will be okay.
Hurry up. We need those chain
codes to get them on the shuttle,
or we're going to have to
blast our way out of here.
Don't worry.
I can slip through security unnoticed
and deliver the disks to you momentarily.
[alert sounds]
[comms chatter]
[Echo] No chance you're getting
past all them undetected.
[Tech] We can't get caught
with these chain codes.
We can't get caught at all.
What are you talking about?
If we get tied up in a blaster fight,
they're gonna lock down the whole port.
Where'd the disks go?
And where's Omega?
Found her.
[Echo] This great plan of yours
is looking really lousy about now.
Have your chain codes out
and ready for inspection.
[Tech] The chain codes are
en route... with Omega.
By herself? You let
her go by herself?
- Well, we didn't let her go.
- I'm on it.
She ran off on her own.
If something happens to her...
Like I said, kids
always find trouble.
[Tech] What is taking so long with the
boot? Are you trying to get caught?
I'm doing my best. You wanna
come out here and give it a try?
Hey, who are you? You
don't belong here.
I'm the maintenance tech.
I've got a situation at bay...
[Tech] That is not ideal.
[Echo] We're in
agreement on that one.
[chirping]
[beeps, wailing]
No! Don't do that.
That hit the spot!
[Echo] Wrecker, we could
use some help over here.
On my way.
They're waiting for you at
the dock. Better get going.
Halt. Where are you going?
Uh...
Show me your chain
code, citizen.
Sure. I got it right here.
Oh, right, must be in this hand.
A couple of locals with
blasters got past the barrier.
[clone trooper]
Next. Step forward.
We're running out
of time, Hunter.
Omega's on her way.
No, something's wrong. She
should've been here by now.
Stick to the plan, Cut.
[clone trooper] Let me
see your identification.
- I can't risk it.
- [clone trooper] All right, move along.
We have to find another way out.
[Omega] I'm here.
- [whispering] And I have the chain codes.
- [quiet] Yeah, Omega!
Tech accidentally made
five disks instead of four.
You didn't tell her?
Tell me what?
[clone trooper] Keep moving.
The extra chain code's for you,
so you can leave with Cut and Suu.
Why?
Did I do something wrong?
You need a family, kid.
They're good people. They'll
give you the life you deserve.
But... I want to stay with you.
[clone trooper] Quit
holding up the line.
You have to go, Omega.
It's for your own good.
[device beeps]
[device beeping]
You're clear. Go on through.
[Tech] Hunter, we have worn out our
welcome. We need to go right now.
On my way.
Ready?
- [shouts]
- [screams]
[grunting]
[grunts]
[Tech] Glad you could make it.
What are we waiting for?
The clamp's still magnetized.
The system's not responding.
Move.
[grunts]
It responded to that.
Let's go.
Wait. Omega's not back.
- Wrecker, she's not...
- [Omega] Wait for me!
[grunting]
Is there a problem?
You look like...
They need reinforcements
at the impound dock.
Carry on.
[droid honking]
I know I made a mistake,
and I have a lot to learn,
but you don't have
to get rid of me.
I left Kamino with you.
This is where I wanna be.
Tell you the truth, kid, I guess
I've got a lot to learn too.
If this is where you want to be,
then this is where you'll stay.