Idaflor, that's where we'll go.
But Idaflor's not
even inhabited.
Which makes it the
perfect place to hide out.
"Hide"? But I've been stuck
on Kamino my whole life.
Can't we explore?
Not right now. We have to wait
for things to settle down.
Well, we won't be doing either.
We don't have enough fuel, and we
are also entirely out of rations.
Without the Republic
to provide us supplies,
we'll have to acquire these
necessities on our own.
[Echo] Well, we got
a bigger problem.
Comm chatter has our ship's
signature on a wanted list.
So we scramble it.
You can do that?
Of course I can do it.
But I need to land in order to
perform those modifications.
By my calculations, the
closest planet is... Pantora.
Well, Pantora it is.
- [computer beeping]
- [footsteps departing]
[exhales] Pantora it is.
- [door opens]
- [device beeping]
Why'd you tell me we're out
of rations? Now I'm starving.
Our priority is scrambling
the ship's signature key.
[grunts] Your priority.
[man clears throat, coughs]
Are you fellas here for repairs?
- Just a minor calibration and fuel.
- [clears throat]
Have at it. Just need
to scan your ship in.
Are you sure about that?
I suppose I could
skip that step.
Mm-hmm.
- Ah, that was easy.
- [clears throat]
Aren't you, uh,
forgetting something?
Huh?
You... You said
you'd skip the step.
- I could.
- Great!
If I had some incentive
of the financial variety.
I think he means credits.
Is that sufficient incentive?
[chuckles]
Pleasure doing
business with you.
[chuckles]
We're getting the hang
of this civilian thing.
- [comm beeps]
- This is Raspar Six at Ro station.
Word on the channels is,
you're looking for a certain modified
Omicron-class attack shuttle.
I might know where to find it, but
that information's going to cost you.
[woman] I'll make it
well worth your while.
Transmit the coordinates and
make sure they don't leave.
[engines starting]
[droid honking]
[grunts] You can't sell that
explosive. It's our last one.
And it's the only thing
we have worth any money.
You wanna eat, don't you?
Why do Tech and I have
to do all the repairs
while you get to go sightseeing?
"Sightseeing"?
No, no. This is a supply run.
In and out, quickly and quietly.
Yeah. And you
stick out too much.
Oh, and you don't?
Not dressed like this.
All right. Let's get moving.
- Omega, you're with us.
- Yes.
Hey! Bring back
something good to eat.
[chattering]
[laughter]
[creatures trilling]
[applause, cheering]
[PA: Rampart] ...registering
for your individual chain code,
every citizen can exchange their
invalid currency for imperial credits...
What are they celebrating?
The end of the war.
[Echo] Chain code post
like on Saleucami.
Your individual chain code,
every citizen can exchange their invalid
currency for Imperial credits at no cost,
thanks to the generosity
of the new Galactic Empire.
Things are changing
quicker than I thought.
Let's get what we came
for and get out of here.
But the war is over.
Isn't that good?
[Echo] Depends which
side you're on.
[PA: Rampart] ...at no cost, thanks to
the generosity of the new Galactic Empire.
The signature key should be embedded
below the rear parallax inverters.
[grumbles] Just tell
me what to rip out.
Well, start with that.
[cracks neck]
[chattering]
No sale.
Look, this is a pyro denton
worth at least 1,800 credits.
Maybe in the black market, but I'm
running a reputable business here.
Hey, kid! You break
it, you buy it.
[Omega] Sorry.
If you're looking to sell
something, how about your droid?
[Echo] Droid?
Uh, he's a... he's a
military prototype.
Military, eh?
Hmm.
I'll give you 2,000.
Give me a minute.
[Echo] No, no, no.
You can't be serious.
We need the credits.
Once we get the supplies, I'll give
you the signal and you can leave.
[Echo] Fine, but
not at that price.
- I am worth more than 2,000.
- Right.
Make it 4,000.
Three.
Deal.
[sighs]
[creatures yapping]
[Omega] Hello, there.
[yapping continues]
- [slurping]
- [chuckles]
Oh. Hey, wait. Wait.
Hey!
Echo, go to your new owner.
[Echo] Yes, whatever
you require.
Omega?
[creatures yapping]
[Omega panting]
[grunts]
Hey! Watch it.
S... Sorry.
[man speaking Huttese]
[sighs]
[creature snarls]
[sighs, breathes heavily]
[woman] Oh, are you all right?
You seem lost.
I got separated from my friends.
I can help with that. Not
to worry. We'll find them.
[droids beeping]
We'll finally have
some order around here.
Now, get to work and start
supervising these droids.
[sighs]
I beg your pardon. I am the droid in
charge... Oh, my! You're not a droid.
[droid beeping]
You're right, Clink. I will
report his deception at once.
I'll take your complaint.
Dear me!
Anyone else?
[droids beeping]
Thanks for helping me
look for my friends.
It's no trouble at
all. You hungry, kid?
Yeah, but I don't
have any credits.
[grunts]
Sorry about that.
[sighs] Thank you.
You're so kind.
My mistake.
Here.
But we didn't pay for these.
It's okay to break
the rules sometimes.
Are you a soldier?
Not exactly.
Then why do you have a blaster?
To protect myself.
The galaxy's a dangerous
place to be on your own.
Yeah. It's a good thing
I have my friends.
Aren't you lucky?
[gasps] I know. If you're
alone, you should come with us.
Hmm. [Chuckles]
Now that's the best offer
I've had in a long time.
Come on. This way.
[Hunter] Omega.
Oh, there's one
of my friends now.
Omega, step away from her.
Why? She was helping
me look for you.
Yes, Omega and I were
getting to know each other.
Hunter!
- [groans] Let go!
- [grunts]
[grunts]
Omega, run!
[both grunting]
[knife, blaster clatter]
[grunts]
[security] Citizen.
Halt!
Wrecker, easy with my ship.
Your ship?
[ship beeping]
There. That is
the signature key.
[Wrecker] Ah.
Got it.
With a slight adjustment,
we'll be able to scramble our
signature whenever we need to.
[Hunter] Wrecker, Tech, Echo. I
lost Omega. Somebody attacked us.
[Wrecker] Somebody who?
[sighs] A woman. Highly
trained. She's after the kid.
Yeah, we'll see about that.
[comm beeps]
I'll tap into the
central security network.
There should be enough cameras
in this city to find her.
[Hunter] Listen, I made a bit of noise
out here. Get the ship ready to go.
Well, it's not technically
a ship at the moment.
And unless you have a team of maintenance
droids, it's going to be a while.
I can help with that.
Gear up, fellas, we're
going into the field.
[droids beeping]
I am afraid that is impossible. We
are prohibited from leaving this post.
Look, the sooner we do this, the
sooner you're back in charge.
Even so, I'm not capable of
removing our restraining bolts.
That's why I'm the supervisor.
[whirring]
- [grunts]
- [droids beeping]
Hey! Where do you think you're
all going? Get back inside.
[stammers] You're not a droid.
You got me for a bargain.
[gasps]
[man 1] Hey!
- [Omega grunts]
- [man 2] Watch it!
[chattering]
[gasps]
[pants]
[beeps]
[comm chatter]
[security] Be advised, a public
disturbance has been reported
in the central marketplace.
[chattering continues]
We have a 315 in progress.
Two suspects on foot.
All available units to respond.
[Tech] I have eyes on Omega.
She went down into the maintenance
tunnels. Head northwest, at 155.
And she's got company.
[pants]
[yelps]
- There you are.
- [gasps]
[Omega] Wrecker?
You had us worried.
Can we get out of here?
You got it.
I'm with Omega.
We're on our way.
[gasps]
- Get to the ship. I'll handle her.
- [cracks knuckles]
You mess with the kid,
you mess with me. [Growls]
[roars]
[grunts, groans]
[keypad beeps]
[gasps]
[Echo sighs] Tech
wasn't kidding.
We got our work cut out for us.
I am not programmed to repair
or assemble starships. Oh!
[droid beeping]
No, you don't, Clink. I
give the orders around here.
225, DK-3, get to
work on the repulsors.
[screams, groans]
Wrecker, where are you?
Wrecker. Do you copy?
[security] Reports of a child hanging
from a tower in the lower division.
[Tech] I do not see Wrecker,
but Omega is hanging from a
maintenance tower in the skyway.
Hanging?
[Tech] For now. I
suggest you hurry.
[man] Hey!
[breathes heavily]
- [gasps, screams]
- [woman grunts]
You can thank me later.
- Tuck and roll when you land, kid.
- [screams]
[grunts]
- [Tech] Wrecker.
- [groans, grunts]
I gotta find Omega.
[Tech] Hunter's already on
it. Get back to the ship.
[strains]
[shouts, grunts]
[groans, grunts]
[grunts]
[electronic music playing]
[grunts, gasps]
[whimpers]
[pants, whimpers]
[grunts]
Hey! [Grunts]
[screams]
Hunter!
Look out!
[grunts]
[groans]
[screams]
[grunts]
- Hold on, kid. We're not out of this yet.
- [beeps]
- [beeping]
- [gasps]
[grunts]
[panting]
[groans, exhales]
Huh?
[grunts]
[groans] I'm missing
all the action.
My diagnostic test indicates
this vessel is now operational.
Thanks for the help, boys.
[droid beeps]
They're all yours.
You heard him. I am back
in charge. Follow me.
We need to go. Now.
Wrecker, pick up the pace.
We don't have all day.
[panting] I'm here.
- [computer beeps]
- [ship powers up]
[gasps]
No. They can't leave!
[pants] No. Wait! Don't go!
She hasn't paid me yet! Stop!
[shouts]
[sighs] She has to
be a bounty hunter.
A what?
Someone hired to
retrieve targets.
And you appear to be the target.
Me?
Hey, don't scare the kid.
We have to find out who
she is and who hired her.
No. Wait. I... I
tried to stop them.
[woman] If they come back,
you know how to contact me.
- [comm beeps]
- The target got away, but I'll find her.