[screams, gasps]
Sorry.
Steady.
Arms level... and keep
your eye on the target.
You can do it, kid!
Not a chance. Miss!
Come on! Miss!
Ah! Got it.
- [laughs] Bull's-eye! Pay up.
- [groans]
Good. Again.
But I've already hit
the target three times.
Out of 12. That's
luck, Omega, not skill.
Soldiers need to be consistent.
[sighs]
[Weequay] Okay, double
or nothing she chokes.
- [groans]
- [cackles]
I was doing better until
those two showed up.
You have to learn to tune out
distractions, which comes with practice.
Again.
[grunts]
[sighs]
Not exactly a natural, is she?
- Hey!
- Okay, playtime's over. We need to talk.
You two, scram.
- Hey! Okay, we're going.
- We're going!
I assume you boys know
what a tactical droid is?
They were the opera...
The operational brains of
the Separatist military...
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba. This is
my briefing, Goggles.
Hey!
Tactical droid intel
has tremendous value,
which is why you're gonna break into
this decommissioning facility on Corellia
and retrieve one before
they're all destroyed.
We haven't decided if we're
gonna work for you or not.
Allow me to decide
for you. You're in!
I'm talking a mutually
beneficial arrangement.
You make money, I make
money, and I watch your back.
With the heat on you, it's
the best option you've got.
[sighs] I guess we're in.
I know you're in. I
just told you you're in.
And you, you're releasing too soon
because of those weak noodle arms.
Build up your strength.
Lesson over.
[target sizzles]
This old trick?
It gets us past the
planetary sensors every time.
Why is a tactical droid more
important than the other droids?
The more tactical droids fought,
the more they learned... and won.
Yeah, except against
us. [Chuckling] Yeah!
With clones now
serving the Empire,
knowing how to defeat them
just went up in value.
We're approaching the
decommissioning site.
We can land at the industrial
dockyard and go in on foot.
[droid chatter]
[Hunter] Cid didn't mention this
place was guarded by police droids.
[Tech] They're operating on
a rotating quadrant scan.
If timed correctly, there's an
entry point in their blind spot.
Follow me.
[Wrecker] Uh-oh.
[groans]
[sighs]
[bubbling, sizzling]
- [worker grunts]
- [Wrecker] Nighty night.
[Hunter] Echo, Tech. We'll
locate and retrieve the droid.
Wrecker, cover us up top.
[Wrecker] But being the
lookout was Crosshair's job.
[Hunter] That wasn't a request.
What about me? What should I do?
[Hunter] Stay here and keep
your eyes peeled for the target.
Let's move.
[Wrecker groans]
[worker gasps]
[Echo] A tactical droid is listed
in the system, but only one.
The rest have already
been destroyed.
[Hunter] We have one shot
at this. Let's get it right.
[Tech] Where was the
droid off-loaded?
[Echo] North end conveyor.
[Omega gasps] Found it.
Sort of.
The droid's already in pieces.
[Tech] Is the head intact?
[Omega] Affirmative.
Wait! Someone just ran
off with the droid head.
[Wrecker] I see 'em. One of the
workers is stealing our target.
I'm on it.
[Hunter] Negative.
Stay out of sight.
[worker] I don't think so.
Stay back.
Whoa, whoa. Take it easy, kid.
I don't wanna hurt you, but I
can't have you getting in the way.
You're the one in my way.
[Trace] Rafa, I've got
the target. Where are you?
Don't answer that.
[Trace] Rafa, come in. What's going on?
Where are you? We need to get out of here.
[Tech] Who are you?
Who am I? Who are you?
Your arms look a
little shaky there.
Okay, you win.
Why don't you ease up on that
thing and we can talk about this?
[Omega grunts]
Uh-oh.
[worker] We've got blaster fire!
All eyes on the floor!
[gasps]
[worker] Security
breach! Lock it down!
[male electronic
voice] Danger. Danger.
[alarm blaring]
Great. How do you plan on
getting out of here now?
[scoffs] Nice going, kid.
Me? You're the one
who grabbed my bow!
[droid chatter]
Don't just stand
there. Grab a weapon.
I had one.
[droid chatter]
[Wrecker] Get moving!
See ya.
Hey!
[Echo] We've got police
droids closing in.
[Hunter] Focus your fire.
[droid chatter]
- [comm beeps]
- Omega, report.
There's a second person
after the tactical droid.
Don't worry. I'm in pursuit.
[Hunter] No, stay put. We
already have the droid head.
No, you don't.
Rafa, I have the package.
Meet me at the rendezvous.
[Hunter] I'll get the head.
You get this lockdown lifted.
- [comm beeps]
- Trace, where are you?
[Trace] Down here!
Catch!
[grunts] Got it! Come on.
[both] I've got it!
[droid chatter]
Hope you're not
expecting gratitude.
[Hunter] Should I have
let the droids shoot you?
[Omega shouts, grunts]
- Thanks!
- [Rafa shouts]
I have the droid head!
[Echo] Nice work.
Now hang tight.
[electronics power down]
[Tech] You shorted
out the entire system.
[Echo] I had to
override the lockdown.
Wrecker, get to the
main control panel.
[Wrecker] Whoa, whoa! Whoa...
I can't reach the platform.
[Echo] It's the only way to reboot
the whole facility. Figure it out!
[Wrecker] Yeah, that's
easy for you to say!
[sighs]
[Echo] Wrecker, hurry.
[Wrecker groaning]
[grunting]
Don't look down. Don't
look down. Don't look down.
[grunting]
- [Tech] Wrecker, what are you waiting for?
- [groaning, grunts]
[alarm blares]
[shouts, grunts]
I'll take that.
[grunting]
[Tech] Wrecker, the system's
online. Now get down here.
[groans]
My... [grunts] ...head.
[whispering] Good soldiers...
[inhales sharply, groans]
[grunts]
Good... soldiers... [groans]
[droid chatter]
[Hunter] Why are you
after that tactical droid?
That's not your business, clone.
[Hunter] It is today.
- [comm beeps]
- Rafa, I've got the target.
Meet me at the north exit.
Little busy right now.
[grunts]
[Omega grunts, panting]
[grunting]
Hunter, I'm stuck on the
conveyor. I need help.
[Hunter] I'm on my way.
- What are you doing?
- I'm taking down the support posts.
Follow me!
Who put you in charge?
[metal creaks]
[Rafa screams]
[grunting]
Hunter!
Hang on, Omega!
Hey, you maniac, you
almost got me killed!
[grunts]
[screams]
Hey, over here! Hurry!
[grunting]
I can't reach!
Grab something!
[whimpers]
[grunts]
[Hunter grunts]
[Hunter] We got you, kid.
Are you okay?
Yeah. [Panting]
[Hunter] Thank you.
You're welcome.
- [metal clanks]
- [Rafa screams, grunts]
Oh, I'm fine. Don't worry
about me or anything.
[droid chatters, groans]
Well, this has
been a real treat,
but as you can see, the
tactical droid is ours.
[Hunter] We can
debate this later.
If we wanna get out of here,
we need to work together.
Fine, but I still
don't like you.
[Hunter] I'm used to it.
[Tech] Wrecker,
come in. Wrecker?
[grunts]
- No. No. No, no, no.
- [Tech] Wrecker?
[Crosshair] Good
soldiers follow orders.
[grunts, pants]
[Hunter] All the exits are blocked.
And it's about to get worse.
A larger wave of police
droids is headed our way.
We need a diversion.
What we need is a diversion.
Is there an echo in here?
- [Echo] Yes.
- What?
I'm Echo.
Really?
Okay, Echo, we
need a distraction.
And he can help with that.
What's that thing gonna do?
We need an army to get out of
this. And we happen to have one.
[whirring]
[Echo] If you activate those clankers,
they'll start shooting at us.
Not if we're controlling the
droid who's controlling them.
[Tech] Excellent idea.
That should do the trick.
[beeps] Cannot
transmit... [powers down]
It didn't work.
[Tech] It will, once
we boost the signal.
And this will help me
access the program.
[device powers up]
[beeping]
- [comm beeps]
- Wrecker, do you copy?
[grunting]
[Omega] Wrecker, where are
you? We need your help.
[grumbles]
[Wrecker] On my way.
Brilliant plan, Trace.
Really. One of your best.
We just need a little more time.
[Wrecker screams]
[Wrecker laughing] Yeah!
I got tired of you guys
having all the fun.
Now, him I like.
[Tech] Hang on. The data
exchange is nearly complete.
[beeping]
Done!
[tactical droid]
What is happening?
Activate battle droids. Command
them to attack all police droids.
Affirmative.
[battle droid 1] Huh?
What's happening?
[battle droid 2] I
don't know. Did we win?
New command sequence. Your target
is factory security personnel.
[battle droid 1 screams]
[battle droid 2]
Orders are orders.
[screams, grunts]
[Echo] Never thought I'd see
battle droids helping us.
[Hunter] That's
our cue. Move out!
[Tech] Mission accomplished.
[Hunter] Nice work.
- [comm beeps]
- R7, we're ready for a pickup.
[R7 whistles, beeps]
We're almost there.
Trust me. You'll see us.
No!
Yeah!
Nice shot.
It's all about tuning
out distractions.
He's here. Let's go!
[R7 beeps]
All that work for nothing.
Whoever Cid's buyer is
isn't gonna be happy.
Let me get this straight.
You knew how dangerous the
information on the tactical droid is,
but you didn't know who
you were giving it to?
We're being paid to acquire
and deliver, not ask questions.
Our contact needed that information
to fight back against the Empire.
They're trying to help people
and make things better.
Why aren't you fighting for the Empire?
Isn't that what you clones do now?
Not all of us. We're different.
Yeah, I've heard that before.
You should come
visit us sometime.
Isn't that part of Ord
Mantell a little... seedy?
Very. It's great!
Keep working on that bow, kid.
I will. Bye!
Bye, Omega.
[footsteps departing]
Here.
What's this?
Tech copied the tactical droid's intel
to this data rod before it got destroyed.
Why are you giving it to us?
You'll use it for
the right reasons.
Huh. Maybe you are different.
To be honest, things were clearer
when we were just soldiers.
Take it from me.
In the end, we all choose sides.
Patch him through, R7.
[R7 whistles, beeps]
We acquired the tactical
droid data from Corellia.
And we had help.
It was a squad of rogue clones,
and I know where to find them.
Thought you might wanna know.