[wind whistling]
[child laughing]
- [parent] Race you there. [laughing]
- [child laughing continues]
Mommy, how far does it go?
[Gloria] Forever.
- [parent laughing]
- [child groans, shrieks, laughs]
Gloria.
No.
I... I... I have to go back.
[breathing heavily]
[softly] One sec.
Where...
Where's the water?
It's right here.
[Gloria breathes heavily]
[nurse] You missed a dose.
That's all.
[Gloria groans]
I have to find them. [exhales heavily]
It's okay.
You're okay.
[breathing heavily]
[Diego] She's taking it with her.
Should we send someone?
No. Leave it.
Are you sure?
Keep following her.
[computer whirring]
[computer chimes]
[door opens]
- [switch clicks]
- [door closes]
[Juliette] Morning.
- [computer beeps]
- How's the baby?
She's good.
- [computer chimes]
- [inhales deeply] You've got messages.
First one's an apology from maintenance.
For what?
It says they broke your vase,
and they've taken it to be repaired.
Why were they there in the first place?
I don't know how things are
in the Down Deep,
but up here we learn early not to question
the workings of maintenance
unless you want your toilet
to stop working.
Down in Mechanical,
we fix things ourselves.
Uh, I'm heading out for a bit.
And you're not gonna tell me
where you're going.
Something I need to take care of
in the Mids.
[inhales sharply] There's another message.
"Mayor Holland requests meeting
with Sheriff Nichols first thing this a.m.
Please acknowledge receipt."
- Well, acknowledge it.
- So, I should tell him you're on your way.
Tell him I'll have to reschedule.
You're gonna brush off the mayor
a day after the holiday
with the whole Silo still on edge.
I'm not worried about the mayor,
just like I'm not worried about
leaving you in charge for a few hours.
[Molly on radio]
Karins for Billings. Do you copy?
[Juliette] You should get that.
[Paul sighs]
Billings.
[citizens chattering]
- [nurse] Can I help you?
- Yeah, I'm looking for Gloria Hildebrandt.
- She here?
- I'm sorry.
I'm not authorized
to give out that information.
You're... Why not?
- Like I said, I'm not authorized.
- Authorized. Right.
Do you see this? This...
Wait, hold on.
This makes me authorized to know, right?
- So, is she here or not?
- [stammers] Um, she is, Sheriff.
Great. I want to ask her some questions.
I'll take you back,
but you should be prepared.
For what?
Uh, you might not get
the answers you're hoping for.
Gloria, you have a visitor.
Gloria, I'm, uh, Sheriff Nichols.
I found them.
She suffers from hallucinations.
They're a symptom of her condition.
Advanced vascular dementia.
[Gloria]
Right where I left them by the water.
What... What water?
[nurse] Uh, it's best not to disturb her.
The water they don't want us
to know about.
She gets agitated,
says things that make no sense.
- [shushes] Wait.
- We keep her as comfortable as possible.
I wanna take her for a walk.
Gloria, would you like that?
Would you like to go for a walk with me?
No, that's not possible.
She's not cleared to leave the ward.
- I will clear it, okay?
- You can't.
- There's an order to keep her here.
- By who?
Judge Meadows.
If there's nothing else,
I think you should leave.
[Kath] Excuse me, Deputy.
I'd like to report a crime.
My husband forgot his lunch this morning.
I'll make sure he's apprehended, ma'am.
[Kath] Hmm.
[both chuckle]
[whispering] Oh, my God.
- [shushes]
- Oh, shit.
Hey.
- How are you feeling?
- Better.
You didn't have to come all the way
up here.
I wanted to show off
how important her daddy is.
- Guess she's not too impressed. [chuckles]
- As long as she's not crying.
[chuckles]
Was hoping to meet the sheriff.
Where is she?
Yeah. Your guess is as good as mine.
Ah, forget it.
I could use a break. You want a coffee?
Always.
Come on.
I'll be in the cafeteria if you need me.
I need the sheriff.
- [Paul] Uh, she's not here.
- It's an emergency. [breathing heavily]
[grunts, sighs]
[Paul on radio] Billings to sheriff.
Do you copy? Billings to sheriff...
[secretary] Ma'am. Ma'am.
Ma'am, I told you.
- I told you she's not in.
- Where is she then?
Like I said, if you want to see the judge,
you request an appointment.
I don't need one. I'm the sheriff.
An appointment is part
of the protocol that comes...
I don't give a shit about protocol.
Okay, if she's not here, I'll wait.
- You'd be wasting your time.
- That's not your problem, is it?
She's out sick with a cold.
[sighs] When will she be back?
When she's feeling better.
- Uh, all deputies report to 26. All de...
- [grunts]
- [Paul] Sorry.
- [groans]
They're outta control.
- We're handling it.
- Like hell you are.
Sheriff Nichols,
if you hear me, come to 26 now.
Damn it. [stammers]
Sorry. Excuse me. Excuse me.
Sheriff's department. Out of the way.
Move, move. Sheriff's department.
[citizens clamoring]
- Where the hell is the sheriff?
- I don't know.
Hey, excuse me. Sheriff's department.
- Sheriff's department. Excuse me.
- Get out of the way. Coming through.
I'm trying to pass... I'm trying
to pass you. Sheriff's department.
Sheriff's department.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Hey! Sheriff's department.
[citizens clamoring]
- [grunts]
- [screams]
[straining]
[clattering]
[grunts, yelps]
- [grunting]
- [groans]
[grunts]
[straining]
[clamoring continues]
[citizens chattering]
Ow.
- What's going on?
- [Molly] There you are.
- Where have you been?
- What's happening?
If you hadn't turned off your radio,
you wouldn't have to ask.
Shit. I...
- The bar on 26 was trashed last night.
- By who?
The owner says a group
from the lower Mids.
They got too rowdy last night.
He cut 'em off.
When he showed up this morning,
he jumped to his own conclusions.
By the time we got there, the entire floor
was ready to tear each other apart.
The people are scared and they're angry,
and they need their sheriff.
- Billings.
- I'm not done.
In addition
to getting an elbow to the face,
I had to cover for you when the mayor
turned up asking why you never showed.
I lied for you.
- Okay. I'm sorry.
- We're past that.
You have to come clean right now.
I want a reason why you are neglecting
your duties and dishonoring that badge.
- Otherwise, I have no choice...
- George Wilkins was murdered.
What?
Just like Jahns and Marnes and Trumbull.
Trumbull?
You told Judge Meadows he jumped.
Yeah,
'cause that is what she wanted to hear.
[sighs]
You want me to be honest with you?
I have no idea what I'm doing. Okay?
I came up here 'cause of George,
and the only thing I figured out is
that the man that I love...
He lied and he used me,
and I just still want to find out
why he got killed.
And now that somehow is connected
to Jahns, to Marnes,
to why Holston went out
and to why his wife before that went out.
So you're asking me to look the other way
as you pull on a thread that's connected
to four murders and two cleanings?
Yes.
[inhales sharply]
George Wilkins's case was closed.
That is...
until we found one of his relics
in Trumbull's apartment,
which is related
to our larger relics investigation.
So, technically it can be seen
as an opening to reexamine George's case.
Thank you.
Thank the Pact.
And just promise you'll see the mayor?
I'll see the mayor. First thing tomorrow.
You should go home.
You... You look like crap.
- [Paul sighs]
- One more thing. Um...
Do you know where Meadows lives?
I'd ask why, but something tells me
this is one of those moments
I'm supposed to look the other way.
Level 15. Manager's Row.
If you want to get in her good graces,
she has breakfast delivered every morning.
She likes bacon and eggs.
[sighs]
[door closes]
[machinery whirring]
I was on my way
when I saw your lights in the sky.
They're gone now.
Oh. They're not gone. They're just hiding.
You're not a fan of mushrooms, I take it?
Just 'cause we live underground
doesn't mean we have to eat fungus.
- I think they're pretty good, actually.
- Hmm.
- Mmm.
- Well, guess we could agree to disagree.
What do you do when you're not here?
Uh, I'm a systems analyst.
- You work in IT?
- Mm-hmm.
And whatever
computer problems you're having,
I promise that they are not my fault, so...
Mmm.
So you knew Mayor Holland
before he became mayor?
Oh. "Know" is a bit of a stretch,
you know?
He once lectured me
on the proper protocol for unplugging
a toaster in the break room, and so...
- Yep, that sounds like him. Hmm.
- Hmm. [chuckles]
- There. Look.
- Where?
[Juliette] See?
- Oh, uh...
- Oh.
I think that is here,
which means there should be
another one there.
Wonder how long they've been there...
like, if they've always been there...
Even before,
when people used to live outside.
Wondered the same thing. [chuckles]
Have you ever noticed anything strange,
besides the lights in the sky?
- What do you mean?
- Like a clue
to what it was really like out there?
Mmm. [inhales deeply]
No, but, uh...
Well, there was this one time that, uh,
I saw a light move across the sky
and then disappear.
[kisses]
Uh...
- Uh, hey, um, I'm sorry.
- Enough, wait, um...
Uh, I thought that
because of what I said yesterday
- about wanting to...
- It's okay. I shouldn't have...
Um, I'm gonna go.
[Lukas sighs]
[Lukas stammering]
No, it's okay. I've got it.
[Juliette sighs]
[no audible dialogue]
[Bernard] We have a problem.
Okay.
I've received a threat.
- What?
- No, it's not, um...
No, I'm gonna get you a security detail.
Uh, Sheriff,
I know it's not your inclination,
but I need you to listen.
Have a seat.
The other day, after Sims accused you
of planting evidence,
I was informed
that Judge Meadows was not pleased
with my intervention on your behalf.
She sent Sims with a warning that
if I were to obstruct her efforts again,
she would use some contortion of the Pact
to remove me.
Years ago, I... [sighs]
...made a choice to stay out of her way.
To protect your job.
Of course.
But my job in IT isn't any job.
I know you think it's the generator
that keeps the Silo running...
'Cause it is.
'Cause without power, we have nothing.
It's how the power is used.
To water crops,
transmit messages, to circulate air.
All of these invisible functions
are controlled by the servers in IT.
Now, if the servers were to fall into
the hands of the wrong person,
no amount of power
from the generator would matter.
Do you think Meadows would hijack
the servers?
I know I don't want to wait around
to find out.
We need to find something
that we can use to wall her in,
to keep her from stepping
outside her bounds.
There is something I've been looking into.
What is it?
According to the Pact,
I can't discuss ongoing investigations.
[chuckles] You sound like Billings.
He's not so bad.
He's your replacement.
Whatever it is you're onto,
I hope you get to the bottom of it
before Judge Meadows gets rid of you.
Because as soon as she does,
there's nothing either of us can do
to stop her.
[Meadows] Leave it there, Carl.
Not Carl.
It's the sheriff.
I'm here with your breakfast.
Leave it and go.
I wanna ask you some questions.
[Meadows sighs] I'm not well.
My first one has to do with your policy
of locking up citizens
and then drugging them against their will.
[door closes]
I wasn't expecting company.
I've been sick.
Yeah. That's what your secretary said.
Didn't stop you from forcing your way
in here and violating my privacy.
Don't worry. You'll get it back.
As soon as you tell me why you're keeping
Gloria Hildebrandt captive in Medical.
Who?
The fertility counselor.
Oh, her.
It's for her own good.
You're drugging her 'cause you think
she said something to Allison Becker
that made her want to go out.
I don't know
where you're getting all this.
In Gloria's file.
Gloria said to her that she's not the type
the Silo wanted having children,
so I wanna talk to her.
Why?
The relic investigation,
the one you approved.
She's been on your watch list for years.
I figured she might know something.
You're not a good liar, Sheriff.
Then let me talk to her,
and I'll leave you alone.
- I'm not stopping you.
- Her brain is filled with drugs.
Gloria doesn't have dementia any more
than you have a cold.
Oh. So, not satisfied with sheriff,
a post that you're not qualified to fill,
- you're now diagnosing people?
- You don't want me to be sheriff.
I want to talk to Gloria.
So why don't you lift
whatever medical order she's under,
and then I'll turn in my badge
by the end of the week.
I want you to go
before I summon Judicial security.
Don't threaten me with Sims.
I'm making you a good offer.
Let me take Gloria out of Medical
for a few hours,
and then I'll be back down in Mechanical
before you know it.
- It's not possible.
- Course it is. You lift the order.
I can't.
You're the judge.
I said I can't, and there isn't anything
that I can do about it.
You need to stop doing what you're doing.
Not until I find out what I wanna know.
[clicks tongue, inhales deeply]
They'll never let you.
Who will not let me? What do you mean?
Who are they?
[Meadows slurps]
[sighs]
Is this how it works?
[Meadows swallowing, inhaling sharply]
The apartment, the relics...
You get to keep them
as long as you're quiet?
Wow.
No wonder you stay in here,
drinking your cold medicine.
[sighs] You don't know anything about me.
Now get out!
- [Sims] Stop.
- [mouse clicks]
Nichols visited Hildebrandt in Medical?
- Yesterday.
- Show me.
[watcher 1 clears throat]
How long have those been there?
- They were there yesterday.
- You should have told me.
Sorry, sir. We'll send someone in.
[citizens chattering]
[Pete] Jules?
[sighs]
Y... You wanna come in?
[light switch clicks]
They transferred me here after...
It's small, but I'm only here to sleep.
[breathing shakily]
I've thought so many times about...
[stutters]...what I'd say to you if you...
if you came back.
And now you're here,
I don't even know where to start.
Don't worry about it.
That's not why I'm here.
I, uh... I want to ask you for a favor,
and then I'll be out of your way.
That's not what I want.
There's a patient in long-term care,
um, and I need you to help me get her
out of there for maybe one, two hours.
Whoa, just... [stammers]
...hold on a minute.
I think she's being held and drugged
against her will.
I need the drugs to wear off,
so I can find out why.
[shushes]
You shouldn't be talking like that.
It's dangerous. I can't do that.
Yeah. Yeah, I should have known
you wouldn't come through.
[door opens]
Wait.
[sighs]
- Oh.
- Oh... [chuckles]
Sorry, Doctor. [chuckles]
I didn't hear you coming.
I, uh... I just came to raid
your medicine cabinet.
I'll get the inventory sheet
for you to sign.
I just came to nab two aspirin.
I thought I could tough it out,
but this headache has other plans.
[chuckles]
I'm heading home for the night.
Help yourself.
Thank you.
Gloria, can you hear me?
I've come to take you for a walk.
How would you like to visit the nursery?
[whispering] Babies.
[door closes]
[gasps]
[baby fusses]
- Did anyone see you?
- I don't think so.
[panting] We're safe now.
I don't know why,
but they don't listen in here.
Gloria? Gloria, do you remember me?
I'm the sheriff. We met yesterday.
- They've got her on a sedative.
- Yeah, I know. I told you.
Well, it could take five or six hours
for it to flush through her system.
- [sighs]
- We got to get her back
- before the night nurse starts his rounds.
- Fuck.
I know you're frustrated.
Let's step back and take a deep breath.
That didn't work when I was five.
It still doesn't.
[exhales heavily]
There's gotta be something we can do.
Can we... Can we... Can we give her coffee?
Can we... Can we put her underneath
a cold shower? Anything?
[Pete] She's not a machine
we can switch on and off.
So that's it? You won't even try?
[breathes heavily]
I could try giving her something
to reverse the sedation.
Why didn't you say that before?
- 'Cause it doesn't always work.
- [Juliette] Okay.
[breathing shakily]
There can be side effects.
They are doing this to her,
and I need to find out why.
So, please.
Okay. I'll get some things.
Gloria, can you hear me?
- [Gloria breathing heavily]
- [Juliette] Wha...
- [Gloria grunts]
- What's wrong?
This is what I was afraid of.
- What's happening to her?
- Shit! She's having a seizure.
[Gloria groans]
[Pete] Jules, I need your help.
[Gloria groaning]
- It's okay. You know what to do.
- Okay. Okay.
[Gloria groaning]
One one thousand. Two one thousand.
Three one thousand.
Four one thousand. Five one thousand.
Six one thousand. Seven one thousand.
Eight one thousand. Nine one thousand.
Ten.
- Eleven. Twelve.
- [Gloria whimpering]
[Gloria gasping, groaning]
[Gloria hyperventilates, groans]
It's abating.
[breathing heavily] Is she okay?
[Gloria gasping, breathing shallowly]
[Pete] Are you?
Yeah. Yeah... [sniffs]
...Yeah. I'm fine.
[Pete sighs]
[Gloria breathing shallowly]
[Pete] We shouldn't wake her.
It'll have to wait.
[Juliette sighs]
- [door unlocking]
- [hinges creaking]
[keys jangling]
- [switch clicks]
- [mechanical whirring]
- [keypad beeping]
- [electronic tone]
[Diego] We lost the sheriff.
She was last seen heading into Medical.
We figured she was coming back for
the old woman, but she went the other way.
Must have gone someplace
where there's a camera down.
- Ah, she wouldn't know that.
- Maybe she lucked into a blind spot.
Where are the blind spots on Medical?
We've been repurposing cameras
from down there for years.
The last few we took
went to replace the busted ones on 52.
Look, we try and keep
the main areas of Medical covered but...
But none of you have any idea
where she could be? None of you?
Then get a map and start checking
every single room for what we're missing.
What?
That badge looks good on you.
My daughter, the sheriff.
Yeah, well, it's not for long, so...
What's this about, Jules?
Why would I tell you?
[sighs] I need a coffee.
- You want a cup?
- [Juliette] Nope. Thanks.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Oh, where am I?
Gloria?
You're... You're in the nursery.
Oh, why?
I'm the sheriff.
I... I've... I brought you here 'cause
I need to ask you some questions.
You're not... You're not the sheriff.
He's...
That was Holston. Holston Becker.
He went out three years
after his wife Allison went out to clean.
- [Gloria breathing shakily]
- And you spoke to her about her fertility.
- Oh.
- Look, I know this is a lot to remember,
but I really need you to try.
Did... Did the two of you
- talk about anything else?
- [door opens]
[Pete] How is she?
She's... She's still out of it.
I... I'm running out of time. And...
- [sighs] Oh. [breathes shakily]
- Gloria. Gloria.
I'm Dr. Nichols.
I'm just gonna listen to your heart. Okay?
Nichols... [breathes deeply]...Nichols.
I know you. I know you.
- What do you want from me?
- It's okay. It's okay. He's my dad.
- He's just trying to help...
- He works for them.
- [Juliette] What is she talking about?
- [Gloria panting] It was him.
- He was my doctor.
- What is she talking about?
- Was... Was she one of your patients?
- [Gloria] You. It was you.
- Answer me, were you?
- [Gloria] You. It was him.
I don't... [stammers]
It would have been 40 years ago.
- He stopped me from having a baby.
- What? Is that... Is this true?
- [Gloria] It was you!
- Jules, I, uh...
- [Gloria] Making it all come back.
- [Juliette] No. You're upsetting her.
I'm not the one
who's put her through this.
- Go. Get out of here. Get out.
- [Gloria] No. Not again.
- Hey, Gloria. Look at me. Look at me.
- No! No.
- It's okay. He's gone. He's gone.
- [door opens, closes]
Hey, what did you mean,
he worked for them?
- What do you mean...
- [stammers] I don't want to be here.
- It's okay.
- [sobs]
Listen to me. They are doing this to you.
They're drugging you
so that you will forget.
I wanna forget.
I want to be anywhere but here.
I don't trust you. [breathes shakily]
[Juliette sighs]
Oh. [breathing shakily]
- [gasps]
- You've seen this before, haven't you?
Oh. Oh. [sighs] Oh, my.
- Where did you get this?
- It belonged to someone I knew. George.
I was told he got it from you.
Little George?
He's not the one I gave it to.
I gave it to his mother.
- [stammers] I can't remember her name.
- It's okay. It's okay.
- She... She was one of us.
- What do you mean "one of us"?
[Gloria breathing heavily]
I don't know you,
and I don't know what you want.
Have you heard of the Flamekeepers?
No.
That's because they erased us.
- [Juliette] Who did?
- The Silo.
They've been trying since the rebellion.
That's when they put something
in the water so memories would fade.
What?
They wanted to erase the past
and anyone who tried to preserve it.
I don't understand.
Who were the Flamekeepers?
The people who fought back,
who kept things, like this book.
To keep their memories alive.
- Are you one of them?
- Yes, I was.
U... Until they put our flame out.
You said my dad stopped you
from having a baby.
- They wanted us to die off.
- [Juliette, softly] What?
They made us think we had a chance
of having a family, but we never did.
Wait. And the doctors knew about this?
[Gloria] They had to.
They said they were taking out
our birth control.
But it was a lie.
I figured it out...
- [Juliette gasps]
- ...after we failed our second lottery.
Henry, my husband,
he wasn't a Flamekeeper,
and he wanted children so badly.
And I knew he'd never
have a chance with me
and he'd never go if I told him
the truth. So, I pushed him away.
I ran into him once
when he was with his children,
and he pretended not to know me.
Seeing what they took from us,
I couldn't do it anymore.
So, I gave my most treasured relic
to the last Flamekeeper I knew.
And that was George's mom?
Yeah. Her name, it was Anne.
She died not long after that.
Her poor little boy had no one.
When was the last time you saw him?
Did... Did he say... Did he say
anything to you about a hard drive?
Oh, I kept tabs on George
when he was growing up,
but I...
I lost track of him over the years.
How is he?
When?
Last year.
He, um... He fell off the stairs,
and it wasn't an accident.
This place, it's...
They may be keeping me drugged,
but at least I can escape.
Look at this.
Let me find it.
The water.
They called it the ocean.
I've pictured myself there so many times,
but I'll never know what it sounded like
and how it smelled.
[baby babbles]
Can I hold it?
[baby fussing]
[softly] Yeah, sure.
- [Gloria exhales deeply]
- [baby babbling]
Oh. Hello.
Hello.
You're Hanna Nichols's daughter.
Yeah. Did you know her?
I remember hearing about her from Anne.
George's mom knew my mom?
Well, she was helping your mother
with something.
I... I can't remember what.
It was some kind of magnifying device.
Do you know, I was always really surprised
that they let a woman like Hanna Nichols
have children.
Was my mom a Flamekeeper?
She shared the same curiosity.
It's the one thing
that they can never breed out of us.
When I heard what had happened to her...
it really felt like
we'd lost one of our own.
[door opens]
- How is she?
- I'm taking her back.
Well, it's not safe for you, Jules.
[Juliette sighs]
You are the last person
I would ever trust to tell me what's safe.
I would never put you in danger.
But you would trick your patients
into believing
their birth control has been removed?
I didn't have a choice.
If I wanted to do this work
to help people and...
Help? The only ones you're helping
are the ones trying to breed people out.
You have to understand.
They never told me anything about that.
When they came to me,
they said this was necessary
for long-term survival
to prevent genetic disease
from running rampant.
But why lie to people?
Why give them false hope?
Did you ever think to question that?
Of course I did.
I always wondered if somehow they
wanted to punish the ones they picked.
And yet, you just went along
with whatever they said?
There are consequences
to asking questions.
We both know that.
[Juliette sighs]
- I know you think I betrayed Mom.
- No, don't.
[scoffs]
Clearly she wasn't the only one
that you betrayed.
Shit, I got her.
[night nurse] Hey. Hey!
What's going on? Is she okay?
[Juliette] One of my deputies found her
wandering around the stairs, so...
You said she didn't go back
to Hildebrandt.
- She... She didn't.
- Then how the hell do you explain that?
- I don't know.
- Find out where they just came from. Now!
And stay on them!
[night nurse] Sheriff, I can assure you...
I'm going to escort her
back to her room and file a report.
[door opens]
Oh, wait. I wanna walk.
Okay.
[Gloria sighs]
- You okay?
- Yeah, I think so.
[breathes shakily]
[door closes]
- Um...
- [Gloria breathing deeply]
Can I see it one more time?
[softly] Sure.
[sighing] Oh.
- [Gloria] You keep it safe.
- Yeah, I will.
My flowers, they're gone.
I remember now. Sheriff Holston was here.
- When?
- I... I don't... I don't know.
Not long ago. I lose track.
He brought flowers,
and he put them right there.
- In front of the mirror?
- Yes.
- [Juliette] Never seen this one before.
- Maybe it's what he wanted you to see?
[Juliette] No idea what it is.
[whispers] I think they can see us
through the mirror.
- That's why Holston put flowers there.
- [whispers] What?
[whispers] They've got these devices
like the sensors outside,
and I think they're watching us.
[Gloria exhales deeply]
[whispers] Do you remember anything else
when he was here? Anything he said?
[Gloria whispers] No, no.
He... He wasn't here for very long.
And he spent most of his time
working on that vent.
- She's blocked our view.
- [Sims shushes]
What is she doing?
- The problem is we only have audio.
- No, Diego.
The problem is
she knows there are cameras.
[Gloria] What is it? What did you find?
Send the raiders. Now!
[Juliette sighs]
Oh.
[whispers] I can't stay.
They're gonna be coming.
- You're the last Flamekeeper now.
- No.
You didn't ask for it. It's not fair.
But it's the way it is. It's down to you.
- No.
- If you let it die, the truth dies too.
I have to go.
What would your mother want you to do?
- I wish I could ask her, but I can't.
- No, you can't.
But do you know why she killed herself?
Where is she?