There is nothing a father
wouldn't do for his son.
Your mother
never understood this.
She looked at you
and saw a monster.
I saw potential.
When a bully took your money,
you took his eye.
When they called you crazy,
you took their tongues.
But I brought you here today.
Was it generosity?
Love?
No.
It's so what I built
doesn't die with me.
So my legacy can live on,
because a father and his son
is everything.
I have a job that I can
only trust with one man.
You.
My most ruthless soldiers
were watching our cash houses,
and they let this Dominic
Toretto burn what is mine.
I'll kill Dominic Toretto.
I'll kill 'em all.
Kill them?
You'd show them mercy?
No, my son.
When suffering is owed,
never accept death as a payment.
Make Toretto suffer.
Now the work begins.
And in there,
today we'll put our family
on a path to real power.
Let's get started.
Shit!
Hey, there's too many of them!
-We're not gonna make it.
-You're right. We aren't.
-You are.
-No, I'm not leaving you.
Now, you stick with the plan.
It was always the plan.
Get him.
You had it.
I didn't have it.
B, no one starts
at the finish line.
You got to have faith.
Remember today's lesson.
Find the line,
feel the car,
and let it fly.
It's okay to be afraid.
Sometimes fear can be
the best teacher.
I wasn't scared.
-Everyone gets scared, son.
-You don't.
You're not afraid of anything.
We better hurry.
Great-Grandma just flew in.
And she's making
her famous maduros.
We got to get to those
before Uncle Roman does.
Now, that's something
to be afraid of.
You have been dead.
-It's time to get you living.
-Told you guys,
I don't need that.
There, profile done.
You're welcome.
Now, you give it
about three, four days...
It never happens instantly.
-Wait, what?
-Hmm.
Wow.
Let me see
your profile picture again.
He must have
put a filter on there.
What are you guys looking at?
-Oh, wait. No, no, no, no.
-They're just video games, man.
-H-H-Hold on, man.
-Just videos, man.
Can I sit next to you?
-Boy nosy.
-You drifting yet?
I am.
You should've seen us.
It was so cool, Mom.
Hey!
¡Oye, familia!
I am starving!
Come on.
I also want a hug from
every single person in--
Oh.
-Ah.
-You see the line?
We're all waiting in line
for this love, abuelita.
-Oh, yeah.
-Wait till you taste this.
It's really good.
I put myself out for this one.
Oh.
Okay, everybody pipe down,
please.
Abuelita would like
to say something.
Piping and downing, please.
As I look out
at this wonderful family,
I am filled with so much pride.
The kind of pride that my son--
your father--
would have enjoyed
if he were here.
I know that this road
has been very hard
and also not fair.
And yet here you are,
despite all of the odds,
building this magnificent
leg...
It is a legacy that will go on
for generations.
No one can take it away.
Not now.
Not ever.
Yeah!
To familia.
Familia.
Siempre. Always.
Hey, these new Nikes, man.
Stop playing! Goddamn...
Come on, Roman.
The agency put you in charge,
and you said I get to drive.
See, what I really need
is I need your brain.
Words Roman Pearce
has never said.
So talk me through it again.
I need details.
Yeah, the agency got a tip on
some stolen military hardware.
Tomorrow, a next-gen
quantum computer chip
will be transported
through the streets of Rome,
and they need us to steal it.
I checked Roman's intel.
It's legit.
Of course it's legit.
We're talking 'bout Rome.
Rome. Roman.
Come on, man.
That's like planning a heist
in my backyard.
Only thing you know about Rome
is "ro-man" noodles.
One thing
you didn't explain to us is:
Why the hell
do we need a RC car,
a gold Lamborghini
and 12 tanks of laughing gas?
Yes, I'm in,
'cause you are definitely
going to need
all the brains you can get.
You up to something.
-Hey, Rome...
-Don't talk to me, man.
Don't talk to me.
-All right.
-You know what?
The disrespect
is gon' have to stop.
Now!
That's just my--
You know what I'm saying?
Me just, you know,
practicing my leadership voice.
I see what's going on.
Tej, you think you slick, bro.
Look at you.
Spying on me.
What's up with
this old boat anchor?
No fuel injection.
I mean, I'd expect
something bigger
and better from you, Dom.
Little B and I
are building it together.
The carburetor
forces him to listen.
That's the problem nowadays.
-Nobody listens anymore.
-Well, you better watch out.
Little man's gonna be
a better wrench than any of us
by the time he's 12.
I mean, that's the whole point,
isn't it?
Pass it down.
Each generation
better than the last.
That's true.
That's fatherhood.
Come a long way from
the two of us popping gas trucks
-in the D.R., huh?
-We sure did.
Those were some tough times.
Those were some great times.
Oh, you...
Y-Y'all was in a meeting?
I'm sorry.
I-I ain't want
to interrupt y'all.
Han, let's go, man.
Roman asked if he could
lead this mission.
How could I tell him no?
But you know I can't let them
go to Rome without you.
Los bandoleros for life.
Lo bandolero for life.
You honor his name.
Hold us in your heart...
...and you will never
lose your way.
You will be better than me.
What are you looking at?
You.
-Kid's asleep.
-Mm-hmm.
How do you get more beautiful?
Is it here yet?
No.
-It'll come when the time
is right. -Mm.
You know, when we were
in the car today...
...B said, "Daddy,
you're never afraid."
But I am.
I'm afraid of losing a son.
Or a wife.
That's not gonna happen again.
You can keep your eyes
on that rearview all you want.
But you know what you miss?
What?
Eternity
in this moment.
I'm as surprised as you are.
I've imagined killing you
a thousand times.
Last time, there was six inches
of reinforced glass,
-guns...
-No!
...guards.
I couldn't reach you then.
Now I can.
You're gonna want to hear
my last words.
-Dom!
-No!
Did you hear Elena's last words
before you killed her?
Then don't you think I'd have a
goddamn good reason to be here?
Maybe the only reason
that's ever mattered to you.
Little B.
Wake up, sweetie.
We have an unwanted guest.
You know what to do.
What is it that you want?
Speak.
I met the devil tonight.
Honestly, I always thought
it was me.
So that was
kind of disappointing.
He came to my door.
He let himself in.
They say
when you're facing death,
your life flashes
before your eyes.
Are they right?
I'd start with who you are.
A question most can't answer
in a lifetime.
You have three seconds.
Before you bleed out
on my couch,
you might want to explain
why you're here.
I'm here
because the enemy
of my enemy
is you.
I am a man with
no name.
Heir to nothing.
And I'm here for
the same reasons you are.
Dominic Toretto.
You want to kill Dom?
Line's around the block.
No, no, no.
Never accept death
when suffering is owed.
But I need your help.
Your toys and your tech.
All your boys.
'Cause you're either with me
or you're...
I don't play well with others.
Then you'll have to watch
who you love most die.
You're looking at
who I love most.
You thought you could use
my own move against me?
I wasn't talking to you.
I was talking to Zeke.
Amir.
Kevin's dad.
Who could it be?
Cute kids.
Ooh.
They all had something to take
except that poor bastard.
Not even a kitty cat.
The rest of you have a choice.
Me or...
You want to control the world.
I just want to punish it.
I will remember this.
I think everyone will.
Huh. I need someone to help me
operate this, don't I?
Nerds?
Come with me.
All right, you know what to do
if you want to see
your families again.
Ciao.
Kill her.
Shit.
Did you think I would trust you?
It is hard finding good help
these days.
There's a war coming.
The sides are being chosen.
And everyone you love
will be destroyed.
Lost six pints of blood.
Normal person dies at four.
We're shipping her back
to our black site.
-She may not make it.
-But did her story check out?
We confirmed
the shooting downtown,
but her tech wasn't there.
And whoever took it
now has an electronic arsenal.
-You've alerted your people?
-Yeah, Mia and Brian are safe.
I tried to get in touch
with Roman, Tej, Ramsey, Han.
-No answer.
-Any idea where they might be?
In Rome.
Working for you.
Dom, we don't... we don't have
a mission in Rome.
It's a setup.
Shit.
We're going to Rome.
-Follow me.
-Yes, sir.
Son, you and I will finish
that driving lesson.
It's a promise.
No matter what happens.
And I always keep my promises.
Head back up.
So can somebody
please help me understand
how we're pulling off
a mobile heist
but I don't even get to drive?
Well, the sooner we break into
the truck and steal the chip,
the sooner you get to live
la dolce vita, okay?
Roman, the convoy's
almost in position.
Where the hell are you at?
You're supposed to be
running interference.
Romey-Rome's in the building.
You see me shining, baby.
We on my mission now.
Yeah, we all know
that this is your mission.
'Cause nobody else on Earth
would put Han in an Alfa.
You know, we'd already
be there if Roman wasn't
driving Fort Knox on wheels.
You know
what's under this hood, baby.
This car is sick.
What this old girl lacks
in horsepower,
she makes up for in agility.
Yeah, it's true.
While the Lamborghini has a V-10
with a Stage 3
UGR twin-turbo kit,
the Alfa will definitely have an
advantage in this environment.
What?
Oh, that's right.
I know stuff now.
Will you marry me?
That's all it took?
All those agency toys,
and you still can't reach Roman?
No cell phone,
emails or text messages.
Nothing's going through.
I even tried swiping right
on Han's dating app.
Whoever sent him
on this bogus mission
made for damn sure
we couldn't warn them.
Keep searching. They're close.
All right, everybody, showtime.
Here we go!
In position.
Cue Tiny Tej.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold up. Tiny Tej?
What are you talking about,
Roman?
All right, all right,
fire 'em up!
We never agreed on that.
You said you wanted to drive.
Now you driving.
What are you laughing at?
Don't...
Where'd you even get that?
Just so you know,
Tiny Tej's brain?
Still bigger than yours.
Back is blind.
Watch out, ladies.
This ain't "nun" ya business!
It's time to shine!
We're in. I have the wheel.
We're locked inside!
The truck's being
steered remotely.
And a one, and a two, and a...
Holy shit! What happened?!
Put a little too much in, huh?
Ready?
That was awesome!
Ooh.
Scusi!
They're stealing our truck.
And with us inside.
Just got reports of
two explosions near the Forum.
That's them.
Ready? And...
Wait, you hear that?
-What the hell is that?!
-I have no idea!
Oh, shit.
That's a big-ass bomb!
-What?
-Bomb!
Roman, you said
this was carrying chips
for a supercomputer.
That is not a chip.
It's a bomb!
What happens if it goes off?
What do you mean,
"What happens if it goes off?"
The Seven Hills of Rome
will be down to two and a half!
City-wide devastation,
countless lives lost.
You know, the thing bombs do.
We're coming to you.
All right, dorks.
What are we blowing up?
What?
The Vatican?
Wow.
Okay. I'll do it.
But you guys are going to hell.
That's their truck.
Oh, thank God. Dom, Letty.
Ooh. Look who's here.
You're right on time, Dominic.
Turn off the encrypted radio.
Ramsey?
We're being remote-controlled.
There's a bomb on board.
It's a DM-79 subnautical
high-yield neutron mine.
Ah! Found it.
I can disarm it
with an agency kill switch.
I just need physical hands
on the device.
-We have to stop that truck.
-Sorry, Captain America.
Can't let you do that.
We got to hurry!
The truck is speeding up.
-We got to block its path.
-I'm gonna get ahead of it.
Ramsey, Tej, strap in.
Whoop.
Ah-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
Dom, go ahead! I'm pinched!
Dominic.
Come on!
Damn it, he's fast.
Really? The clothesline?
Well, we can't drive it,
guess we're just
gonna have to roll it.
Holy shit! The truck's
about to go over the hill!
-We have to crash into it.
-We have to what?!
I'm so sorry, my gold baby!
It's not stopping!
Dom, the bomb is out.
Everybody, stay clear.
I got this.
No. We got this.
Letty!
Have we made them all
terrorists?
Their images have been
fed to the authorities.
All right, Bob!
I got to go kill that jerk
that's trying to disarm my bomb.
It's always something, you know?
Oh.
Remember, I still have your
families, so don't go anywhere.
Buongiorno, Roma!
All right.
Man, who the hell is that?
Hey! There he is!
Man of the hour.
Roman Pearce, team leader.
Can't wait to see you
get out of this one.
Oh, Letty!
I think I found our guy.
Hey, Letty. Vaffanculo!
I'm on him.
That pump's gonna blow.
Little Nobody, you're up.
-Moving to dis...
-Peekaboo!
-Get out of there!
It's gonna blow! -Oh, shit.
Boom.
We need to jam
the detonator now.
I got it, I got it.
Letty, don't lose him.
I can lock on to your location
and transmit
cellular interference
through your phone.
That should jam his detonator
and buy us some time.
Letty.
Bravo!
It's getting tricky, guys.
I can't stay on him
for much longer.
Ramsey, how deep is that river?
The Tiber? Uh...
Uh, 60 feet.
I mean, the water could
smother the explosion,
reduce its power
by ten times, maybe.
Damn it!
You missed me
by that much, baby!
I lost him. He's gone.
Damn!
He's out of our reach.
We can't jam the signal anymore.
Bad news, Dom.
I'm back in business.
You got 30 seconds to save Rome.
Dom, he armed the bomb,
and you're almost at the river.
15 seconds, Dom.
Dom, listen to me.
The Vatican's within
the blast radius.
Get out of there.
You've done
everything you could.
Not everything.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
What have we done?
Through your suffering,
I'll fulfill my destiny.
Come find me.
Your pain has just begun.
I'll see you soon, Dom.
Breaking news from Italy.
The capital Rome has been hit
by a massive explosion.
...to be
a large military weapon.
The Vatican has sustained
some structural damage.
...but no lives were claimed.
Authorities have identified
the terrorists as
these five individuals.
...as these five individuals,
led by this man.
-Dominic Toretto.
-Toretto. -Toretto.
Law enforcement is
working across borders,
mobilizing
an international fugitive hunt
-of unprecedented scale.
-I'm sorry, sir.
-I don't know how she got in.
-I do.
I stole your badge.
I'm done with it now, though.
Thanks.
Well, if it isn't, um--
Honestly, I-I don't know
what to call you.
Little Miss Nobody?
How about you call me
by my actual name?
Last I heard, Tess, you were
running ops in Damascus.
You think you can
walk in this room
just 'cause your daddy's
an agency legend?
I'm here because
someone needs to speak
on behalf of the defense.
What just happened in Rome
was an unmitigated disaster.
Casualties were kept
to a minimum,
but the impact was global.
And what do you think
happened in Italy?
Oh, sightseeing,
eating bucatini,
-stealing a 20-kiloton bomb.
-Oh, come on, Aimes.
-That's bullshit
and you know it. -Careful, now.
With Little Nobody
out of commission
and your daddy in the wind,
you're talking to the new boss.
Showtime.
Los Angeles, 2001.
Humble roots, local kids,
street racers
who became hijackers.
Graduated to
high-speed smuggling,
mobile jailbreaks,
train robberies.
If it could be done in a car,
they did it.
If it violates the laws of God
and gravity, they did it twice.
You write that yourself?
We first took notice in 2011,
Rio, when they robbed
a drug kingpin, Hernan Reyes,
left his body on a bridge.
My predecessor, Mr. Nobody,
saw potential,
so he recruited them--
freelance, of course.
They ran missions for us
in Abu Dhabi,
Tokyo, London,
New York, Tbilisi.
You ask me, we should've
cut ties years back,
but they had their champions.
That's their M.O.
To corrupt law enforcement.
Brian O'Conner.
Elena Neves. Luke Hobbs.
Everyone becomes family.
It's like a cult with cars.
Even Tess's dear old dad.
So we're all just
a barbecue and a beer away
from corruption?
What's your point?
Point is they're criminals.
Rome was a matter of time.
They've stolen
hundreds of millions of dollars
and at least one nuclear sub.
The real question is: How did
we let this go on so long?
This family has gotten their
hands dirty to keep ours clean.
They've driven to the gates of
hell and back for this agency.
Something is not right
with Rome.
It can't be.
It can and it is.
The agency is better than this.
We are smarter than this.
We should be standing with Dom
and his family.
That is the very least
that we can do.
If we don't act,
this blows back on all of us.
The fallout will be existential.
I'm asking for
full green-light authority.
Kill or capture
the Toretto clan by any means.
Aimes, what are you doing?
Looks like the ayes have it.
As your direct superior,
I don't give a shit about
anybody's heart of gold,
and I hate barbecues.
You know I'd make a
freight train take a dirt road,
so do not get in my way.
Okay.
I'll go my own way.
When Rome falls,
so does the world.
Well, it ain't no Roman holiday.
And you're no Gregory Peck.
Mm.
My family?
Your team's gone to ground.
They're safe for now.
They've taken Letty.
-Who's they?
-The agency.
And you've just shot
to number one
on the world's most wanted list.
Whoever did this wanted
to sever your ties to the agency
and isolate you
from your family.
Any attempt to contact your team
will be traced.
I need you to get a message
to Mr. Nobody.
You'll need a medium for that
or a magician.
He's done his disappearing act.
Just get the message out.
Tell him I'm ready
to have that Belgian,
and he'll know where to go.
I've got a message for you,
ducky.
The world is on fire,
and you want to keep running
into the burning building
to save lives,
but eventually the building's
gonna collapse on you.
I don't care about dying.
I only care about protecting
the people that I love.
You know why gladiators
never had families?
-Why?
-Because they knew
that every day
might be their last.
You're choosing a lonely way,
my darling.
Can't take anyone with you.
Bring God's Eye online.
-Yes, sir.
-Initiating.
Get me Toretto
and the others' locations
to the millimeter.
Sir, we have a problem.
The God's Eye tracking hardware
has been removed.
Tess.
I guess her visit
wasn't purely a social call.
Do me a favor.
She pops up on any grid,
let's see where she goes.
As for the rest, our fugitives
aren't unknown quantities.
Toretto has a sister, a son.
Until we find him,
find his family.
Oh!
Again.
Wow.
Are you cheating
on-on your favorite auntie?
It doesn't matter if you win
by an inch or a mile.
Winning's winning.
Where have I heard
that one before?
Go! Go!
Search everywhere!
We need them alive!
Get on the ground!
No! Mia! Let her go!
Run!
-What's up?
-Uncle Jakob?
Your dad sent me.
Change of plans.
Don't move!
I said don't move!
Do you have Little B?
B!
Freeze!
-You okay?
-Yeah.
Are you okay?
B!
Come, come.
Who the hell were those guys?
Agency. Rome was a trap.
Whole family's being targeted.
Okay, I got to get to Brian
and the kids...
Dom sent me to take him.
Remember that place
we said we'd go
if the world went to hell?
Dom wants the team
to meet there.
Yeah.
Okay, look.
Little B, you're gonna go
with Uncle Jakob.
Okay? You do whatever he says.
Yeah?
I'm gonna get you to your dad.
If that's okay with you.
Protect him with your life.
I love you, Jakey.
I love you, too, sis.
Let's do it.
Oh, my God.
Yo!
It's not that one.
It's this one.
Yep.
Wait, but...
Hmm?
I'm looking for someone.
You boys look like
you could use a drink.
How about a round on me? Huh?
As a matter of fact,
I will buy as many rounds
as they can handle.
Shots? No?
Shots?
Beers. Two of 'em.
Thanks.
Cheers.
Queenie told me
I could find you here.
Belgian?
Mr. Nobody said
he had a daughter.
He did?
Well, now that
he's gone missing,
I came in from the cold.
Your dad kept the agency
in line.
Now it feels like
all the anchors have been cut.
In a world where there is
no code, no one's safe.
You're right.
The agency has turned its back
on everything it stood for.
The new boss, Aimes, he's coming
for you with everything.
I'm buying you some time.
And borrowed their, uh,
little tracking device thingy.
Look familiar?
-God's Eye.
-Mm-hmm.
I'd put that
in a vault somewhere.
People pull vaults out of walls,
so I think it's safer with me.
I pulled a screen grab
off of a traffic cam
that they missed,
put it in God's Eye.
There was a hit in Rio.
You wouldn't happen to have
any enemies in Rio, would you?
-Reyes.
-Hernan Reyes?
Still pretty dead,
but he has a son, Dante.
So you're gonna
have to get me to Rio.
That's your second wish.
You have one more.
Letty.
Letty's in a black site prison
off of every map.
Then get her out.
Nobody can.
Nobody would.
Dom, I'm so sorry,
but what you're asking me to do
is impossible.
Nothing's impossible.
You just have to have faith.
Sneaking us out of Rome
in a shipping container
full of aftershave,
that was a terrible idea, Roman.
Wait, I think
I lost my sense of smell.
That is not aftershave.
That is tear gas.
Hey, man, I don't know
what y'all are talking about.
You know what I mean?
I smell magic.
I took a bottle for myself.
This is all thanks to you.
You know that, right?
No, see, you just got to follow
my "leat" as a "leater."
You see what I'm saying?
I'm a natural-born "leater."
Where are we?
I brought you back home, Ramsey.
The city with the most
amount of surveillance cameras.
Perfect.
-Dad know you drive this thing?
-He should.
I raced him in it.
And just so you know,
in the '90s,
if you were rolling in a 5.0,
it meant you were the man.
Like it or not,
it's still a 'Stang.
So, you know, respect.
You know what?
Traveling music.
I got this car when I was 13.
Did the repaint myself.
Rebuilt the motor, too.
Ah. Sometimes you just
can't help what you love, kid.
Are you gonna tell me
where we're going?
A place of mine your dad knows.
We're gonna meet him there.
So he's okay?
We'll meet him there.
This guy was an underwear model.
-What?
-Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Here we go and...
Little B, bring it back.
It's a boomerang.
It's a boomerang, maybe.
Ah...
Oh! Look at you!
That's feeling it.
That's called
feeling the vibrations.
It's just energy, man.
It's energy. It's vibrations.
Feel it! Feel it!
Come on! Come on!
You're clear, Director.
Fancy coat.
Expensive earrings.
Those got to hurt.
You really brought out
the big guns, huh?
I'm not here for the agency.
You could've confiscated that.
That scar on your left wrist,
you got it
the night you met Dom.
He said he was showing off.
I put an ultrasonic jammer
on the audio,
but the cameras
can still see us.
Look, I'm gonna
get you out of here,
but it's gonna take some time.
Time is what I don't have.
I need to get back to Dom.
I'm no good to anyone
in this cage.
I have a feeling you didn't come
all this way without a plan.
Game recognizes game.
If I make this move,
there's no coming back.
I like it already.
Okay. First, let's get you
out of this cell.
-It's gonna hurt.
-Hmm?
Work with me.
Open the door!
Knock it down!
Guards! Guards!
-Help!
-Let her go!
Let her go!
Really?
Que surpresa!
Look at this.
None of this happens
without you.
Welcome home.
Good to see you, bro.
Diogo, good to see you.
Ah. Look at you.
So, uh, I hear you got
a little heat on you.
Nah, I'm just looking
for someone.
How can we help?
You already did.
I need you to meet somebody.
A GOAT.
A living legend, literally.
You must be in
the winner's circle tonight.
I see you put in a RB26
in that, right?
L24 would never handle
this much boost.
My boy back home would approve.
I'm not looking for
anyone's approval.
Before you get ahead
of yourself, look around you.
We're all looking for
a little validation.
You racing or what?
Trust me,
you don't want that smoke.
I'm not here
for pink slips tonight.
You and everyone here.
Yeah!
A million dollars
for whoever can beat me.
Diogo, here.
Yes.
Isabel.
There will be
a race tonight, yes?
Yeah, maybe.
Pretty please, with me on top.
Dominic Toretto.
I knew you would come for me.
I'm sorry we didn't
get to meet in Roma.
We were both so busy.
I'm Dante. Enchanté.
And you were
fantástico, fabuloso, o cara.
He saved the Vatican.
Who does that?
Seriously. The Pope? God?
By the way,
did you see what I did there?
The ball through the city was
a bit of an homage
to my family's safe.
Except it was on fire.
You remember my father?
-Hernan Reyes.
-Yes.
I remember he thought he had
his foot on this city's neck.
But you know what happened?
I took him down.
Let's not argue
in front of the children.
You are absolutely right.
My father was a horrible man,
very bad daddy,
but I kind of liked him.
And you took him from me
when you stole our money
and left us
with nothing but suffering.
Well, that's what
I came here for.
To end that suffering.
Oh, and I didn't take
that money.
I burned it.
Uh-oh.
Well, Brazil is mine,
and I own this city.
Ooh.
You people think
you can buy everything.
But you can't buy the streets.
We stand with Dom.
Well, this is awkward.
So, how about we all just
start shooting each other
and see what happens?
Or we race.
If you win, you take me in.
If you lose...
Don't lose.
You all came 'cause
you wanted to see a race.
Let's race!
Ouch.
Ooh.
Black on black look good.
I know what you're thinking,
and, yes, the carpet
matches the drapes.
Thank you.
I can't believe I'm gonna race
the great Dominic Toretto.
I have butterflies.
You're just so impressive.
You've won so many races.
Everyone loves you.
You've saved so many lives.
I know.
It's like you're a...
a saint.
Saint Dominic.
And I've been studying you.
And watching you.
I can't figure it out.
How...
How do you choose?
How do you choose
the ones you save?
Cheguei.
Yahoo!
Yeah!
I'm beating you, baby!
Oh.
You're too eager.
That's what I'm talking about!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You shouldn't do that.
Dominic, who will you choose?
Who you gonna choose, Dom?
Are you gonna save her?
-Or are you gonna save him?
-Let's go, baby!
This race is mine!
Eeny, meeny, miny...
Looks like you made your choice.
Finally! Whoo!
Oh, no, Diogo!
Trick question. Everyone dies.
And one, two, three.
Boom!
Yeah!
I win, baby!
Keep coming, Dom!
There's so much more fun
to be had!
Come on.
Good morning, sunshine.
Goddamn it.
And then he was like, "Boom!"
And I was like, "Blam!"
And she was like, "What?"
I was like, "Shut up."
And now I'm the best racer
in the world, so...
Do not touch that. Let it dry.
You guys look fantastic.
I know the black is
very slimming and very scary,
but the pastels, you know,
they're in season,
and I feel like it tones down
the masculinity a little bit,
which we all need these days.
Did you know...
Listen to me.
Did you know that I was
legally dead for two minutes?
Two minutes.
Bob, pay attention.
And you know what I saw?
Nothing.
Not a goddamn thing.
But I do feel like
once he, uh...
cracked my skull open,
it just opened my mind.
Yeah, that's deep, right?
You're absolutely right, Bob.
We should get back to work.
Such a stickler.
All right. Let's see.
Should we take all their money?
You. You are evil.
Thank you for listening.
So, mi casa, su casa.
Let these dry,
finish those mojitos,
and, um, someone's gonna come
and bury you guys soon.
I'm gonna go wash my hair.
No.
What?
All right.
Whoa.
Cool. What is that?
That's a technical tool kit.
Don't worry, it's just
a bunch of awesome stuff
that you're never
gonna get to use.
Okay.
Eyes open. Hold still.
Don't smile like that.
It's unsettling.
Sweet.
Your new name is Chester...
-Chester? -...and you're
on a kayaking trip with
your handsome,
ripped Uncle Roger.
All right.
Now, time to get you
some new clothes.
You know, something
a little more chic than
pj pants, all right?
-From a gas station?
-From a gas station.
See, I just don't understand.
Why would the agency
turn they backs on us,
after all we've done for them?
That madman pinned it all on us,
and now we're
public enemy number one.
Well, Dom is gonna meet us
at the rendezvous point.
But in the meantime,
we have to stay under the radar.
And we got to get ready
to fight.
Wait, so we need guns,
artillery, tanks?
Yeah, but how are we gonna
get that with no money?
What?
We've been hacked.
Look. Every account.
Every dollar we made
over the last 20 years is gone.
He took everything.
We got heisted
during our own heist.
-Just decrypt the... Yeah.
-Decrypt the blockchain.
I'm on it. Then we can find
the transaction hash.
The transaction hash.
Gets us the receiving IPs.
Exactly.
English.
Following our money, genius.
We're trying to see
where he sent it.
The coding is next-level.
I've never seen
anything like this.
We need more computing power.
How are we gonna do that
if we broke?
What do you mean, "we" broke?
Wait, you holding out on us?
No wonder you've been so calm.
Bro, what-what d--
what do you think this is, bro?
You know what? Turn around.
"Turn around"? What do you...
What you mean, "turn around"?
Man, I'm a grown-ass...
-What-- N-- What are you doing?
-Hey, Roman, do not.
Please tell me
you're not wearing Spanx.
Oh, this ain't Spanx.
These banks.
But it's okay, bro. I got you.
All right?
You know what I mean?
Yeah. That's for you.
That's for you.
Let me see.
Han, you always good
for the bag,
'cause the bag
always come back, you know.
So what I need from
all of y'all, I need receipts.
Who is you talking to?
Got your receipt.
So where do we go
to shop off the grid?
I know a place.
Wait. The agency's after us.
Aren't they gonna see our faces?
Yeah, I'm counting on it.
The first rule of tradecraft:
you can't lose a tail
if they don't find you.
-Oh, sorry.
-Sorry.
I'll just-- Wait.
You know what, I'm just...
We'll just--
If you want to, uh, go.
Uh, we'll stay here.
-You guys, you guys go around.
-Go around? Great.
Go around.
Sir, we just got a hit
on the boy and his uncle.
The rest of the team
is still in Europe.
We're interfacing
with local authorities.
Forget authorities.
These people have been
outrunning the cops
since they could
reach the gas pedal.
Get word to
every snitch, smuggler,
hitter and hacker
we've ever used.
Money talks and so will they.
We're getting an alert
on Black Site A.
Tess just visited Ortiz.
They have a nice chat?
Guess not.
Run it back for me.
Stop. Zoom in.
Back-trace her flight path.
Find out where she was
before this.
That's where Dom is.
You knew who I was
all along, didn't you?
From the moment I saw you.
Your sister smiled with her eyes
and led with her heart.
Just like you do.
We were nothing alike.
She was the good sister.
Always putting others first.
Always doing what was right.
Sometimes I would think
that the wrong sister died.
Why the good one and not me?
You're wrong about
not being anything like her.
You think
that's what she wants to hear?
A cop and a street racer.
I'll tell you something.
They travel down the same road
long enough...
...and they realize
how much alike they really are.
Trust me...
...I know.
She's still doing it, isn't she?
She's still helping people.
She's helping us.
You know, Elena,
she knew everything
about the Reyes family.
After they killed her husband,
she dedicated her life
trying to take them down.
I think I still have her files.
Wait, so we gonna find
military-grade gear
in the middle of London?
You said you wanted
to shop off the grid.
Wait a second.
Did we just time-travel?
Would you look for
a black-market operation
in a place like this?
You've got mail.
-Ooh, snacks.
-Get me a receipt, homey.
How am I gonna get a receipt
from a vending machine?
How about you figure it out?
Paper trail, bruh.
For tax write-off.
I swear to God...
What's up, Bowie420?
Oh, shit. FreddieMerc?
What? I had a life
before you knew me.
Bowie here runs
one of the most notorious
online black markets.
If you want it, he'll sell it.
I thought you didn't like that
about me, though.
Well, desperate times.
What kind of muffins are these?
Oh, those are fun muffins.
You have like four of them,
you'll be in your underwear
watching Fantasia.
Is that what you guys came for?
My muffins?
Oh, it's gonna be
a muffin party?
We, uh, we need transport.
Weapons, cars, the works.
And quietly.
Cool, then I'm just
gonna need cash. Okay?
None of that crypto stuff.
Oh, the Black Jeff Bezos here
got you covered.
-Black Bezos? -Yeah, he's even
been into outer space.
-Wow. -If y'all was gonna be
giving out my money,
I'd appreciate
some type of a heads-up,
you know what I'm saying?
How much we talking about, bruh?
Just like a reasonable amount.
How about that?
That won't even cover
the muffins.
Is this guy serious?
Shit's crazy. Mm-kay.
Come on, man,
you're an astronaut.
Well, how about that?
What, did you leave
all your money in space?
Man, give me this.
-Thank you.
-Are you serious right now?
You know I pay for everything
around here, right?
You should pay for everything.
It's your mission in Rome that
got us here in the first place.
No, it was your intel
that led us to Rome.
To be fair, that setup would
have confused the best of us.
No, I'm tired of this.
'Cause all he do is talk.
And then everyone
has to do their job and yours.
What are you saying, Tej?
-Mean, what I'm saying?
-Hey, guys.
-This is a family environment.
-What? Really?
-Really?
-Take it outside, fellas.
So, what we doing, bruh?
Uh-oh.
Gentlemen, please! Guys!
-Oh, not the vending machine.
No. -Unbelievable.
Guys, you're causing like
dozens of dollars in damage!
Let's go. Come on.
Should we stop this?
-Hold on!
-Nah, let 'em bond.
Hey!
That computer's from, like, '98!
Huh?
What the hell, man?
Okay. All right.
We doing stomachs now.
All right, all right,
that's enough.
-You've been wanting that
for years! -Uh, I think
he hit the copy machine so hard
it works now.
What the hell was that?
He's like a ghetto magician.
You know what it is, bruh.
-I beat your ass.
-You just beat my ass?
-Beat my ass, huh?
-My God,
will you two just quit it?
Please.
We don't have time for this.
You.
-Get to work.
-Oh, I just need
to hack into the marketplace.
It'll just take a second.
Oops.
What the hell, Bowie?
What did you just do?
I'm sorry.
Your guys's faces are,
like, all over the dark web.
I mean, that reward is dope.
-Ow. Hey.
-We have to move.
-The agency's minutes away.
-Look, it's nothing personal.
-Hey, fun muffins on me, okay?
-What? Huh?
-Oh!
I deserved that.
-Are you okay, bro?
-Yeah, thank you, man.
All right, so where to now, huh?
Jail?
I know somewhere.
Last place I want to go.
How does it feel to be
on my side of the law?
They like to fix things
before they break 'em.
It's a sick place, Letty.
You're welcome.
What did you do?
I rerouted anesthetic gas
into their air conditioning.
And I bought us a few minutes
before these cameras reset
and they find out this place
turned into a sleep study.
You gonna stay grumpy or
do you want to get out of here?
They're not gonna sleep forever.
Don't you want to get back
to your precious family?
Shit.
Seems like you got this covered.
-What do you need me for?
-I have a plan,
but it's a two-person job.
Now, was that so hard?
How much time do we have?
I'd say about four minutes.
It'll have to do.
I'd stay down if I was you.
You got to hit me harder
for that.
You're gonna regret this.
Dante Reyes.
Born in Portugal.
Mother from the Pacific Islands.
Sociopathic tendencies
from an early age.
He bounced from juvie to prison
to mental wards.
And each time, Daddy was there
to spring him out.
After his father died,
he disappeared.
Properties Reyes owned
before he died.
Now all sold and repo'd.
Except this one.
The police station.
It's been abandoned for years.
And guess whose name
is on the deed.
Dante Reyes.
I'll find my answer there.
I'm coming with you.
I need you to stay safe.
I would have won that race,
you know.
So you want a rematch?
I'm demanding it.
So I guess I'll see you soon.
Guys, you don't want to do this.
He needs a new watch, cop.
Look, the watch was a gift.
But I got 16 carats of
uncut diamonds in my jockstrap
if you want to take a look.
Now you really do need
a new watch.
Damn it.
B, you okay?
Tried gum? Gum helps.
I don't like planes.
If it's the height,
that's gonna be an issue.
You know, I used to be
scared of cars.
After my dad died,
I guess I blamed myself.
It was tough.
I had panic attacks,
the whole bit.
Heck, I took the bus.
Yeah. I think I was just
so worried about making mistakes
and not being
as good as my brother.
-You?
-Uh, excuse me.
Have you met your dad?
He casts a pretty big shadow.
Huh. Feeling better?
-Yeah.
-Good.
Me, too.
Here's the drink
that you ordered, sir.
You know her?
Yeah, it's good to have friends
in high places.
On the count of three,
we're gonna get up
and go to the bathroom. Ready?
Three.
Who were those guys?
Agency. They found us.
Now let's lose our tail.
Holy shi...
Wait! Swearing is for song
lyrics only and stubbed toes.
Forget about it. Pay attention.
Okay?
We're-we're too high to glide,
so we need thrust,
which means, uh,
combustion, which means...?
Oxygen and fuel.
Alcohol.
-Um...
-Huh?
Oh.
That's rosé. Not gonna work.
Long story.
But good initiative.
I'm glad it wasn't the height.
Enjoy the ride, Little B.
Bowie tagged us.
The agency is on our tail.
We need to find gear
and get to the rendezvous
as soon as possible.
It's right here.
You guys hold back.
Let me take care of this.
No, no, no.
Th-That's a bad idea.
-I mean like Roman-level bad.
-What?
What are you talking about, man?
You heard what I said.
Look, bro, you don't
have to do this, man.
You know I got your back.
We got your back.
I got to do this alone.
I have something
to talk to you about.
The only reason a dead guy
shows up at my door:
revenge.
Oh, shi...
-Oh, shit.
-Shit. Han!
Should have stayed dead.
I can get in. I can get in.
I don't like repeating myself.
You ruined my snacks.
Relax.
I don't want to fight you.
Then this is gonna end quick.
You bring more men to kill me?
They're trying to kill me, too.
Well, it looks like
we got more company.
-You still drive?
-What do you think?
Okay, just give me a second.
Freeze!
-Drop the laptop!
-Okay.
Guys, I'm in.
No, no, no, no!
Now we're even.
You okay?
Now, see, I understand all this.
What the hell was that?
You got scared. I saw that.
-Ain't nobody got scared, bruh.
-No, you were... he was scared.
We have an unwanted guest.
My family?
They're safe for now.
You're not afraid of anything.
I don't care about dying.
I only care about protecting
the people that I love.
Hold us in your heart
and you will never
lose your way.
You're not afraid of anything.
Fear can be a great teacher.
How do you like my place?
I'm bummed I'm not there
to show you around.
And a little embarrassed
you saw my vision board.
But at least you know
how hard I've been working
to get us to this point.
Now I know you're a dead man.
You mean resurrected.
Thanks to you.
You know, if you never would
have gotten behind that wheel,
I'd never be the man
that I am today.
You built such a beautiful life,
filled with love and family.
I never got that chance.
Collateral damage, chaos, death.
This is your legacy.
I'm your legacy.
You know what
I can't figure out?
How someone born so rich
chooses the poorest path
through life.
You got no honor.
Without honor,
you got no family.
And without family...
...you've got nothing.
I have nothing because of you.
My future. My family.
You stole that from me.
And now I'm gonna break yours,
piece by piece.
Stop talking and face me.
Do you like surprises, Dommy?
I adore them.
But the game's not over yet.
There's still
so many people to hurt.
I'm coming for you.
Well, that's gonna be
hard to do in handcuffs.
Okay, bye, Dommy.
No, you hang up first.
Okay.
Toretto, freeze.
Time to face the music, Dom.
You're playing
right into his hands, cop.
Okay. Come on.
Oh.
Yeah.
Great.
Just great.
Shit.
Little chilly?
Your plan still sucks.
Maybe, but at least
you'll be warm.
"Thank you, Cipher. Thank you."
Oh, wow.
Take a look at this.
This should cover us
in the gear department.
You are not to be trusted.
Hey, you ain't
on my Christmas list either.
Nothing here is for free.
Let me be clear on that.
Make sure you get a receipt
from him, okay?
I'd love to see that.
Well, I guess Bowie
wasn't entirely worthless.
I can use his hard drive
to complete our trace of Dante.
He's been ten moves ahead of us
this whole time.
How does he do it by himself?
Uh, this isn't good.
Our money, it's been split into
accounts all over the world.
And look
who they're registered to.
Those are mercenary kill teams.
Real scum.
He used our money
to buy an army.
So this guy doesn't
just want us dead.
He wants to erase us
off the planet.
He's trying to tear us apart.
That's exactly why we need
to link back up with Dom
at the rendezvous point.
You need to see this.
They've been paid to target us
and anyone who ever helped us
until now.
Mum.
I'll have transport
waiting for you.
And where are you going?
I'm gonna dig some graves.
Mr. Nobody's golden boy,
caught without
so much as a fight.
That's no fun.
It's like going
all the way to Everest
and taking the elevator.
You might want to buckle up.
I know you did some good work
for the agency.
I'm sure you figured
that buys you some leniency.
But it's a new day.
That's the problem nowadays.
Nobody listens.
You should have spent less time
with your head under the hood
and more time preparing
for what's coming.
Spies have been replaced
by satellites,
fighter pilots by drones,
intelligence by an algorithm.
The days where one man
behind the wheel of a car
can make a difference
are over, Dom.
Hell, the days of any man
behind the wheel of a car
are over.
What are you doing?
Preparing for what's to come.
Right.
Go. Go. Go.
Dominic, I brought you back
to where we first met.
And I have a surprise for you.
Dom!
I'm listening now.
Dominic?
Dominic!
Would you stop hurting
my new friends?
No. I'm only here to hurt you.
Oh.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
That little car stunt
you just did?
That was pretty awesome.
Wasn't it?
It was so cool.
But if you don't stop,
I'm gonna cut her everywhere.
Badly.
There she is.
-Hmm.
-Fashionably late.
You got me.
Mmm.
Off you go.
Family.
Will you please get off my car?
Hmm.
That is so disrespectful.
You talk too much.
Stop, stop!
You don't know
your own strength.
You butthole!
Oh, hey.
Do you like ballet?
I adore Swan Lake.
I feel like you're more of a--
kind of a Nutcracker guy.
And a one, and a two,
and...
No!
Wait for it.
Oh, no.
She's in peril.
What will you do?
You know what your problem is?
Family.
You can't save 'em all.
Five. Four.
Ah-ta-ta-ta-ta.
Go on.
Two.
You don't like ballet.
I can feel it.
May I please have the God's Eye?
-Screw you.
-No?
Pretty please?
Oh, there it is.
Ooh. Gotcha.
Good trade. Keep the car.
Oh, Dommy!
I told you,
you owe me suffering!
Your legacy isn't money or power
or the family you built
or the life you led.
It's the life you made.
And a father and his son...
is everything.
You killed my father
on this bridge.
And now I know
where to find your son.
Enchanté.
You're gonna be okay, Tess.
It went clear through.
Kinda hurts.
Your father would be proud.
Yeah.
You will stop him.
Have faith.
She needs a hospital.
Mm.
You're gonna be okay.
I got her.
Go save your son.
My nephew.
I'm not gonna say I'm sorry,
so let me do you one better.
Let's get your son.
So, it used to be an old mine,
and they blasted tunnels
deep into the mountain.
And I just, uh...
repurposed the place.
You just got to keep yourself
open to possibilities.
And, of course, have
a lot of time on your hands.
You said we'd meet him here.
Hey.
You know your dad.
He's got to make it safe.
We'll just wait.
I love you, Uncle Jakob.
What's that?
That? Ah, project
I've been working on.
You wouldn't be interested.
All right, we're entering
Portuguese airspace.
Jakob's already there.
Any word from Dom?
Hey.
Why are you so quiet?
You all right?
Just been sitting here
thinking, man.
I knew I smelled
something burning in here.
Tej, it was my mission,
y'all took my lead,
and I messed this thing up
every step of the way.
I guess this whole...
leadership thing
really ain't for me.
You took us to London
on a container.
You spent thousands of dollars
of your own cash,
strapped to your ass,
that now smells like
cheap cologne.
Now you're sitting here
taking sole responsibility
for something that we all wear.
Yeah, I know. It sounds stupid.
Nah, it don't sound stupid
at all.
You know what
it sounds like to me?
That sounds like a leader.
Come on, man.
Get your ass up, man.
I love you, man.
I love you, too, bro.
Sometimes we got to say,
"I'm sorry."
I'm sorry for
whupping your ass, man,
'cause I didn't really mean
to do that.
The whole thing, it would've
been a whole dif...
You okay? What's wrong?
I'm just allergic
to your bullshit.
Come on.
Hey, go easy there.
You're gonna break that thing.
You all right?
God's Eye was just used to send
dozens of mercenaries
after Dom's son.
Something I created
hurting the people we love.
It was meant to help.
This is bigger than just Dante.
This is bigger than just us.
We have to stop
this monster now.
We got to go.
Hold on!
I got eyes on
Uncle Muscle and the kid.
All right, everybody,
remember the plan.
Contain and kidnap. Thank you.
No.
No guns.
I need this little shit alive.
At least for a while.
-You ready?
-Ready.
Holy sh...
Oh, no, you're good.
You're good.
Okay, uh, song lyrics,
stubbed toes and cannon cars.
Yeah.
Here we go!
It's stuck. It's stuck.
They got an army
down there, Dom.
Your team's not far out.
-Bring us down.
-I can't put her down here.
There's an airfield
seven klicks west.
Okay, we'll meet you there.
Now open the back.
Dom, there's really
nowhere to land.
Who said anything about landing?
Look.
I'm coming for you, son.
What the...
-Dad!
-Hey, son.
Good to see you, big bro.
Good to see you guys.
Follow me to that plane.
We're right behind you.
I got you now.
Aimes, we're on our way.
Dom, I'll be touching down
five klicks west.
But they're still on your tail.
It's jammed.
B, what are you doing?
Careful.
Okay, okay, okay.
Shut the front door.
Little B.
Uncle Jakob!
I fixed it!
B!
Toodle-oo.
-Help!
-Ah-ta-ta-ta-ta. Shut up.
Damn it.
You party? I party.
Whoa.
Dom, I lost him.
Dante has Little B.
Hey, Dominic.
Welcome to the big showdown.
It's the last lap.
Check out my copilot.
-Dad!
-Who could've seen this coming?
I mean, you know, except for me.
Shit. Looks like
my fuel line's been shot.
-I can't get to him, Dom.
-Jakob, stay with me.
I'm out of this race.
It has to be you.
Hey, Dom!
Got a little surprise for you.
You raised a hell of a son, Dom.
Time for me to step out
from under your shadow.
Thanks for showing me the light.
Jakob?
I'm gonna go clear the way.
Go get your son.
Jakob, don't!
Don't!
Uncle Jakob!
Looks like Uncle Muscle won't be
coming to the next barbecue.
Oh.
I mean, it's very honorable.
Three miles away.
Take the service road.
It'll lead you
right to the airfield.
You know how to beat your dad
in a street race?
Take away the streets.
Dad!
Amazing.
Oh.
We got it.
My turn.
He's good. Your dad's good.
Dom, you got one mile left.
Son, I never break a promise.
Now, let's finish
that driving lesson.
Feel the car,
find your line
and fly.
Oh!
Now!
No.
Take the service road now.
-I'm wheels down.
-We're headed to you now.
Your team is on their way.
I'll meet you at the airfield.
-You okay?
-I'm good, Dad.
I'm real proud of you, son.
Oh, Dommy boy.
It's so good to see you again.
Did you hit me with
a helicopter back there?
Hmm.
Ow, you big brute.
I mean, I get it.
You're showing off
in front of your son.
But honestly,
did you really think
it was going to be that easy?
You're exactly
where I wanted you to be.
Yes.
Wait for it.
I got a surprise for you.
The cavalry's here.
We got you, Dom.
Roman, get out of here.
It's a trap.
Incoming!
Yes!
See, that's the problem
with having a big family.
Can't protect 'em all.
Ooh!
Oh, Dominic,
is that your new friend?
Aw.
You are so predictable.
You think everyone's gonna
end up on your side?
Problem is Aimes was mine first.
Now the work begins.
And in there,
today we'll put our family
on a path to real power.
Let's get started.
Well, looks like
our partnership's
off to a fantastic start.
You know, Dominic,
to become a real saint,
you have to perform miracles.
Or die a martyr.
So what's it gonna be?
I took your money,
I took your freedom,
and I'm gonna take your family.
And you're gonna die
knowing that
you couldn't save your son.
Dad.
I have faith.
You made one mistake.
You never took my car.
Oh!
The suffering is over, Dom.
It's time for you to die.
No way.
Still think my plan sucks?
Howdy, partner.
Do you like surprises?
You've done some dastardly,
dirty deeds, Sheriff.
You took the most important
thing in my life from me.
Dom drove the car.
-But you...
-Help me.
...you pulled the trigger.
And now I'm gonna
make you suffer.
The devil is coming for you...
lawman.
Well, I ain't hard to find,
you sumbitch.