[Juliette] Where are we going?
Not much further, Bean. Okay.
[Mosley] You said you'd be on time.
And alone.
[Hanna] My daughter can keep a secret.
Unless you'd rather I find another
taker for these.
[Mosley sighs]
You get caught,
I'm gonna say you found it.
No one's getting caught.
Don't be so sure. The Silo always wins.
- I can carry it.
- [sighs]
[breathes deeply] Okay.
- You got me a rabbit?
- [Hanna shushes]
It's not a pet, okay?
- We're not gonna eat it.
- [chuckles] No, we're not gonna eat it.
It's barely moving. I think it's sick.
That's the point, Bean.
[baby fussing]
[baby crying]
We're not looking for a baby.
[footsteps departing]
[Gloria] Please.
Won't be much longer.
Come on, I need to sleep.
I know.
I can't stay in here.
Miss Hildebrandt.
[Gloria breathing heavily]
[Sims] You weren't very cooperative
with my agents.
I hope you'll be more cooperative
with me, Gloria.
You're the security man.
Your wife had a miscarriage.
Your memory is sharp.
That bodes well for us.
You two were about to give up on a family,
but you still had time on your lottery.
And then I got you s-some f... [sighs]
- Folic acid.
- Folic acid. That's it.
One drop in her tea every night.
Did it work?
Our boy turns six next month.
Oh.
I need your help.
If you cooperate
and give me what I'm looking for,
I'll personally guarantee
you're never kept from your dreams again.
If I don't help you?
You gonna send an old woman out to clean?
No.
I'll leave her in this room unmedicated
to spend the rest of her days
staring at these walls.
Why should I trust you?
Because thanks to you, I have my son.
I take no pleasure
in putting you in this position.
But now the situation
is of grave importance to the Silo.
Juliette Nichols paid you a visit.
Took something out of that vent.
I need to know what that was.
[sighs]
A bag.
Did Sheriff Holston hide it in there?
[sighs] Yes.
What was inside the bag?
Give her the good stuff.
Every dose, every day.
Anyone try to pull her out,
they go through me.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, Miss Hildebrandt.
For everything.
Do you really think you'll win?
[Sims sighs]
We have to.
Cameras had her on the stairs
below here going down,
but then we lost her. [sighs]
Stair coverage gets pretty spotty
below Medical.
When you find her, secure her.
She has a red-level relic with her.
Tell your team nobody touches it.
[agent] Yes, sir.
[sighs]
[typing]
[beeps]
[sighs]
[inhales sharply]
[switch clicks]
What's gonna happen?
[Hanna] Well, I think there could be
a small hole in his heart.
- Like Jacob had?
- Yeah.
And, uh, I'm gonna find it and sew it up.
- How are you gonna see it?
- With this.
All right, bring him over.
Now, this next part's gonna be scary.
- Are you sure you want to stay?
- Yeah, I wanna watch it all.
[chuckles] Okay, then.
You wanna see his heart?
Come on, then.
- [heartbeat thumping]
- [Juliette] Whoa, it's gigantic.
My darling Bean, this is a magnifier.
It's the first one in the Silo.
It makes tiny things appear big.
Now, if this works... [sighs]
...we can use it to help other people.
Okay.
- [radio static]
- [Paul] Billings to Sheriff.
- What is it, Billings?
- [radio static]
[Paul] You need to come to the office.
[objects scraping, thudding]
[papers rustling]
Hey! What the fuck are you doing?
- You need to wait here until we finish.
- No, no, no. This is our office.
How can they do this?
Meadows ordered a search
for unregistered relics.
What?
Sounds like a load of rat shit to me.
The real question is why she did it.
Why are you looking at me? I don't know.
Sims took the last relic.
I don't think anything's come in since.
Uh-huh. What happened at your little visit
with her yesterday?
Nothing happened. I brought her eggs
and bacon like you said.
- She's sick as a dog.
- [clatters]
Hey! Take it easy, Howey.
You realize this is a blatant violation
of the Pact, right?
Law enforcement premises cannot be
searched without extreme probable cause.
Do you hear what I'm saying?
[objects rustling, clattering]
Make sure you check under the flooring.
[Hanna] Do you know how lost I felt?
This was the one thing that I could do.
Imagine if we'd had something
like this for Jacob, hmm?
We... I mean, we could... [stammers]
All I... All I want
is to stop other families
from going through the same thing.
You don't think I felt lost too?
But that doesn't mean you can start
making unsanctioned devices.
That device could help fix heart defects.
- [sighs]
- It could save lives.
Why is a magnifier even illegal
in the first place?
I don't know, but there are rules.
You're good at following rules.
I'll give you that.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- No one else knew what I was doing
besides you and Jules.
What, you think I told Judicial?
I'm sure there's something in the Pact
about reporting your family.
[sighs] How can you even suggest that?
[inhales shakily]
How else could they have known?
[Pete] Because there are
fucking whisperers everywhere!
You haven't exactly been subtle.
Glass and metal deliveries to our door,
taking our daughter to the farm
after hours.
- [objects clattering]
- Oh. Oh, please.
Please, Hanna.
Just give them what they want
before they tear down our entire home.
[inhales shakily]
Juliette's room is... Please.
I hope whatever you're getting out
of this is worth it.
- [clattering continues]
- Stop.
I'll give it to you.
Stand down.
What is all this?
[snaps fingers]
No!
Now the animal.
Tell us where it is,
and we'll drop the charges
against the farmer.
It died.
We ate the meat, composted the rest.
The Judicial Department thanks you
for your time and your cooperation.
I swear to you, I didn't.
[mutters] It's okay. I've got this.
[clatters]
[lid slams shut]
- We need to check that.
- That's not gonna happen.
Little help here?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Fine.
There. You happy, asshole?
[objects clattering]
[agent] Let's go.
And you used to work with these people?
I was in administration, not one
of these overcompensating fuckwads.
- What? I cuss.
- [scoffs]
Either way, this doesn't feel
like a regular toss and turn.
- This feels...
- No, this is personal.
[sighing] Fuck.
Meadows didn't do this.
She's not behind this.
- She signed the warrant.
- No, when I was there,
something didn't feel right.
I don't think she's the one
calling the shots.
- Then who is?
- Sims.
- Robert?
- Yeah.
He enforces the Pact.
He's not some power-hungry...
No. No, he's wanted to get rid of me
ever since I arrived.
This here, this is just a warm-up.
He's not gonna stop until I'm either
in that cell or over the fucking rail.
[sighing] Fuck.
You said this was an illegal search
and seizure, right?
They skipped about ten steps.
There should have been an initial notice,
a request for evidence...
- You're coming with me to Judicial.
- To do what?
[Sims]
Does this look like a hard drive to you?
No, sir.
How about this?
- Does it plug into a computer?
- No, sir.
Did the warrant say to bring back
useless fucking office supplies?
That's all we found in her office.
Then you didn't look hard enough!
New plan.
I want you to find every porter
who worked between level one and 50.
Find out if she handed off anything
or talked to anyone. That's what...
[assistant stammers] I'm sorry.
I tried to stop them.
Miss Nichols,
you can't just barge into my...
- Robert Sims, you're under arrest.
- ...office like this.
[Sims] Wait, this is about your office.
- I told Meadows you'd be pissed...
- [Juliette] Fuck Meadows.
You're under arrest
for breaking Pact investigation protocol.
- What, are we making up crimes now?
- Deputy Billings.
Section 14, subsection three,
paragraph 12B.
- And illegal search and seizure.
- Section 23, subsection 19, paragraph six.
All those Pact Bees you won
while you were a kid
finally paid off, huh, Paul?
Seems that way.
Miss Nichols, I had nothing
to do with that search order.
Your agents broke protocol,
and I'm holding you responsible.
You don't like it,
you can take it up with Meadows.
Cuff him and take him upstairs. [sniffs]
Are you sure you want to do this?
Want's got nothing to do with it.
She's the boss.
For the moment.
Take all this back upstairs
and put it where you found it.
- [Sims grunts]
- Hey!
Do you wanna join your boss in jail?
I've got more cuffs.
- You'll regret this.
- I doubt that.
Great. Place better look like you
were never there.
[breathes deeply]
[gasps]
Jules?
Is everything okay?
[stammers] Why didn't you want mom
to build a magnifier?
[Pete sighs]
Look, I... I know you
have very strong feelings about...
No, I...
I wanna know why she killed herself.
I know I wasn't willing to listen before.
I am now.
I, um... I really need to know.
Wasn't about the magnifier.
What do you mean?
A couple of times a year,
I have to break the news
to a young, happy couple
that their newborn has died.
[breathes shakily]
It's my job.
But it's not the hardest part.
The hardest is running into that father
and mother in the years after
and seeing what it's done to them.
Loss affects people differently.
Sometimes it shrinks your world,
draws you inward. [inhales shakily]
And that's how it was for me
after we lost your brother.
I spent a lot more time in here
when I should have been there
for you and your mother.
I'll always regret that.
And I'm sorry.
But your mother...
grief turned her outward,
pushed her toward dangerous things.
She so desperately wanted answers,
she stopped caring about the lines
she had to cross to get them.
[softly] But she still wanted
to help people.
And I wanted to help her, protect her.
That's all I cared about.
Not the magnifier. Not anything else.
[softly] But it wasn't enough.
I should have stopped them...
[breathing shakily]
...Judicial, when they came into our home.
I should have done something
besides bowing to their will.
When those agents crushed her machine,
they crushed her spirit.
And I tried to bring her back,
but she didn't wanna listen to me.
I gave up.
I failed her.
That's why I left you in Mechanical.
You're like your mom
in so many ways, Jules.
[sobs]
When you went down there, it wrecked me.
But I knew it was for the best,
even if it meant you'd hate me.
I knew that down there,
you could put your talent
into fixing real things in front of you
instead of chasing impossible answers
like your mother did.
And yet here I am. [sniffles]
Here you are.
And she blamed you, you know? [sniffles]
She thought you had reported her.
I did too.
I know. And I swear to you, I never. Ever.
No, I know. I know. [breathes shakily]
Judicial, they were watching Mom
with sensors through the mirrors.
I found her file.
- What do you mean?
- They... They have their own cameras.
That's... And they listen,
not just with porters and other people,
they have devices.
- That's how they knew about the magnifier.
- [gasps] Oh.
- That's how they know everything.
- [sighs]
She never believed me.
I know. I know.
I do.
[breathes deeply, crying] Oh, Juliette.
[softly] I know. I'm so sorry. [sniffles]
[breathes shakily, crying]
I still miss her so much.
[Juliette] I do too.
[Juliette sniffling]
- [Alice] Sorry to interrupt.
- It's okay.
Maintenance is here. [sighs]
- What for?
- Something about checking the vents.
He's very insistent.
- Did you send for a work order?
- No.
- Did you?
Can you tell him to come back later?
[Pete] Please.
Okay.
When we brought Gloria here, you said
you thought there were no listeners.
- Uh-huh.
- There are no cameras.
This maintenance guy,
he's here to put one in.
Right now, this is a dead spot for them.
- What's that?
- A hard drive.
- What's on it?
- I don't know.
I... I tried using your computer
to find out, but I couldn't open it.
It requires some authorization. [sniffs]
I'm gonna take it to Walk.
If anyone can get around it, she can.
Could you just, um...
Could you let her know I'll be coming?
I should... [sniffles]
...I should be able to be there by 6:00.
Yeah. Jules, you be... you be safe. Please.
[whispers] Yeah, I will.
Okay. [sniffles]
[door closes]
- [citizens chattering]
- [checkpoint agent] ID. Next. ID.
[citizen] Come on.
- [checkpoint agent] ID. Bag check.
- Shit.
- What's going on?
- I should be asking you.
Can't you get them to speed this up?
If I'm late for my next job,
I'm late for every one after.
Yeah, sure, I'll look into it.
Hey, Jerry.
- Yes, sir?
- Could I trouble you for a cup of coffee?
[Sims] Black. No sugar, no cream.
[softly] Right.
[liquid pours]
[sighs]
Thanks.
Also, could you do me a favor?
Let me use your radio a second.
- Mr. Sims, sir... I... I just...
- Just one call.
I... I just...
I really think we need to wait,
you know, until someone gets back.
[sighs] I-If that's all right.
Sheriff? Or Billings?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, you're right. I understand.
Don't worry about it.
I won't hold it against you.
Hey, you.
- I missed her again, didn't I?
- I just put her down.
Busy day?
You have no idea. [breathes deeply]
Dinner's almost ready.
[Paul sighs]
[sighs]
[plates shattering]
- [groans]
- Are you okay?
[sighs]
[straining] Mm-hmm.
[exhales]
- Sorry, I just...
- Don't be. I'll get it later.
The tremors have gotten worse
since you went upstairs.
I'm fine.
- This job is...
- It's not the job.
I like the job. I just... [sighs]
She put me in a position today where I had
to choose between her and Sims.
- How is that even a choice?
- It's complicated.
[Paul sighs]
[scoffs] People are saying she's laying
the groundwork for another rebellion.
- Where'd you hear that?
- Everyone's on edge.
Everything that's been happening,
all these deaths in a week.
- It's not normal.
- If you're worried about me...
I am.
Clearly, the stress is making it worse.
Honey... [chuckling] ...I'll be fine.
I promise you.
[Paul sighs]
[breathing deeply]
[exhales]
[breathing shakily]
Hello?
Hello? Is anyone around?
[sighs]
Hello? [breathing heavily]
Son of a bitch. [inhales deeply]
[footsteps approaching]
- Hello?
- [Shirley] Walk?
What's going on?
- Have you seen Jules?
- Should I have?
She was supposed to be here an hour ago.
- Can you let me know if you see her?
- Will do.
[sighs]
- [dishware clattering]
- [workers chattering]
Lukas Kyle?
Yes.
For you.
You see it?
[Juliette] I see a "W."
Hi. Get in.
- Were you followed?
- No.
In about five minutes,
Judicial raiders are gonna be here.
I've got three to talk.
- W... Why are you...
- [shushes]
[whispers] They can hear us. Okay? Don't.
Okay, I don't understand what you're...
[whispers] Look, I've got this.
- An old hard drive?
- Yeah, and I need to get into it,
but it requires some kind of authorization
I don't have.
[sighing]
Okay, um, what kind of authorization?
Um, sys... something.
- Sysop?
- Yeah. What's that?
That's, like, reserved
for the head of IT, Judicial security.
- That's not...
- And the sheriff?
- Yes.
- I tried it. It didn't work.
That's because you need to take it up
to your workplace computer.
[scoffs] No, I can't go there.
Um, is there any way
that you can work around it?
Please.
I think this drive holds
the answers to a lot of questions.
What kind of questions?
Like w-why Holston's wife
went out to clean.
What happened to George.
Why Jahns and Marnes were killed.
- They were... I'm sorry, they were what?
- Yeah, they were murdered.
Um... [stammers] ...why?
And who's George?
He was a friend.
A friend?
Oh.
- Well, that explains a lot.
- No, I don't have time for this.
- To use me? Clearly.
- Yeah. You know what?
Right now I'm using you
'cause I have no other choice.
And you should want to help me.
You're the one sitting
in the cafeteria every single night,
wondering what's out there.
What if the answers
to your questions are on this drive?
W-Well, I don't think that I should be
trying to open something
- that I'm not authorized to open.
- No, but I am.
Yes, Juliette,
but the rules apply to everyone.
- What the fuck?
- [mirror shattering]
[sighs]
Look at this.
A sensor. A camera.
This is how they look at us.
This is how they control us.
- These... These are in our homes?
- These are everywhere.
And if we don't figure out the truth,
no one else will.
So, please help me.
- Please.
- I, uh...
Even if I could, my mom...
- I'm the only one...
- Your mom?
Yes, I'm the only one
taking care of her right now.
- If something happens to me, I can't...
- It's...
Time's up.
You better leave too. For your mom's sake.
- Juliette.
- [door closes]
[breathing shakily]
Fuck. Juliette.
[banging on door]
Juliette Nichols. By Judicial
order, open the door immediately.
[object thudding against door]
[door breaking]
[citizens chattering]
ID and bag, please.
- Bag was checked upstairs. I'm in a hurry.
- ID and bag, please.
Are you serious? Do you know who I am?
- Ma'am.
- This is my ID.
- Open your bag.
- Where is your supervisor?
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Wherever they are, they won't be pleased.
This is your sheriff, and she's with me.
Uh, but...
Oh, now you're questioning the mayor too?
You arrested Sims.
Now there's checkpoints.
- What the fuck is going on, Sheriff?
- You were right. Okay?
Judicial is planning a takeover,
but Meadows is not the one behind it.
- It's Sims.
- Can't be.
Robert is so by the book.
[inhales sharply] We can't talk here.
- I know a place. It's a bit of a walk.
- Okay.
Okay. [breathes deeply]
We're about as alone as we can get
in the Silo.
Walk me through it.
You think Sims
is secretly running Judicial?
Yeah. It's not the judge.
- Well, what does Sims want?
- I don't know.
Control the Silo? Cover up a crime?
I don't know.
Whatever it is, he wants me gone.
And after you, me. [inhales sharply]
[sighs] I never wanted this fucking job.
[exhales deeply]
What are they looking for?
What do... What do you mean?
Well, they searched your apartment.
Now there's checkpoints everywhere.
What do you have that's so threatening?
[stammers]
I don't know what you're talking about.
The clock is running, Juliette.
There isn't much time left.
If you have the hard drive, then...
Fuck me.
I said, "hard drive."
How would I know that it's a hard drive?
- Oops.
- [Juliette breathing heavily]
[gasps, pants]
You. You're the one.
I'm sorry, Sheriff Nichols.
Did you just say you want to go outside?
No, no. No, I didn't.
I distinctly heard you say you want
to go outside.
- Robert, did you hear that?
- [Sims] Sure did.
No.
That's two sheriffs in as many weeks.
What is it about being sheriff these days?
You're the one. [breathes shakily]
Meadows isn't afraid of him.
She... She's afraid of you.
Yeah.
The Founders knew someone
would have to make the hard decisions
to keep our Silo alive.
A person that possessed the knowledge,
the intelligence,
the information about everything
that happens here.
Lucky me.
Why would you kill all those people?
I don't... I don't understand.
Miss Nichols,
throughout our entire existence,
problems have arisen
that must be taken care of.
The needs of the many
require the sacrifices of the few.
For what?
For a hard drive
and some fucking heat tape?
This isn't about heat tape.
This is about survival.
And that hard drive threatens the lives
- of everyone in this Silo.
- [footsteps approaching]
[Bernard] And you are the greatest threat
to our home in 140 years.
Well, you were.
[breathing heavily]
[panting]
[both grunting, groaning]
- [Juliette grunting, screaming]
- [raider grunting]
- [raider 2 yelling]
- [Juliette grunting, groaning]
[Juliette groans]
Where are her friends?
Her sister. Her aunt.
- [Pete] You know why they're not...
- They're cowards.
That's not...
[sighs]
If she'd died of a heart attack,
they'd all be here.
[exhales deeply] I know it feels
like more should be done, but...
But nothing.
They're cowards.
So was she.
Jules.
[Juliette] Go on. Leave!
Leave! Leave, damn it! Leave!
[grunting]
[groaning, panting]
I told you you'd regret arresting me.
[breathing heavily, groans]
[citizens chattering]
You got this from Hank?
[Shirley] All of the sheriff's stations
got a message ten minutes ago.
No, it doesn't make any sense.
Look, she was on her way here.
- Who were the witnesses?
- [Shirley] The mayor.
- Some Judicial raiders.
- Oh.
Yeah, let's believe them.
They never lied to us before.
I'm just telling you what I heard, Walk.
All right. You're right.
I'm sorry, Shirley. I'm just...
[Shirley] I know.
[Martha sighs]
Knox said they'd eventually punish us
for the rebellion.
I always thought he was crazy.
So? What happens next?
Wait, Paul.
Please, please, please just listen to me.
- No. I'm done trying to make sense of you.
- I never... No, listen! You need...
You want me to enforce the Pact
when it suits you...
- No.
- ...and not to when it doesn't?
- I never said that I wanted to go out.
- I can't do that.
- [Sims] I heard it.
- No.
- As did the mayor and my agents.
More than enough evidence,
I'd think, Sheriff Billings.
- I'm not sheriff until we finish...
- No. They're trying to set me up.
- Shut up!
- You're lying!
Hey! If you believe you were misheard,
you have the right to request a hearing.
- Do I? Do I? With who?
- Yes!
- With Judicial? He's fucking Judicial!
- [punch lands]
- [Juliette groaning, gasping]
- I said shut up!
[Juliette gasping]
That was uncalled for, Robert!
I warned her.
Make sure you mention that in your report.
[Juliette gasping]
What are you looking at?
- [Juliette gasping]
- Hey.
[both breathing heavily]
Oh, shit.
- [Paul panting]
- [Juliette grunts]
[Paul groans]
- [Sims groans]
[Juliette panting]
[Paul] Don't!