Ah, Cham Syndulla, the
liberator of Ryloth.
Now the traitor of Ryloth.
Attempting to assassinate
your own senator?
How unfortunate for your
people to see you fall.
They won't believe your lies.
Taa said you'd be a challenge,
but he was mistaken.
Your loyal followers will
be even easier to deal with.
Your daughter too.
Surely you know how dangerous
it can be out there.
You don't know Hera.
Eleni, you're the
reasonable one.
Tell us where she is and I will
ensure she is returned to you safely.
I have seen how you treat
your allies, Admiral.
I prefer to be your enemy.
Have it your way.
Scour the entire
planet if you have to.
I want all of Syndulla's
sympathizers found and arrested.
Sir, the people
are not insurgents.
We have no cause to arrest them.
They're supporting a menace.
Syndulla's forces attacked our
transport and shot Senator Taa.
I was there.
That blast didn't come
from Cham or his fighters.
Is that so?
Then please enlighten
me. Who is responsible?
I don't know, sir.
Leave the thinking
to me, Captain.
You have your orders.
Yes, sir. I'll locate
Hera Syndulla myself.
That's not necessary. Another
squad is handling that.
It's only a matter of
time before she's found.
[chatters]
[Chopper chattering on comm]
Chopper. Shh. I'm here. Hang on.
[ES-04] We searched the house.
The Syndulla girl's gone.
[ES-03] She could've
already fled the planet.
[Crosshair] Not without
her parents. Find her.
New plan, Chop.
Meet me at the base.
We need to send out a
transmission, and fast.
[Chopper chatters on comm]
[Gonky honking]
Uh-oh.
What's going on here?
Gonky's prime power source won't
fully charge. I'm fixing it.
You can't. He's
a defective unit.
[Tech] Hunter.
[Gonky honks]
Don't worry, we're
defective too.
We are receiving a recorded transmission,
but I do not recognize this frequency.
Patch it through.
Omega, it's Hera. You have
to come back to Ryloth.
- Isn't she the kid from the weapons drop?
- [Gonky honks]
Hera?
The Empire's taken my parents,
and they're after me now too.
I'm sending coordinates.
Please hurry. I need your help.
You gave her our comm channel?
For emergencies, and that
sounded pretty urgent.
We have to go.
Perhaps the situation is
not as dire as described.
Children often overreact.
No, we don't. You heard
her. She needs us.
Omega, it's a big galaxy.
We can't put ourselves on the line
every time someone's in trouble.
Why not? Isn't that
what soldiers do?
[Chopper chattering]
What's his problem?
[Hera] Thank you for coming.
I wasn't sure you would.
You said you were in trouble.
Care to tell us why the
Empire is after you?
Because my father
is Cham Syndulla.
The freedom fighter?
Yes. This was his
old command outpost.
It's where I've been hiding.
The Empire's begun targeting
anyone loyal to him.
What do you want us to do?
Free my parents from the Capitol.
That's where they're being held.
They can pay you if
you get them out.
Please. I don't have
anyone else to ask.
Let's see what we're up against
first. But no guarantees.
[probe droid beeps]
Citizens of Ryloth,
the shocking attack on your beloved
senator has left you shaken,
but Orn Free Taa's condition continues to
improve, and he will make a full recovery.
[Rampart] But...
The perpetrators of this heinous
assassination attempt have been captured.
- Assassination attempt?
- [Rampart] Rest assured,
- Cham Syndulla and his insurgents...
- That's not what happened.
Will answer for their betrayal.
Hunter... Crosshair's here.
[Wrecker] Great.
Just what we need.
The plasma bridge into the
city's been deactivated.
Well, I say we fly in
and blow our way out.
The Capitol scanners
would detect our ship.
I don't like the look of this.
The troop presence here is
similar to that of Raxus.
This is a military occupation.
Ryloth's not a
Separatist planet.
Exactly my point.
[probe droid beeps]
Wait here.
[probe droid beeps repeatedly]
[Chopper chatters]
Oh, good. A probe droid.
The Empire will know we're here.
And so will Crosshair.
Come on. Let's move.
Come on.
[Chopper chatters]
[ES-02] Command received a transmission
from a probe droid in sector five.
All my father wanted
was peace on Ryloth.
Why is this happening?
He's a voice the
people stand behind.
That makes him a
threat to the Empire.
I don't care about any of that.
I just want my parents back.
[Chopper chattering]
We're all over the
Imperial comm channels.
They've increased
patrols within the city.
Crosshair will expect an attack.
The element of surprise is
gone. There's nothing we can do.
Wait, you can't leave.
I told you no guarantees.
We'll get you off world and
take you some place safe.
Stop!
I'll pay you double.
All the money in the galaxy
won't matter if we're dead.
What you're asking us to
do, it's not worth the risk.
Not to you.
[Chopper chatters]
You shouldn't have said that.
Being strategic means knowing
your limitations, Omega.
She's trying to save her family,
Hunter. I'd do the same for you.
[Chopper beeps]
No, Howzer. "Some" isn't good enough. I
want all of Syndulla's supporters found.
Sir, if we continue rounding up peaceful
citizens, it will incite an uprising.
Then they will be arrested
too. Peace has a cost, Captain.
Clone Force 99 is on Ryloth.
They were spotted
near the Capitol.
We have a battalion of
troopers right outside.
That's not enough. I know
what they're capable of.
I'm more worried about
what you're capable of.
Since your squad has yet to locate Hera
Syndulla, I suggest you stay on task.
Or I will find someone who can.
- [Chopper chatters]
- [sighs]
I don't need a lecture, Chop.
[Chopper chatters]
I didn't give up. He did.
[Omega] Hunter means well.
I know you're scared, but don't
give up. He'll come around.
Why do you trust him so much?
Because he's my brother.
- [Chopper chatters]
- Brother? Him?
They all are.
You're lucky.
You can trust them too.
All we need to do is think of
a plan and convince Hunter.
Why would he listen to me?
Because it's strategic.
Ryloth is your home. You
know it better than us.
Yes, I do.
[Chopper chatters]
So this is the
side you've chosen?
[sighs] Look.
You both attacked an Imperial convoy.
What did you think would happen?
Taa gave us no choice.
We had to protect Hera.
That's what I'm trying to do.
Admiral Rampart's squad is
out there looking for her.
She's in danger.
So please, if you know
where she is, tell me.
I'll protect her.
Like how you swore
to protect Ryloth?
We trusted you, Howzer.
I won't make that mistake again.
Attack the Capitol?
Wh... That was my plan.
Not the Capitol, the Imperial
refinery on the outskirts.
[Hera] I've been spying
on their activity.
I know their routine.
If we attack there, reinforcements
will be diverted from the Capitol.
We can use that distraction
to rescue Hera's parents.
Any heavy defenses
at the refinery?
Five perimeter cannons,
but they are unmanned.
Auto cannons are
extremely vulnerable.
Where is the control console?
[Hera] Right inside
the main gate.
It is heavily guarded,
but Chopper can slip inside with the
other droids and disable the cannons.
All right. You two go with Chopper
as backup, but at a distance.
- Really?
[Chopper chatters]
By themselves?
Tech, Wrecker. Wait until those
cannons are down and move in.
Echo and I will scale the Capitol
wall and free Hera's parents.
I guess we'll follow your lead.
[Chopper chatters on comm]
We are in position.
[clone trooper] Have your chain
codes out and ready for inspection.
[droids beeps]
[Chopper chatters]
They're approaching
the checkpoint.
Get ready, Chop.
[Chopper chatters]
- [droid beeps]
- [device beeps]
[Chopper chatters]
[droids beeping]
[droid beeps]
[Chopper chatters]
- [Chopper chatters]
- [droid beeps]
[droid whimpers]
[Chopper chatters]
What do you mean it won't work? You
said you could disable the cannons.
[Chopper chatters]
[clone trooper] Hey!
You don't belong here!
[Chopper chatters]
We have to help Chopper.
We will, but first, we need
to take the console off-line.
Uh, how are we going to do that?
With one of those.
You said you wanted
to be a pilot, right?
Yeah.
Well, come on.
[clanks]
[comms chatter]
[clone trooper] Huh?
- [Echo] A little help?
- [Hunter] Hey.
[clone trooper groans]
[Hunter grunts]
My parents would never
approve of this plan.
I won't tell if you won't.
[Tech] Omega, has Chopper
deactivated the perimeter cannons?
No, but Hera and I are working on it.
Just don't shoot down our shuttle.
[Tech] Wait. What shuttle?
Here we go.
[gasps] Sorry!
[screams]
[clone trooper] We've
got a security breach!
Unauthorized launch
from shuttle two!
[clone troopers groan]
[alarm blares]
[Chopper chatters]
[Tech] Omega, I am registering
multiple explosions near the refinery.
That was us. Cannons are down.
- [Omega] Do some damage, Wrecker.
- [Wrecker laughs]
That, I can do!
Hang on.
Whoa!
[console beeps]
Yeah! [Laughs]
Call in reinforcements!
[console beeps]
The refinery is under attack.
I'll handle it. Stay here
and guard the Capitol.
[blows landing]
[clone trooper groans]
[control panel beeping]
- What are you doing here?
- [Hunter] Breaking you out.
You know them?
They are mercenaries. But I
didn't hire them for this.
Hera did.
Hera? Where is she? Is she safe?
We're getting the hang of this.
Yes, your dangerous and
uncontrolled maneuvering
is as confusing to
them as it is to us.
[alarm blaring]
Stop.
[ES-03] The admiral said
to protect the refinery.
That's not their target.
[ES-04] Then why are
they attacking it?
[alarm blaring]
[Howzer] Cham, wait!
You're walking into a trap.
There's a squad
out there waiting.
Why should we trust you?
Because I'm on your side.
What the Empire
is doing is wrong.
You have to get out of here.
They have the exits blocked.
We can use Senator Taa's shuttle
in his private tower hangar.
I'm sorry, General. I
should've stopped this sooner.
Our fight for
Ryloth is not over.
We will return.
You can't stay here.
They'll know you helped us.
I will not abandon my squad.
They're good men.
I have to try to
get through to them.
Go, while there's still time.
[Hunter] Tech, Omega, we
have alternate transport.
Meet at the rendezvous.
Gladly. Because there are
multiple Imperial vessels inbound.
[ES-04] Commander,
should we move in?
[Crosshair] Stay in position.
This is their way out.
Brothers. What are we doing?
We came here to free Ryloth from
Separatist control, and we succeeded.
But look around you.
We're now being ordered to target
the very people we swore to protect.
And I will not be a
part of it any longer.
Who will stand with me?
Arrest those traitors.
Here's the payment
Hera promised.
Keep it. You'll need it.
These occupations are happening
on other planets besides Ryloth.
I hoped to have fought my last war, but
our people need us now more than ever.
We must organize.
Well, that's not something
we can help with, General.
I have my own people
to look out for.
[device beeps]
If a war is coming, it will be
their fight as much as ours.
Come along, Hera.
Tech showed me how to
scramble a ship's signature.
We will soon see
how well it works.
It is time for us to go.
Well, copilot, we
didn't do too bad.
Do you have to go?
For now, but I'm sure
I'll see you around.
And keep an eye
on your brothers.
They need it.
I will.
Thanks. For believing in me.
[Chopper chatters]
[ship departs]
It would seem I underestimated
your four friends.
If only they were fighting
for us instead of against us.
Request permission
to hunt them down.
Hmm.
Granted.