[birds squawk]
[chattering]
- The Empire is not your enemy.
- [crowd jeering]
We promise to treat all planets within the
Confederacy of Independent Systems fairly.
All we asked in exchange
was for your loyalty.
Yet that has not been
forthcoming here on Raxus.
I can't go through with this.
[droid] Senator, it
is your only option.
This is what it's come to? I
must be a puppet for the Empire?
[droid] If you do not comply,
you will be arrested like
the other senators. Or worse.
[captain] To deal with
the rise in incursions,
a mandatory curfew will be put
into effect for your protection.
Such measures were approved by
your esteemed senator, Avi Singh,
who would like to say a few words
about the importance of cooperation
as we build a unified galaxy.
[jeering continues]
Senator?
GS-8, if anything happens to me,
follow my instructions to the letter.
What will happen,
Senator? Senator?
[crowd cheering, applauding]
[Singh] Fellow citizens, I implore
you to embrace these new laws.
Under the Empire, Raxus
will flourish once more.
And as your senator,
I promise...
I…
I promise to…
No.
This is wrong.
It is my duty to act
in your best interest,
and it is why I can no longer
condone this unjust occupation.
[cheering]
They wish to intimidate
us, to scare us,
but we shall not cower at
their acts of aggression.
[crowd booing]
- [comm beeps]
- Move in.
[clone trooper] Step
aside. Clear out!
We have every right to be here.
You're the ones trespassing.
- [alarm blaring]
- [walkers stomping]
[crowd screaming, shouting]
[blaring continues]
I'm sending this message on behalf of
my master, Senator Avi Singh of Raxus.
The senator has been seized by Imperial
authorities and is in grave danger.
We require your assistance.
How's the Mantell Mix, kid?
[Omega] Mm-hmm.
Better than ever.
Yeah, it is. [Laughs]
So, when's our next mission?
With two bounty hunters after you,
it'd be wise to keep a low profile.
Tech's right.
There's too much
heat on us right now.
Ha! That never
stopped us before.
The kid's been through
enough. She needs a break.
[Echo sniffs]
She seems fine to me.
[music playing in Cid's
parlor, indistinct]
I've got a mission for you boys.
- A simple extraction on Raxus.
- Raxus?
That is the former center of
the Separatist government.
It has since become
an Imperial outpost...
I'm not interested in a
history lesson, Goggles.
You're being hired to locate and free
Senator Avi Singh from his confinement.
My client will meet you at the
given coordinates to brief you.
Details are on
this. Now get going.
Help a Separatist?
Not gonna happen.
Your debt's still
not paid, remember?
A job's a job.
I am not bringing Omega to a
planet swarming with Imperials.
So leave her here with me.
I'll keep an eye on her.
I don't exactly
trust you either.
Good. You shouldn't.
But if keeping the kid safe
means more money in my pocket,
it's in my best interest
to do so, isn't it?
- If anything happens to her...
- [Cid] Yeah, yeah, Bandana.
Just get outta here, will you?
Ready when you are, Sergeant.
Not this time, Omega.
You're staying with Cid.
But th-the mission. I'm
part of the squad too.
Then following orders
shouldn't be a problem.
Stay close to Cid and
don't leave this parlor.
Got it, soldier?
[groans]
Yes, sir.
Hey, tiny, I got
a mission for you.
Now get scrubbing.
We've never been
to Raxus before.
The coordinates from
Cid have us landing
outside the capital city of
Raxulon, the home of their Senate.
I can't believe we're
helping a Separatist senator.
So you have said. Repeatedly.
I always thought we'd
make it to Raxus someday.
But not like this.
[rapid beeping]
[trooper on comms] Unidentified
transport, this is restricted airspace.
Transmit your clearance code.
Input the codes
from Cid's client.
[rapid beeping]
Hunter, the client
is a Separatist.
How do we know
this isn't a trap?
[console beeps]
[trooper on comms] You're
cleared for entry. Proceed.
Now are you convinced?
No.
[Tech] I am simply stating that
the codes did, in fact, work.
The client being a
Separatist is not relevant.
[Echo] It is to me.
[Hunter] Forget politics.
We're here to do a job.
[GS-8] I am very pleased
to hear you say that.
[Tech] Who are you?
I am your client.
[Wrecker] We're
working for a droid?
That is correct.
My master, Senator Singh,
was arrested for speaking out
- against the unjust occupation...
- [Echo] We don't care.
[Hunter] Just take us to where
the senator's being held.
Right to it. I like you.
Very well. Follow me.
[Echo groans]
[aliens grunting, shouting]
[crash]
[tall alien laughs]
Enough with the moping around.
You're bringing the
mood down around here.
Sorry.
All right, I'll bite.
What's wrong with you?
I haven't heard back from them
yet. Do you think they're okay?
They better be for
what this job's paying.
I should've gone with
them on the mission.
It's not fair.
I've got news for you,
kid. Life ain't fair.
You don't like it?
Stop pouting and do
something about it.
Maybe if you
weren't so helpless,
those four laser brains wouldn't
have left you here with me.
[dejarik figures
whistling, squawking]
What are you two looking at?
I'm not helpless.
Look, kid, I told dark and broody I'd
keep an eye on you and keep you safe.
Hmm. For how much?
[scoffs] Not enough.
[birds squawk]
[camera beeping]
[GS-8] We have reached
our destination.
[Tech] There are six exterior guards
and multiple heat signatures inside.
Four in the subterranean level.
[Echo] Why do I get the
feeling you're setting us up?
It is against my programming
to send my allies into danger.
- [Wrecker] We ain't allies, tin bin.
- [Hunter] Enough.
We need to take out the
compound's surveillance system.
Move in.
[camera beeping]
[clone trooper groans]
[Hunter] Time to
make yourself useful.
[GS-8] I do not possess a military
skill set for a tactical advantage.
[Hunter] We're counting on it.
[clone trooper] You! This
is a restricted area!
To whom are you addressing?
This is my master's residence.
I suggest you leave before...
Oh, dear.
[clone trooper] Stop! Stop!
- [blows landing]
- [clone troopers groan]
[camera beeping]
[beeping continues on datapad]
[Tech] I am tapped into
their security system.
[Hunter] You two,
clear the upper levels.
Tech, we'll take the
main floor and below.
Droid, you're sticking with me.
[clone trooper groans]
[Hunter] There's
two at the door.
[Tech] I'm clocking four
in the adjacent corridor.
[Hunter] I'll handle them. You
and Omega loop back around.
[Tech] That would be impossible,
seeing as Omega is not on this mission.
- [Hunter] Ah, right.
- [GS-8] Not to worry.
- I am getting the hang of this.
- [Hunter] No, wait!
Excuse me, guards.
I appear to be lost.
Can you direct me to
the nearest egress?
[stun grenade humming]
[Hunter shouts]
[clone trooper sighs]
[GS-8] Do be careful.
This antique vase was gifted to
Senator Singh for his years of service.
It is priceless.
[Hunter] Droids.
[up-tempo music playing]
[tall alien laughs]
You've got her cornered!
Oh, yeah, I'm real scared.
Delay all you want, you're
not getting out of this one.
[Omega] I wouldn't do that.
Hear that? We got
an expert here.
[dejarik figure whistles]
- [dejarik figures roar, shriek]
- [tall alien laughs] She's done for!
I told you.
Well, expert, what
should I do next?
- [dejarik figure whimpers]
- [tall alien groans] You blew it!
[dejarik figure shrieks]
Yeah, but you're the one
who said to bet it all!
[tall alien] You wanna
take this outside?
Gladly!
How'd you know to do that?
It's a strategy game.
I'm good at strategy.
Hmm.
How good?
Enough to, uh, win a few
matches for some money?
Depends.
What's my cut?
Hmm.
Thirty percent.
Sixty.
[interrogation droid humming]
[captain] Defying Imperial law
and openly inciting civil discord.
I thought we had an
understanding, Senator.
I refuse to be your puppet.
My loyalty is to the
people, not the Empire.
An unwise choice.
Regardless, we will acquire
what we need from you.
Your draconian tactics won't
work on me, Captain Bragg.
That would be a first.
[rapid humming]
- [blaster firing]
- [Bragg shouts]
[device beeps]
[GS-8] Senator!
I followed your
instructions to the letter.
I knew you'd come through, GS-8.
And behold. I have saved
your most prized vase.
[Hunter] Great. Now
can we get out of here?
With pleasure.
- [datapad beeps]
- [Tech] An alert has been triggered.
[alarm blares]
- Our position has been compromised.
- [Hunter] Follow us.
[alarm blaring]
[clone trooper] Come on!
[Hunter] There.
We'll seize that tank and
blow our way outta here.
[GS-8] How do you intend to gain control
of the armored vehicle from up here?
[Wrecker] Coming through.
[clone trooper groans]
[clone trooper shouts, groans]
[Tech] All clear.
[GS-8] Impressive.
You can't possibly
expect me to do that.
[Wrecker sighs]
- Just don't look down.
- [Singh] Oh!
[Singh grunts, pants]
[GS-8] Nicely done.
[Hunter] Get this
thing moving, Tech.
[Wrecker] They'll feel
that in the morning.
- [comm beeps]
- They've commandeered one of the walkers.
Pin them down.
[Tech] The rear axle
stabilizer is off-line.
We will need to
recalibrate manually.
[Hunter] Get this bucket up and running.
Wrecker and I will hold them off.
[clone troopers groan]
[Wrecker] No, you don't!
- [blaster fires]
- [clone trooper shouts]
- [Hunter] Wrecker.
- [Wrecker laughing] Oh!
Oh, yeah!
[shell whistles]
[Hunter grunts]
Tech, how we doing?
[Tech] I need more time.
[clone trooper] Freeze.
Drop your weapons.
You there.
[GS-8] Senator!
I never much cared
for that vase.
- Repairs complete.
- [Hunter] We're on our way.
Turn down that alleyway.
[Tech] We'll be trapped
in a choke point.
You're going to
have to trust me.
[oil splashing]
[clone trooper] They're
moving into a dead end.
Move into position next to that wall.
It leads to a subterranean passage.
If you don't mind, please blast
a hole in the wall right here.
[Wrecker] That I can do.
[explosion]
[rodents screech]
Hurry. This way.
Captain, the walker's empty.
What am I doing?
I cannot abandon my people.
I must help them.
[GS-8] You will, Senator, but not
if you are in Imperial custody.
[Echo] She's right. Live
to fight another day.
- [whistling, cheering in distance]
- What's all this?
- No one can stop this kid.
- [people cheering]
Of course.
[onlookers gasp, murmur]
[onlookers gasp]
[cheering]
[man] Oh, she did it again!
[onlookers applaud]
All right, show's
over. No more bets.
Kid, where'd you
learn to do that?
She's a natural. I've never
seen anything like it.
I told you to keep a low
profile. This is the opposite.
Ease up, Bandana.
Omega made enough money to pay
off the debt you boys owe me,
so try showing a little
gratitude to my friend.
You did good.
Senator, glad you made it.
Let's talk payment.
You really paid off our debt?
I wanted to be useful, even if
I couldn't go on the mission.
[Hunter] Hmm.
How about we put those
strategy skills to the test?
One match.
If you win, then no more
sitting out on missions.
You ready for this?
Are you?