[Tech] It's not an exact fit.
I get my own comm device?
Technically, it was Crosshair's,
but he doesn't appear to need it.
[echoes over comm] Echo,
what's your position? Over.
[clears throat] It's
not a toy, Omega.
Copy that.
Why are we going to Ord Mantell?
I thought the plan was to lay low.
Not while a bounty hunter's after
you. We need to find out why.
I know an informant there named
Cid who might be able to help.
And you trust him?
Well, the Jedi trusted him.
The Jedi who are all dead?
Well, anyone have
a better option?
[Omega on comm] He has a point.
Right. Not a toy.
[Hunter] Remember the rules?
Don't wander off, keep my eyes
and ears on my surroundings,
and trust no one but my squad.
- [Echo] And if you get into trouble?
- Use my comm and give my location.
[Echo] This is the place.
[Tech] Charming.
[big alien] Filthy
cheat! I saw that!
[small alien] Me? Who
are you calling a cheat?
Which one of them is Cid?
I couldn't tell ya.
I only heard about Cid.
Never actually met him.
That would have been
information to share earlier.
We're looking for
Cid. You know him?
[big alien] You
know what you did!
- Cid, huh?
- [small alien laughs]
You broke the machine again
with your stupid hands!
Nope. Doesn't ring a bell.
What about them?
[big alien] I'll break
you with my stupid hands.
Was I not clear? You're
in the wrong place.
So unless you're here to
spend money, get lost.
Great plan, Echo.
I'm certain this is Cid's.
The Jedi came here
during the war.
[Tech] Well, perhaps Cid heard
what happened to the Jedi and fled.
Or he was arrested for violating
countless health code regulations.
What's your deal, tiny?
You're Cid.
You're sharper than
your friends over there.
Did the Jedi have
any other informants?
Several, but Cid was the
only one I knew how to find.
So, we came all this
way for nothing?
[Omega on comm] I found Cid.
I had a good thing
going with the Jedi.
They valued my insights,
but now that they're all dead, the
demand for my services has declined.
Thanks to this new Empire.
Times have changed...
for all of us.
No kidding.
I never had clone deserters
come to me before.
Yes, well, we separated due to a
fundamental difference in ideology.
That's cute, you
thinking I care.
Cut to it and tell
me what you want.
By all means, make
yourself at home.
We encountered this
woman on Pantora.
Do you know who she is?
No, but I know a bounty
hunter when I see one.
Can you find out who hired her?
That depends on what
you boys do for me.
Are you fresh outta the tube?
You pull a job for me, and I
get the information you want.
That's how this
mercenary thing works.
Mercenary?
Not too quick, are ya?
Clearly, the kid's the
brains of your operation.
[sighs] What kind of job?
A rescue.
There's a nice bounty
on a kid named Muchi.
My sources say she was
taken by Zygerrian slavers
who are holed up on the
other side of the planet.
Bring me the kid and
I'll get you your intel.
Well, who collects the bounty?
Oh, look. It talks.
We split the bounty 70-30, my
favor. Take it or leave it.
Grab a kid from
a few Zygerrians?
[laughs] We could do
that in our sleep.
Looks like we have a deal.
Details of the
bounty are on that.
Don't screw it up.
[groans]
You all right?
Yeah, yeah. It's nothing.
According to Cid's intel,
the Zygerrian slave traders are hiding
in the ruins of Old Ord Mantell city.
What's a slave trader?
Someone who buys and
sells people for credits.
People can be sold?
They don't have a choice. They're
captives treated like property.
That... doesn't seem right.
It's not.
And we are going to stop it
from happening to that kid.
As well as earn a decent amount of
credits once the job is complete.
Yeah, that too.
Don't worry, Muchi.
We'll rescue you.
[Tech] I have a visual.
I only see one child.
Poor Muchi. She looks scared.
[Tech] I'm clocking
two dozen hostiles.
Multiple entry points
with minor fortification.
[Wrecker] Simple smash and
grab like that time on Kuat.
Easy enough.
I'm in. What are we waiting for?
- [Hunter] You get back to the ship.
- But...
[Hunter] That's an order.
Yes, sir.
[Hunter] Echo, you're
the eyes in the sky.
Wrecker, draw the Zygerrian forces
out. Tech and I will grab the kid.
[Wrecker] Not a problem.
[brezak growls]
[Hunter] Echo, sitrep.
[Echo] Two roving
patrols on speeders.
First guard
checkpoint dead ahead.
[brezak growls]
Hang on. I think
I've got company.
[Hunter] Well, take
care of it. Quietly.
- [brezak shrieks]
- [Echo groans]
- [brezak shrieking]
- [Hunter] Watch out!
[hologram speaking Huttese]
A mission of this nature
requires planning.
Assure your employer, he'll
be reunited with Muchi soon.
[speaking Huttese]
Now, now. There's
no need for threats.
I have my best people on it.
- [servos whirring]
- [droid honking]
I'm making some
alterations to my trooper.
Now she's a Bad Batcher.
- What do you think?
- [droid honks]
[Zygerrian] We found their ship.
Gonky, hide.
[Gonky honking]
Check the hold.
Make sure no one's on board.
The ship is clear.
We're returning to base.
- Hunter, do you copy?
- [static on comm]
Tech? Echo? Wrecker?
Anyone?
[exhales]
It's getting looser.
[groans]
Do that one more
time and you'll be...
[groans]
Save your energy. We
are going to need it.
[brezak shrieks]
[brezak growls]
[shrieks]
[child whimpering]
Relax, Muchi. We're the cavalry.
What are our odds
out of this, Tech?
I am not certain.
So much for being smart.
[sighs] This is not a
standard military operation,
and seeing as how
we've never been tasked
with rescuing a child
from slave traders before,
there is no data I
can compare it to.
We need to signal Omega
before their scouts find her.
Except our comms are over
there with our weapons.
We won't need a
comm to signal her.
[door opens]
Look at what we have here.
Four new slaves to
add to my collection.
Strong ones too.
You should fetch a nice price.
The Republic outlawed slavery.
We're not in the
Republic anymore, skug.
You're lucky we
don't have our gear
because this would go
very differently for you.
- [gasps]
- [boulder thuds]
[grunts]
[snarls]
We can make do with
one less slave.
Maybe I'll feed you to my pet.
[brezak shrieks]
[Zygerrian leader] As for the rest of
you, you will be part of a new beginning.
With the meddling Republic gone,
we can return to Kadavo and
rebuild what was taken from us.
Under this new Empire, our
operation will flourish once again.
[growling]
- And if you do not comply...
- Hmm.
I know.
[Zygerrian leader] ...the person
next to you will pay the price.
[growling continues]
- [Omega grunts] No...
- Gotcha!
[straining] Let me go!
[guard] I found her
sneaking around the cage.
I wasn't sneaking.
I was unlocking.
- [thumping]
- [snarling]
Secure the cage.
[roars]
Stop her. Don't
let her get away.
[roaring]
[roars]
A rampaging adolescent rancor is not
the distraction I was anticipating.
That's their problem.
We're getting out of here.
[Zygerrian screams]
[whistles]
[shrieks]
[roars]
It's okay, Muchi.
We're here to take you home.
[speaking Falleen]
Muchi! Muchi!
The rancor is Muchi?
[Zygerrian screams]
[Hunter] Gear up. We
have to go after Muchi.
If we don't capture her, we
don't get our intel from Cid.
[Zygerrians shout]
[Muchi roaring in distance]
What about them?
[Echo] Omega and I will get
them to safety. You find Muchi.
[Hunter] Right. Go for the
speeders at the south entrance.
[Tech speaks Falleen]
[Muchi roaring]
[Zygerrian screams]
[roars]
She's doing fine on her own.
- [Zygerrians screams]
- [Muchi roars]
[roars]
[Zygerrian screams]
[brezak shrieks]
[roars]
Hyah!
[shrieks]
[whines]
[groans]
[growls]
You're going to
pay for this, skug.
[Hunter] I'll handle
him. Go get Muchi.
[groans]
[grunts]
[Zygerrian shouts, screams]
[Echo] Omega, stay close!
[brezak growling, shrieking]
[shrieks]
[roars]
[brezak shrieks]
[Wrecker] Any ideas
how to stop that thing?
[Tech] Rancors adhere
to a social hierarchy.
[roars]
[Tech] You have to challenge
the alpha for authority.
[roars]
[Wrecker] Oh, that
I can do. [Shouts]
[Muchi growls, roars]
[shouts]
[Echo] You're free. Go quickly.
[speaks Falleen]
Bye.
[Echo] Come on. Let's
get back to the others.
- [Muchi growling, roaring]
- [Wrecker grunting]
[Echo] How long's
he been at this?
[Tech] Too long. He's
losing his touch.
- [Wrecker] Oh. You...
- [Muchi roars]
[Wrecker groans]
- Come on, Muchi.
- [Muchi whines]
Go to sleep.
[Muchi snoring]
[Wrecker groans] There we go.
Aw. She's kinda cute up close.
[Hunter] Nicely
handled, Wrecker.
[Wrecker grunts, chuckles]
What a pleasant surprise.
I'm graced by the presence
of Jabba's right-hand man.
[Bib Fortuna speaking Huttese]
Bib, relax.
I always deliver on my
promises. You'll see.
[speaks Huttese]
I told you, this is
a delicate mission.
Tell Jabba to be patient.
[Muchi roars in distance]
Oh, Muchi.
[Gamorrean squeals]
[Muchi roars]
Aw. That's a good rancor.
Ah.
- [speaks Huttese]
- [Muchi purring]
See, Bib? All is well.
Now, about the
matter of payment.
- [Bib snaps]
- [Gamorrean grunts]
[speaks Huttese]
Bye, Muchi.
[roars]
Gotta say, fellas.
I wasn't sure you could
pull this job off.
You could have told us we
were going after a rancor.
Hmm. Must've slipped my mind.
You, dark and broody. My office.
Your bounty hunter
is Fennec Shand.
She's new to the scene
but has already proven herself
to be cunning and ruthless.
Who hired her?
Unknown.
My sources in the Guild say she's
working on a direct commission.
With someone like her
nipping at your heels,
you're going to need two
things: Friends and money.
Mostly money.
Well, we're not swimming
in either at the moment.
I guess it's a good thing
ya met me then, isn't it?
Here's your cut.
There's more where
that came from
if you're looking for work.
I'll think about it.
[Cid] It's interesting,
a bounty hunter of Fennec's
caliber being after you.
You fellas must be
pretty valuable.
Don't worry.
I'm good with secrets.