Gentlemen, when I look
at this battlefield,
I see some of the
bravest men who have ever worn a uniform.
Is that you, Johnson?
You are a real
lazy piece of shit.
Johnson, right!
Sorry sir.
Just guarding the tank.
You were Sleeping.
I heard you.
But it's so comfortable here.
me, huh...
what drug
And you, stop posing.
- Sorry sir.
Damn showboats.
Excuse me, dear captain.
What you want?
Can I get some cigarettes?
- No.
- How about a rifle?
You are a prisoner of war.
That doesn't mean we
can still be friends.
- Not really.
- Really?
I had never heard that.
How about a horn?
We already have a guy
who plays the horn.
I can definitely
play better than he can.
It is true. I'm bad.
I won't give you a bugle.
If I had my way, I would kill
every German in this place.
But you've already killed all
the Germans in this place.
I would do it again in a
heartbeat, so don't test me.
There. It's very cruel
to threaten someone
with a
war crime, my friend.
We are not friends...
Sir, I see something there.
What was it? Where is Johnson?
Yeehaw.
Johnson, you imbecile!
Everyone run!
This is the "Video Journal
of Neurosurgery" with...
Guys, I said
the list is endless.
So why wait?
Call this toll
free number and order now.
Please stop.
Oh wait.
It's so cool.
Let's go.
No!
Man, I'm going crazy.
Yea! Yea!
I'm out of my mind.
Ahh!
Screw this!
Shh. Hey.
What's going on, man.
Get out of here! Stop!
Hey, make sure to clean.
♪ Writing this down ♪
♪ Because she knows
I'll never leave her ♪
♪ Because I can't live without her ♪
Pick it up and throw it on the floor.
Do you want some of this?
This is my dick.
That's right, it's big.
Now, don't be a pussy.
Oh shit. Are you hurt?
♪ I don't think you ever
made a big mistake ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't want to get
you off my back ♪
♪ No wonder we hate
the same things ♪
♪ I hate everyone ♪
Let's fuck everything!
♪ I don't think you ever
made a big mistake ♪
Welcome everyone to the party of...
- Let's fuck everything!
This is yours.
That's the closest you
It's going to be something of
mine, you little girl.
- Oh!
- cove to mouth
I get the pussy.
- Ah, you understand what...
- I get pussy.
- Yea.
- Who's a fag?
Dick.
Let me take a picture of this
beautiful piece of meat right here.
- Look this.
- It looks good on you.
Why do you look
hotter than Rachel?
- Who wore it best?
- That's what I'm saying.
Poor Rachel.
Don't even make that comparison.
I'm fine as fuck, man.
Listen, this is a
very special episode, because
tonight, RACK
is going on a mission.
We're invading the Colony!
Don't use that word, idiot.
What is wrong with you?
We are visiting Cologne.
The infamous Underground Colony.
Why do you have to keep
acting so effeminate lately?
It's you and what, Mohammed?
Anyone who, for
those of you born yesterday,
The Colony Underground
was very perverse like that...
It was an art collective.
"Was it an artist collective?"
So this art collective
had shows all the time.
It was for all
ages, and some bands
big ones came
from the city, like the KGB,
Eddie Cash e os Star
Fuckers, Valentine Fox,
- mostly pumped hardcore stuff.
- Yea.
We would totally
have played there.
- Yea.
- Certainly.
- Serious.
- We would have if it wasn't
by the strange fire
electric that
happened three years ago.
- Wait, is this really serious?
- Yes, March 6, 1996.
It's March 5th.
Can you let him talk? God!
Three years ago, a
strange electrical fire
fritou o interior do
The Colony Underground
and claimed four innocent lives.
The life of the band
that played that night.
Legend says that their bodies
were only burned after
of being trampled to
death by their own fans.
Fans so desperate
to escape the flames
who crushed their heroes
without a second thought.
Honey, go on.
Hum?
Oh, yes, yes, see how
scared Ankur looks.
Shut up, I'm fine.
Oh, your left pocket.
Ankur is a little bitch?
Let's see, let's see.
Hey, it's spinning! It's spinning.
I swear to God, look, look, look!
Ok, ok, ok.
So that band was Bitch Cat.
Can you put some things
from the tape you have in there?
- Yea.
- It would be a nice edit.
what fita?
Oh, man, it's so sick.
At church. Can't you say?
♪ You want it your way ♪
♪ Well, why don't you stay like this? ♪
♪ Ah, keep poking at face ♪
♪ Eat cake like you... ♪
Well, we weren't made
by a corporation.
We made our sound and
our following bases.
♪ What will it take? ♪
♪ I think I've seen it all ♪
♪ I know I've seen too much, oh ♪
♪ My God, what could it take? ♪
We entered na van de
Dierdre and basically
we played
wherever it took us.
- We're road warriors, man.
- Yea.
♪ Don't mind
your angels ♪
♪ Get off my back, boy ♪
We don't even feel
like we relate to LA anymore.
Like, that stage is our home.
Yeah and the fans our
family for sure.
Our shows are
these big parties.
Everyone belongs.
Everyone has a killer time.
♪ Too bad because I say ♪
Of course.
I mean, what's a party
without a little violence?
♪ We went out to play ♪
♪ Get off my stage, bro ♪
♪ Get the fuck off my stage ♪
♪ My God, what could it be? ♪
I think America has, like,
an anger revolution on its way.
Everyone is so angry.
♪ Come on, come on ♪
Everyone's father got very rich.
Yeah, so give us all
your damn money, Daddy.
Give us your money!
♪ Bad boy, you already know ♪
♪ I'm no angel ♪
♪ Diamonds turn black ♪
Play or die.
Play or die!
Oh my God, look how
angry he is.
Hey! Quickly! Come on! Come on.
Hey, wait, wait.
Tell everyone about
today's mission.
RACK is heading to
The Colony Underground
to do a show about
what's left on that stage.
And we're gonna suck because
we're rehearsing,
what, two months?
Yes, show yourself to
your Nazi dictator father.
- I hope it's...
- Oh my God, whatever.
No, wait, come on.
Like, what else?
- What else?
- I don't know.
Let's get the equipment,
if there's any that work.
Yes, but why did you
stop here? It's your house?
- Come on, K.
- Hey, no.
I just think
curious minds want to know if
you're really just
scared, little bitch.
That's all I want to know!
Come on!
Hey, I'm sorry. I
meant a little baby
scared that he thinks he
's going to meet some ghosts.
Hey Rachel, get the camera.
Get the fucking camera, Rachel.
Why is Ankur
being such a bitch now?
It seems
You want your mama because
you don't come home.
Stay away from me!
Oh no! The ghost ladies
will eat me.
Man, I can't believe
we're here now.
Come on, it's gonna be fun.
C'mon C'mon.
Rach, these girls
seem kind.
I just don't think we should
fuck up their graves.
But, like, you have
to say why.
Come on, you'll make
a better video.
I think it will be cool.
OK everything is fine.
So, you know
these stories, okay?
Hindu stories about bhuts.
- Bhuts?
- Yes, dead people.
Restless spirits with
unfinished business, and supposedly
if you bother them they
won't like it, they'll just...
They go what?
They'll own you, okay?
- Yea!
- We're in.
So, is that why you went home
and bought a bag of spices?
They are like spices
for killing ghosts.
Just stop, I don't want to...
Relax, spice boy.
Stop bugging me,
you motherfucker.
Wow, calm your boobs, man.
He, he, wait.
Welcome to what's left
of The Colony Underground.
Like, literally
below ground.
Yes, about six feet below.
It's insane that the whole audience
got out of here alive.
Yeah, well, they sacrifice
the band to do that.
Imagine dying in a stampede.
Herd mentality, man.
sheep.
It still smells like fire here.
Crispy bodies.
Wow.
What is it?
Rachel I don't...
Let's go. Just go.
We will. Hurry up.
Boo!
This place is a total maze.
So many runners.
We've
been down here for 10 minutes.
I have no idea how to get back.
Keep cool. I know the way.
What is this?
Hell how am I supposed to know.
I think someone
lives down here.
Look look. Come here.
Look at this.
Why would anyone
want to live here?
Well, I mean, for a
homeless person, it's not that bad.
- Yeah, I bet.
- Look at all the...
I bet we're not alone.
Dude, seriously.
It's just us here.
- I know it is.
- He's some drug addict,
a homeless man who
licks heroin here.
Can you please stop?
Sorry.
What are you doing?
Stop. Don't go in there.
- Let's go.
- Whooo.
Dude, seriously?
Oh my God. Oh my God.
You are kidding.
- Not really.
- Yeah, fuck it.
Anyway, look,
someone made a shrine.
- What did you think?
- Wow.
No way.
Hey, Kaleb, stop it.
Hey, that's not cool.
Stop, dear.
As you want bro.
Rachel, come here, come here.
Did you see that?
Ew. Is that a boot?
Melted to the floor.
It should belong to one of the girls
in the band, don't you think?
Yeah, I bet my money
it was the bass player.
She wore boots like that.
I'm sure they
all wore boots.
Stop saying that word.
Or what? Boots?
Hey Rach, come here,
you have to see this.
- Or what?
- Shit, no chance.
No way.
Hey Rachel, come here.
- Which? What is it?
- Okay, do you remember?
- Amanda Pears, don't you remember?
- Yea.
Can you tell me
how could she
wait for fat bunda
dela here.
- Dude, there's no way.
- There's no way!
Yes, that's what I'm saying.
Yes, no one likes to be
robbed after asking.
That's why she can no
longer work, except in the
gas station, because
she is very funny.
Ah-ha-ha.
Cum! It felt like
someone pulled me.
Yeah, you tripped, man.
Guys, come quickly!
No no no.
Hey, did you do this?
No way.
Rachel, look at this.
- Did you guys do that?
- No.
No, Anchor.
Surprise, bitch!
You are awesome.
Do you really think some
ghost set this up here?
Not. Did you, like, steal
them from my house?
Yes, I did it.
What did you think of it all?
- Are you going to cry about it?
- You are unreal.
Big crybaby.
All right, everybody try
not to fuck it up, okay?
- Oh, sure.
- You are the boss.
- We will.
- Thanks.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight!
No no no!
Come on!
Guys?
Guys, what the fuck is this?
Guys, is this serious?
Guys, stop it.
You think you're
having a lot of fun right now.
If this is a joke,
I will kill you all.
Yes, let's go.
He's so predictable.
No, we like
you very much with all...
It's been like three times.
I know. Hey.
Tell people what you are...
How are you feeling now?
Mr. Ankur, tell them here.
What?
Man, you have to admit
we got you so good.
Man, it was fun as fuck, man.
Serious.
Man, like, we're
just kidding.
- Look, it was my idea.
- We will.
- I'm sorry.
- Damn it.
Why can't you learn to take
a fucking joke, spice boy?
- Oh or what?
- Ankur.
What are you
doing now, bro?
what the fuck?
What are you doing?
Don't be such a bitch
about it, Ankur! Come back!
Hope the bhuta catches you all!
- Ankur, come on.
- Drug. Or what?
What the hell is he talking about?
So, are we still going
to do the gelatin thing?
Four Bitch Cats.
Four sex dolls.
Welcome back, sick.
We came to
The Colony Underground
to find a very scientific answer to the age-old question.
How hard is it to crush
four puppies to death?
Let's find out.
Are you ready?
Die, bitch!
Oh!
Oh, fuck you bitch.
Are we in trouble here?
Die, bitch!
He is going to screw it up! He is going to screw it up!
Did you hear this?
Yes, it must be a car out there.
A estrada is dated, cara.
Jesus!
Ankur, is that you?
Get the fuck off my stage!
What the fuck?!
Touch or die.
Play or die.
Play or die!
Shit. Oh shit, oh shit!
Please help! Help!
Oh shit, oh shit, oh shit!
You can peacefully go to
your final resting place!
Psychopath dude, I'm going crazy.
Please help me!
Please!
Please someone!
Stop it!
Help!
Anybody here?!
Better!
Stay away from me!
Let me out! Let me out!
No!
It seems!
You can feel
it at the shows now.
Everyone is so angry.
What's a party without
a little violence?
Let's fuck everything!
Too, too.
Hum.
There you are.
Hello.
Hey. Um, I just...
OK.
Hey.
I just had to record
this video after going to
Beta Sigma Eta today and
meet all the girls.
No, it's bad.
It's broken. OKAY.
OK.
I just want
you to know that since the
moment I
joined Beta Sigma Eta
I knew it was my home.
I want you to be
my friends for life
whole, and I will not
apply for more fellowships.
I knew from the
moment you
I knew that we
would become soul sisters.
- A suicide attempt?
- Helen?
I thought you were
studying at the library.
You are only putting one
fellowship in your application.
- A suicide attempt.
- Yes, I know what
a suicide attempt is, Helen.
I am not stupid.
And?
Well then, if they
say no, you will be
excluded from the entire
fellowship process.
And that means spending all
his freshman year
as an outcast.
Do you really want to take
that risk with those girls?
What do you mean
by those girls?
I mean, have you
seen the way they
did they look at us when they
showed us the place?
I mean do you
really think that
Will they say yes
to people like us?
No, not us.
Do you have a cigarette?
I can not do it.
Jesus Christ, Annie.
You will bring the security here.
Why did you take so long?
Do not roll up your panties.
- We had to get some supplies.
- Oh my God.
It turns out that Lily here
really likes to party.
Oh, let's party.
Guys, do you understand?
Do you have the keys?
My father will
kill me if he finds out.
Yes, but do you have the keys?
You know I have.
Come on, let's go!
Come on, it's time.
Oi, Lindsay.
- Oh shit.
- Oh my God.
We're going to have a fun night.
- College Scholarship.
Isn't she cute?
Welcome!
Oh my God,
this place is amazing.
Pretty cool, huh?
Dude, we love your message.
It was so sincere.
Wasn't it girls?
- So cute.
- Adorable.
We were so flattered
that you gave it a try.
of suicide just to
join our brotherhood.
Yes, friends forever.
Yes, soul sisters.
- Soul sisters!
So what are we doing here?
Have you heard of the
Legend of Guiltine?
Guiltine, was a
very young freshman
who went to TCU
maybe 20 years ago.
She wanted to join a
sisterhood, our sisterhood like you.
And she was desperate
and alone, just like you.
And the girls took her
back here to the cemetery.
And they told her that to
be part of their sisterhood,
she had to spend the night
buried in a coffin.
Only they didn't
leave her there for one night.
They left her there
for a whole week.
And when they finally
dug her up...
There was no one there.
What happened to her?
Nobody knows.
Some say she just
crawled straight to the underworld.
And if you listen carefully, at
sometimes you may
hear a tapping sound.
It's Guiltine,
desperate and alone.
Looking for someone
awake that she can
take to the underworld to play.
Drink!
Lily! Lily! Lily! Lily!
We have something for you.
Surprise, bitch.
Do not play!
We want you to join our family.
Right, girls?
We just need you
to do one thing first.
Thanks. OK.
A tiny thing.
We need you
to spend the night in a coffin.
Just like Guiltine.
Come on!
You will have
fun, I promise.
OK.
You will be a little scared.
Oh.
Um, Annie, I don't know if I'm
really wanting to do this.
Oh come on Lily.
We all had to do this.
Did you... have all of you done this?
Of course.
It really isn't that bad.
- I promise.
- OK.
There is enough air in a
coffin to last 24 hours.
The faster
you breathe, the faster
you use your air
not to panic.
You can pull this cord at any
time, and it will ring the bell.
And we're going to dig it up.
But if you do, you will have lost the
your place in our fellowship.
Here it is.
We want to see how
scared you are.
And so, you can see down there.
Just be brave.
It really isn't that bad.
Annie probably won't
let you stay there all night.
Take it.
Only open when you have more
scared and about to pull the string.
It will give you strength. I promise.
Thanks.
Watch out for the Guild.
If you hear her knock,
whatever you do, no
let her know
you're down there.
If you let her know
you're alive, she'll
will take you to the world of the
dead to play.
She's just playing with you.
B-S-E, B-S-E, B-S-E, B-S-E!
Good luck down there.
Don't be too scared.
Oh, it's cute and cozy.
Last words?
Very good.
Lily! Lily!
Lily! Lily! Lily!
Lily! Lily! Lily! Lily!
Wow!
Ah, terra, terra.
Ah, damp earth.
You took my father
and my dear mother.
You took my father and
my dear mother, so
take me too because
I'm very alone.
Goodnight.
He is well.
It's okay, just don't panic.
Do not panic.
Everything is fine.
It's all just for show.
They won't
let you down here.
Come on, you knew
they were going to do this.
I'm not scared.
Oh Helen, if only you
could see me now.
What did you do this weekend?
Library?
Oh, that's cool. I?
Oh, you know, the usual,
just buried alive in a coffin.
No, that's what
you want, isn't it?
You want me to fail so
I can end up like you.
Sad and lonely every
Friday night wishing for a
boy, any boy
would ask you out.
But I'm not like you.
I'm like them.
He is well.
It's gonna be okay.
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
She is probably very scared.
The box, the box.
what shit?
Oh, poor baby.
Poor Lily.
Let me out!
Let me out! Let me out!
Oh my God.
She is definitely shit.
- Let me out!
Let me out!
Hit or else.
If they find out we
're making a
prank prank,
we'll all be expelled.
Cum! My father will kill me!
Nobody will be expelled.
Let's hide and
come back later.
Mas e a Lily?
I said we'll be back later.
Come on.
Hey, dispatch for
1061 no cemetery,
Answer us by updating.
Fuck this.
Let's go back inside
before we hit pneumonia.
Help!
I need help!
Let me out! Let me out!
Let me out!
Let me out! Please!
Please someone!
Helen, if you've seen this,
I just want you to know
that I'm really sorry.
I was such an idiot.
You are my best friend.
You are my only real friend.
I don't know why I thought I could
fit in with those girls.
I don't know why
I even wanted to.
Oh my God.
No! No!
No! No! Let me out!
Let me out!
No! Help-me!
Oh my God!
No! No! No!
Please! No!
Please help me!
Please help!
No!
Help!
Oh my God!
Annie?
Annie, let me out!
Let me out!
Oh my God!
I will be sick.
Are you filming now?
We have to throw it out.
It is too late.
Imogen, no.
He's empty.
What are you talking about?
The coffin is empty.
Lily is not in.
That's not possible.
- What if Guiltine took her?
- Don't be stupid.
Guiltine is just a story.
We were never here, okay?
We'll never talk about it again.
understand?
Hello?
Hello?!
Hi Annie.
I made a deal with Guiltine
that if she let me go,
I would give her as many
sisters as she could want.
Your own brotherhood...
soul sisters.
Let me out!
Oh my God!
Anderson, are you alive?
Tell me honestly, Sergeant.
I will die?
No, no.
You'll be fine.
My legs.
I can't feel my legs.
Why can't I feel my legs?
Y-You're in shock.
Everything will be fine.
It's all getting dark.
So, so dark.
Oh, damn, he's dead.
I really thought
he was going to make it.
Alright, no one else was
bitten in half by the rat monster.
♪ No ♪
♪ That's right, boy ♪
Welcome, welcome.
Welcome to "Ozzy's Dungeon",
where boys and girls
fight toe to toe
for the opportunity to have
your favorite wish granted.
That's right, folks.
Anything
your heart desires can
be yours if you go
through the obstacle course
not Dungeon Ozzy.
Let's start with
our first challenge!
Are you ready? OK.
AND...
Pop those balloons!
Oh come on la.
What do you want?
I want to be a
basketball player
most famous and best in the world.
You don't want to drown, fool.
He's going to be fine, guys.
That's what Ozzy
Dungeon, dungeon does.
Here we go with
our first class team
Aid always on hand
to take care of the boys
and girls who
can trip and fall.
They will be...
They will be fine eventually.
Oh.
I think my stomach is
trying to tell me something.
Anyone else hungry out there?
- I!
OK then!
Who hasn't seen this movie?
Now our
first team to catch
successfully one
of these delicious,
beautiful coxas from peru
no bucket com a boca
will go to the next round.
Let's start.
Ready and...
Get that meat!
It was pretty close, Blue team.
Ah, team Amarela,
let's have it
open that mouth a little more.
Oh come on la.
Come on.
Let's open that mouth.
Oh, and we have a winner.
Largue. Largue!
Good girl. Tell us
her name and where she's from.
Donna, and I'm
from Detroit, Michigan.
Oh, Donna gives big D.
Well, you traveled a lot
to get here, didn't you?
Mm-hmm.
We drove all the way here.
- Did you drive?
- Hm-hm.
In a car?
What? You can't
afford to fly?
- We're actually doing...
- Right.
So, now you know how
difficult the next challenge is, don't you?
Hmm?
Now, many people cannot.
In fact, nobody can, Donna.
But I have a hunch.
Oh yes, I have a hunch.
And that feeling
starts at my feet.
And it goes higher and higher,
and higher and higher.
Anyone else feel this?
Oh yeah.
Oh can you feel it Donna?
Now tell me.
What makes you think
you're better than everyone else
the boys and girls
who came before you?
Well, my family says
I can do anything.
I put my mind to it.
I know I can.
Right. Of course.
We'll see.
I like that.
Okay, well Donna, let's just
say that fate
smiled on you
and by some absurd miracle
you make it to the end...
What will you wish for?
I will wish...
Any talent lurking
out there that I should know about?
And welcome back
to "Ozzy's Dungeon".
I'm here with the two
remaining contestants.
We got Donna from the
big D, Detroit,
Michigan and Timmy
of the City of Angels,
Los Angeles California.
Okay, so who's
ready for the ultimate challenge?
Okay kids, let's
start doing
our way through
Ozzy's holes
and make our way
back to find
a flag hidden
in the cracked rock.
Then we climb the ladder and
go through the mouth hole and
down the throat, ending up
in this disgusting, dirty stomach.
And then through
the green gelatin,
let's look and let's find
ourselves a red flag.
And with that red flag,
let's crawl with our hands
and knees through the
large intestine, and in
then along the
poop chute escape route.
Eca!
Now if you beat the
clock, and you give it to me
the red flag
before time runs out,
you will be the first contestant
to reach the dungeon,
meet Ozzy and have
that favorite wish...
guaranteed.
Try!
Okay, now before
anything else,
let's have a minute
on the clock, please.
Wait, children, wait.
Wait until I speak.
In your brands...
get ready...
They go! Through the holes.
And they're out
through the... Oh!
Timmy, what
a horrible start to the game.
Come on.
This is a terrible start.
Now go get or bring that flag.
Let's get going.
Oh, Donna already got the
red flag
and climbed the ladder.
Come on dear!
And here it goes down the throat.
All right, let's look
for that red flag.
Oh, Timmy is dating lacuna.
Oh, adventurer.
Very good, Timmy.
You really did.
All right guys, we don't
want to get the uniform dirty.
We found...
Oh, God, you've got the flag.
In the gut you go now.
Timmy is not very good.
One of those... There he goes.
Oh, Timmy almost
stood there for a second.
Okay, let's see
who will come out of this
big long
pink hole first.
Who will come out of the intestine
long and winding first?
Oh, there she is.
It's Donna leaving...
Ooh, someone got hurt.
No! No, Donna!
Donna! No, let me go there!
I'll get Timmy!
You can not do that!
Have Jesus.
We may need a band-aid.
Oh, for love.
Don't put that in my shoes.
Do not do it. Here it is.
You're out, carry on.
Come on, Donna.
Stop the game, please.
Please stop the game!
- Wait, your mother!
- Please stop the game!
Donna arriving.
Ooh, someone got hurt.
No, Donna!
Donna!
Throw that shit.
Yes mom.
Do you know where you are?
Huh?
Hum?
Does none of this look familiar to you?
This is my set.
It's a pretty good replica, huh?
Oh come on la
You will hurt
Marcus' feelings.
- He worked really hard on it.
- Marcus?
- Didn't you, honey?
- I don't know any Marcus.
Yes.
Okay, how about
Donna, my daughter?
- Who?
- From Detroit?
I don't know a
Donna from Detroit.
We have a lot of kids on set.
How many were made?
Ah!
You signed the waiver.
You signed a waiver.
Everyone... everyone
signs a waiver.
Baby?
Baby? Come on, dear.
Who cares about
a goddamn quit, bro?
Honey, honey,
your blood pressure.
- Mommy?
- I just...
I think I just need to
take this shirt off.
You fucked up.
Barely...
Oh my God.
What are you doing?
That's better.
Do you know what it
looked like to me?
It's just that you
motherfuckers created a track
impossible obstacles that
shattered a little star.
She would be the only one.
She will be the one to leave.
He is well.
But look at that leg!
Show him that mutilated bitch!
- Live? live?
- Ah!
Because it seems...?
Nobody wants to see
that on the big screen.
What does it look like?
- I don't know. It looks...
- What does it look like? Say!
- I don't know, it looks like...
- It looks like dog meat!
Looks like puppy meat, okay?
Fuck you, you idiot.
Don't do it, honey.
I'm sorry.
We almost had a winner
before everything was cancelled.
Okay, I mean the
show is not rigged.
Your showbiz,
motherfuckers from LA leave my
pussy drier
than the Sahary desert.
- Sarah, dear.
- Cala to mouth.
Oh fuck.
Let's just...
- Suffice it to say it's not manipulated.
- No.
Can't you
prove this theory?
- Or what?
- Huh?!
What? What the
fuck are you talking about?
Fred, swallow me or mug.
Q-Which?
One who has no water.
You can't do this, honey.
I won't say it again.
The fuck is in it? Huh?
What the fuck is there?
I didn't tell you I'd
get your cast
dreams if you did
what i told you to do?
- Yea.
- Cum?
My people know I'm here.
They're going to come after
me, you know, right?
They will come after me.
What the fuck is this?
oh! Club!
- Honey!
- Keep that shit away from me.
Raise-o.
Look, if we give every kid
their wish, we'd be fucked.
You know we're without a budget.
Ah!
Oh, what's the problem? Huh?
Are you worried
about your beautiful
face bubbling and
melting on my floor?
- Just...
- Huh?
Smell it!
Ooh.
Welcome, welcome, welcome.
What the fuck are you doing?
This is the first challenge.
No, no.
No, I need a helmet!
- Three two one!
- No, untie me!
- Untie me!
- To charge!
Oh! Oh fuck!
Are you ready for
our next challenge?
Huh?
Are you hungry?
Because it's lunch time!
- Very good.
- What the hell is that?
Three two one!
Get that meat!
No! No! No!
- Wow!
- No!
Lets go Girl.
- Here it is.
- No!
Takes it!
Come on, doggy, get it!
I really can't catch it.
- Takes it.
- I am trying!
- Takes it!
Lets go Girl.
Let me show you how to do this.
I can't catch.
You have to
put it here and then...
Just put everything
in his mouth hole.
Oh, that's right, doggie.
It took very well.
Oh shit.
Ah.
Brandon, get that
damn camera off the floor.
Okay, Mr. game show host.
Now, when I say, you
're going to jump through these holes.
Go up the ladder, up
through the mouth, down the
stomach slide
to this pool here.
Mm-mm-mmm.
Oh my God.
Then you will
find a flag.
when you find this
flag, you
will leave this way,
go through the bowels,
make your way through everyone
your slides and
slides until you reach the exit.
You have 60 seconds.
What is all this brown stuff?
Well, it sure isn't bean sauce.
What if I don't finish?
No!
- Get ready.
- Okay.
Ready, go!
Come on doggy, come on.
Run that run,
run that run, run that run!
Here it is.
Try!
I can not. I can not.
You still have more
things to do!
Go under the poop shooter.
I don't think I
can get through this.
Go through everything.
Oh oh oh.
Time is running out.
Will he make it?
Through the shit city.
Go under.
I am going. I am going.
I can do this.
I achieved!
I achieved! I achieved!
I won your stupid game.
I just couldn't
do it, could I, son?
I beat the fucking clock.
You are a few seconds late.
I'm very sorry.
Brandon, get up-o.
No!
No winners.
No wishes.
Just pain.
- What is this?
What is this thing?
What is this?
Wishes.
This is all about wishes, right?
Right?
I can help make her wish come true.
I can help you.
Are you fucking with me now?
No, no.
I thought Ozzy was
out of this world, cancelled.
I know where is.
Baby, does this thing
do super close-ups?
'Cause I'm going to show
you all how to make a damn...
No! No!
I'll take you to him!
I will take you to him.
what the hell?
The security got
a little…robust.
Okay, okay. Everything is fine.
We can't
get in here anymore.
We have to go deep hairs.
What the fuck do you mean
he can't go this way?
Club.
Do you remember that, Donna?
Don't talk to him, honey.
He is well. Everything is fine.
You leave my girl alone.
You've done enough.
He is well.
Do you trust this guy, baby?
Of course not, but it is
here we have to be.
Oh shit.
- Go ahead, honey.
- OK.
Go ahead, I'll follow you.
All right, Donna baby.
Mom said she
'll get your wish.
I will get your wish.
This is a real cave.
What the fuck do you mean
by a real cave?
I had never
walked through the door before.
Oh shit.
We'll be fine.
I guarantee I'm meaner than
anything we'll find here.
We want that
new car and $10... $15 million. OK?
Don't promise her
all these things.
Shit to mouth, Vinn.
Yes, Mom, I'm scared.
It's so dark here.
Can you hear this song baby?
- Mnh-mnh.
- No?
What... What?
What is that?
Baby?
Wait.
What?
Here.
He is well.
What are you doing?
He knows my aura.
Make it a good wish, girl.
Mommy Daddy? What the hell is that?
Mom, Dad, what...
- What the hell is that?
- No!
- Jesus!
- Mommy!
Papi!
What the hell?!
What... What the hell is she...
Get down, get down.
Which...?
I don't understand.
What the fuck is going on?
Oh!
What did you do, bitch?!
What did you wish for?!
What the fuck are you
doing, loser?
Hey. Hey, is that my camera?
No, don't put your hand...
No.
Oh. Oh, do you like it?
Oh, do you like these?
Yes, I thought you would.
Yes, I'm a big boy.
Oh, do you like big boys?
Yes, I thought you would.
Someone better call the
vet, these pythons are sick.
Did you say something, honey?
Yes, yes, yes, no... Don't come in.
Do not do it. I am studying.
OK.
What do you want for lunch?
Hot Pockets.
God, of course.
Holy crap.
No no. No. No! No!
Hey, you there. Come on...
Is that a camera?
No... I'll tell your parents.
No!
What a drug!
No, shh, shh, shh.
Sh, sh.
Hey, should we get the cream?
Do it again, do it again.
Oh!
- Fucking shit.
- Bonner.
- Boner, what happened, bro?
- What happened friend?
- You got me.
- Did you just come on yourself?
Was that cool, bro?
Wow, man, this is crazy.
- Wow.
- What the hell is that?
Wow, what is this?
What... hey.
Ah, man, that's a
gnarled snake, bro.
An anaconda.
Look at that strip, man.
Oh!
- Hey!
- Eca! Shit, hand.
Hey, Boner, I'll give you 50 cents
if you eat right now.
I'll fuck your
mother for 50 cents, bro.
Oh!
I don't believe this boy.
Hey, after that, we should head
upstairs to Blockbuster, yeah?
No, man, RadioShack
is way better.
No, man, I was there yesterday.
Not. You're traveling, bro.
Bro, do you know who
they look like to me?
Oh shit.
- Club.
- Expensive.
Brother, are you okay?
- I am fine.
- Oh!
- Oh shit. I-is this normal?
- No, no.
Dave, it's not real.
There's no way...
Okay, I'm telling you, it's real.
And y'all need to take
this shit more seriously.
- Okay, right.
- Yes, that would be crazy.
Okay, you know what?
Just observe.
The New Year will come and
all the unbelievers will
fuck off, and there's
no way in hell
that I'm going to make you, any
of you sick even.
Not Y2K bomb coat.
Oh no. What are we
going to do without...
Or Boner's bomb coat, face.
- Open door.
- Cale-se.
Hey, what the fuck
are you writing?
My supplies, okay?
I need to have PT, condom,
obviously, and then...
- Why?
- How so why?
I think the end of the world is over
likely than
you get laid, bro.
100 percent, man.
- This is the stupidest...
- It will work.
- It will work!
You are a fucking idiot.
Dude,
it sure works.
Eu vi em "Candid Camera".
God.
Look, it's practically invisible.
Hey, guys. Hey.
- Follow me.
- All right, calm down, bro.
He is fine?
Hey, girls.
What's happening?
How are you?
- Hey.
What are your names?
I'm Cassidy, and this is Emma.
Cassidy, Emma, ​​Emma, ​​Cassidy.
Legal.
My name is Breckie, and my
friends call me Brex.
Like music and such. Um, I
have a question for you.
Hmm, I'm with some friends
here, but we are hungry.
- Is that a camera?
- No.
- Are you serious?
- No, no.
Wow, you are so perverted.
You little worm.
Yeah, you better run, you worm.
I liked your dress!
Oh yeah.
Oh shit.
- So fucking hot.
- Shit.
Go Go.
Oh my God.
You weren't lying.
Man, she's been there every
day since she moved.
How often
can you clean a car?
I'm telling you, my new
top three in hitting one,
Sarah Michelle Gellar,
Britney Spears
and this girl over there.
You're so lucky you
get to live across the street
- of that piece of ass.
- Dude, I know, I know.
Look, she's bowing.
Look.
- Oh.
- Oh!
Hey guys, what are you doing?
- Boo!
- Mind your own business, idiot.
Hey, what did I say
about coming to my room
- sem be invited?
- Come on, Dy.
- Outside!
- I'm not intruding.
Now!
Drug.
Will he deliver?
No, we're holding your
war hammer hostage.
We are well.
- Dude, let's go.
- Incredible.
Holy crap!
Look at her hand on
that hose, bro.
Look at that grip, man.
Oh yes, dear.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- No!
- No, move your van!
- Seriously, man?
- Right in front.
It sucks, man.
- Damned.
- Come on, honey.
- Hate this guy.
- This sucks, bro.
Hey, pull your shorts
up a little.
Ah, he has to prepare.
- No way, bro.
- Hey dude. Hey.
- Ah, ele acha...
- Come on. Let's go.
What does he think she will do?
- Brother.
- Oh no, man.
You can see how
disgusted she looks.
- Not that! There!
- Oh shit!
- She... she just went...
- Wait.
Is this a new Macintosh?
Is she trying... is she
trying to fund my college?
You could make my sugar mom.
Oh, man, you're
telling me, man.
Man, he's still talking to her.
- Loser.
- Hey!
- She's leaving.
- She can't hear you.
She's not interested.
- Sai, honey.
- Now. It touches, hand.
- No!
No chance dear!
Not the damn... oh!
Oh shit, man.
Oh shit.
- Get out of here.
- Brother.
What's with all
these weird statues?
Maybe her family is European?
They are elegant and
sexually liberal.
- Mm.
- Oh.
Dude, that's what I'm talking about.
I think I'm in love.
- Oh.
- Oh my God.
She's going to take a shower.
Go Go go.
- Please please please.
- She's going to be naked.
- Please.
- No, no!
- Don't do anything else!
- No!
Drug.
We have to get a better angle.
Okay, I'll buy the
safe from you for $100.
end offer.
Saia gives current, hand.
You have Limp
Bizkit, you have the
Creed, you got
Whole, you got...
Hey guys, let's get Boner out of her.
Come on la Boner.
Ah!
Dude, I swear...
- I have your concert.
- Oh, come on... Shut up, man.
Come on, come on,
I'm killing now.
- No.
- Crippled.
Your brother is badass.
Oh shit.
- Oh.
- Wait.
He has his baby pads.
- What he is doing?
- Cum.
I can't believe I
'm related to him.
- Hey, look.
- Oh.
He's not going to rat us out, right?
Because I need
it, like, it's really bad.
- What the hell is that?
- Hey, you don't just walk with it.
and talk to a girl like that.
- Get away from her.
- What the fuck?!
Hey, did she just
voluntarily touch you?
Is she holding his hand?
This is not happening now.
- Wow.
- He... he's going in.
Expensive. fucking shit.
She probably feels bad for him.
Oh my God. I want her
to feel bad for me every day.
Brady is a goddamn pimp.
Hey, go to mouth, face.
Brady, man, my eternal respect.
Hey, does she have a boyfriend?
How does she smell?
Does she smell
like a hot girl?
Who? Sandra?
- Holy crap.
- Do you know her first name?
Hey, hey, hey, let the boy talk.
Oh my God.
Yes, I should go
over there and help her
set up a
webcam tomorrow, so...
Oh shit, face.
It looks like a date.
Man, I never would have
guessed that he
He has more flair than
his older brother.
Hey, go to mouth!
I had an idea.
Okay, just tell me.
It's possible?
Yes, I could install
a spyware program,
but if I get caught, she
's going to... she's going to kill me.
Then you will die hero.
Brady, if you do this,
you will be a legend of the
Fuck, besides being able to
hang out with us tonight.
Seriously?
He's in, boys.
Here we go.
- Don't look...
- Turn around!
- Oh my God.
- Damn Brady.
Dude, your brother. Oh my God.
Jesus Christ.
No.
Perhaps she is a sculptor.
Man, they kind
of look like Boner.
- No no.
- Ok, sim.
They look alike.
Cale-se.
Dear Penthouse.
Damned.
All right, all right, end it.
Mm, I really need this.
- Shit, man.
- I can't watch.
I am gonna puke.
It's okay, Boner.
Yeah, I'm kind of nervous.
Now or never, man.
Go! Go! Go.
What the hell is spyware anyway?
- OK.
- Shit.
Come on Brady, you can do it.
You can.
- Oh my God.
- Oh shit.
- You have to hurry.
- Jesus.
- Oh my God.
- And now.
- I can't watch this, man.
- Fuck, fuck.
- He's dead, he's dead.
He is dead.
- Yeah...
- I'm going to throw up.
- Oh, we understand each other.
- Let's go! Let's go.
He managed?
- That's it...?
- Oh shit.
Hey, that's some
"golden eye" shit right there, man.
This boy is taking too long.
Let him do his thing.
Baby, God, I know I never
I pray to you
about nothing, ever,
but please don't
be an idiot about it.
It worked?
We're in.
- Yea!
- Do not play.
- The boy did it.
- Yea.
Hey, he was a kid
five minutes ago.
This gentleman is a man.
- Hey, you did well.
- Nice.
- Health.
- Cheers, man.
Glorious.
Wow.
The technology is amazing, man.
- Hey, Boner, this is my computer.
- Hey, Boner.
Guys, guys, bath time.
Finally, brother.
My balls were about
to discover a new shade of blue.
Holy crap.
I can't wait
to see those tits.
Yes.
This is the biggest
day of my life.
Oh.
Come on, go ahead.
- Wow.
- Oh my God.
Hey. What is up?
Dude, don't you like beer?
I just feel like a worm.
Man, we're
just having fun.
I know, it's just...
She trusted me, man.
Just turn it off.
We're going, we
're going, in a little while.
Hey Brady, where
are you going, man?
- Oh, fuck it.
- The Internet is amazing.
Yes.
Eww!
Hey, what? Is she bipartite?
- Brutal.
- I would still touch her.
contortionist.
a wig. I knew it.
I knew that.
- Oh! Oh!
- What the hell is that?
Ah, ah.
Uh...
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Is that that CGI thing?
Man, it's still...
It's still kind of hot.
I don't... I don't like it.
I do not like this.
Not.
fucking shit. People, she saw us.
Like, you need to call a
ambulance, the police
and then his parents.
- Call your parents.
- I understood.
911, what's your emergency?
Yes, I'm calling about
a girl with snakes on her head.
- How many snakes, sir?
- I don't know how many snakes!
Holy crap.
Hey Hey. Did you hear that?
What was that?
Hey Hey.
She's on the roof, man.
- What the hell is that?
- Oh!
Oh!
Oh no.
Oh my God!
Let's get out of here.
- What's up?
- Caution!
Go Go go go go!
Look, we need to get out,
we need to get out of here.
Brady.
S-Sandra?
We... we didn't mean to
hurt you, right?
Right, Dylan? We...
Oh my God...
No! Nobody can kill you!
Leave him alone!
No!
- Jane McAllister, 48...
- Sorry, wait for your release.
Jane McAllister, 48.
I understood.
This is where the vase
will be during the ritual.
Are you nervous about everything?
No, I'm not part of the coven.
I'm just the husband
in the background.
But, yes, I'm nervous.
No.
Did you eat
anything before we left?
Yes, I got one of your Gogurts.
This is not a meal, man.
I ate two of them.
So tell us why
you volunteered
to be the receptacle
and start saying
I volunteered to
be the receptacle because.
Um, I volunteered
to be the receptacle
because I always felt
that I was destined
for something bigger
than me, I think.
That makes sense?
And I just want to say,
it's an absolute honor
offer my body
as the earthly vessel
of Our Lord Ukabon.
Thank you very much, Kirsten.
Good luck tonight.
Yes, good luck or... yes.
Are you nervous to see one?
A demon?
You are on a trip.
Have you ever seen one?
Wait, I thought it would be
like New Year's Eve,
Y2K for the whole thing...
I mean, for
the big ones, yes.
Julia, the book.
- I have to go.
- OK.
It is important to massage the
entrance to the other realm,
but let's not call
Ukabon into the vessel.
until the stroke of midnight,
when the veil is thinnest.
Thanks.
- The window...
- The window.
- It starts to crack.
- To crack.
- The gate...
- Gate-
- starts to open.
- Open.
- The veil...
- The veil
- starts to slide.
- Slide.
- Ukabon
.
We put the
needle with your name
and we pull you to
our earth plane.
Troy.
faces.
- What was that.
- Which?
- Hey.
I think I saw something.
Something is here!
Is that Fergus again?
I just expelled him, dear.
- Okay, follow my lead.
- Do not stop.
- Let's talk to you without being invited.
- Troy, get in there.
Not invited.
Our anger thou hast kindled.
lit.
All your power we...
No, no, no.
And I threw you back...
May?
May, I can't see.
May?!
What?
May?
Dude, how do we get out of here?
Oh, man, your head.
Wow, stop, look at this.
Oh shit.
- What the hell?
- What is that?
Hey, what's going on?
- Dude, what is this?
- Is that a person?
No!
Oh oh oh! Oh!
Oh shit!
What was this? What was this?
Shh, shh! Turn off the light!
Turn it off!
Where's the button?
Shh, be still!
Something licked my hand.
- Which?
- Something licked my hand.
- Nothing licked your hand.
- No, I'm serious.
shut up. I do not care.
shut up. Don't turn on the light.
oh what?
Have Jesus.
Oh my God.
Shh, shh, shh, shh!
We are not Hell.
I shouldn't be in hell!
Stop panicking!
I shouldn't be here.
I go to church.
Listen to me, there is no such
thing as hell. OK?
- And you don't even go to church.
- Help!
Stay down.
- Hey!
- Oh shit! He saw me.
- Troy, shut up.
- Oh Merda.
What are you doing?
Is coming.
What are we going to do, Nate?
Wait!
Madam, wait! Wait!
My friend and I are lost.
We don't know where we are.
You are in the feeding camps.
What is the eating area?
To area...
Oh, you're cool.
What great sin did you commit?
I told you!
Look, miss, my
friend and I didn't do anything wrong.
Oh, of course not.
No, we really don't.
I don't think we died.
We were doing a ritual
with an old book
and everything went wrong.
Book? Which book?
Troy, I think when
those witches sent that
demonic thing here,
we accidentally came with it.
It is possible? These
witches were trying
summon a powerful
demon into a woman's body.
Which name?
What name did they try to invoke?
Shit, I don't remember.
Something like...
It was like Qui-Gon or
Pokemon or some shit like that.
The book on the Order of Blood?
Yea! Do you know him?
Yup. Oh, I hate Ukabon!
You are not far from him.
Eight minutes.
Troy, what we need
is this Ukabon at
midnight when the
witches take you across the valley.
Oh yeah! And then
we can grab it like this
take it, and
we can go home!
Yes.
Can you please
take us to Ukabon?
We only have eight minutes,
shit, seven minutes now.
If I return you
to Earth, you will write
my name in the Great
Book of Witches?
Yes sure.
My name is Mabel the
Skull Biter.
I took command of 30 legions.
Hurry, run!
This way.
- What are you doing?
- Continues.
Shh!
I nearly ruined
my hand on these stakes.
Come here.
Hey Mabel, you might
have been to hell for
cause of an isolated shoplifting ?
Oh yes, Troy, that's the
worst thing you've ever done.
- What does this mean?
- Shut up.
No, seriously.
What does this mean?
- Cale-se!
- Shh!
Remember, fresh souls
are tastier.
Mabel, take it slow.
Man, what if she
's taking us to, like,
one of your little
demon friends or something?
No I do not think.
I'm a good judge of people.
No... Oh, sorry.
No, don't get involved.
Hey, keep going.
We're going to lose Mabel.
Why are you standing still, bro?
Go! Go! Go!
Ok!
- Mabel!
- Oh dear.
I almost stepped into that
huge trap.
- Oh!
- Nate, my hand!
Where?
Mabel, my hand!
They! It seems!
Why are you raising your voice?
Maybe because you're
leading us to our deaths.
Where the hell
are you taking us?
Nobody talks to me like that.
In this world, I give the orders!
I am nobody's servant!
Grand Order, return it to me immediately!
Mabel!
Mabel! Mabel!
Come back here, you stupid bitch!
We are lost.
Nate, get the light.
Let me have this.
What? Not.
You don't know how to fight.
Yes I know.
I did martial arts.
- No you did not.
- When I was a kid I did.
Troy, I barely got... Ah, shit!
Let's go!
I'll stab you
in the face with this thing!
Oh shit, Troy! Troy,
we're making sem tempo, cara!
She just left us here!
Maybe you
shouldn't have been such an idiot!
Well shit, Troy, I
'm sorry I'm no friend-friend
with every hellish demon
I meet.
That's called leadership, Troy.
Someone has to take charge.
It won't be you.
Well, Mabel and I respond
to a different leadership style!
Help me!
Mabel!
Troy, no!
Troy, pare!
Mabel.
help me.
Oh help.
Uh...
Madam?
Run Nate!
Why do you scream like cowards?
Because there was a
woman and then there was...
She needed help, but
she... her arms were...
Oh, you've met her.
They already got me.
Shit, dear.
We only have four minutes.
We won't make it.
Men, we are here.
Here is the back entrance to the
Ukabon residence.
Here, where Worm has gone about
his business, you must grovel.
- Troy, you go first.
- No.
I only have one good hand.
I can't go hold the light.
We need the light.
I can't hold the light
and crawl at the same time...
I will fix your torch to your head.
Wait what? Not. Brutal.
Nate?
Oh face.
Get in soon Go, go,
go, go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Troy, faster!
I'm trying, Nate!
What is it?!
Shh. Calm down, men.
Man, you just pushed me
into that creature thing!
No, I didn't.
It was a reflex.
Stop acting like
I'm a bad person.
Shh!
I'll borrow it!
80 seconds.
I say we're going straight
to Ukabon 60s.
OK.
Nate, do you really think
I'm a bad person?
You can't be serious right now.
Well excuse me for thinking
it's a big problem that
my best friend thinks
i'm a terrible person.
- Shh!
- Ok, Nate, I barely got the hang of it.
and ignore me like
you always do.
You told my ex that I
have a gambling addiction.
Two years ago.
I was just trying to
make her feel better.
You never protect me, Troy.
Shit, 58 seconds. Come on.
Don't forget to
write my name in the book!
Oh shit!
Almost, Troy. We will!
Nathan, watch out!
Troy, go!
Balls!
- It's close now.
15 seconds.
Wait! Mabel!
Come with us!
Ukabon Ukabon.
Ukabon. Ukabon. Ukabon.
Write my name!
Just go, go, go!
He is coming!
Troy!
Troy, we got us!
W-wait, why...
why am I tied up?
Nate, Nate, Nate!
- No!
- Nate!
What are you doing?
How did this happen?
- How did this happen?!
- Just try again.
Do you think we can do
it again, just do it again?
Well, we can't! We can not!
It's all in the book, honey.
How did you let this happen?
Well, the film crew
wasn't my idea.
Will you blame me now?
I cleaned for you.
I prepare for you.
I do everything for you, and this is
how you thank me?
- Be quiet!
- Blame me?
You should have listened to me.
shut up. Julia, where are you going?
I'll get a mop.
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Sold into slavery
in New Orleans ♪
♪ Swamp Goddess of Light ♪
♪ Black dog head
on death bed ♪
♪ Cut and left to bleed ♪
♪ There in flames
in the corner of the world ♪
♪ Down in misery ♪
♪ There in flames
in the corner of the world ♪
♪ Left for God to see ♪
♪ Do you want to take a life? ♪
♪ Do you want to
cross that line? ♪
♪ 'Cause it's a long
way back from Hell ♪
♪ And you don't want to go there ♪
♪ With me ♪
♪ Poisonous father of the human race ♪
♪ God of tainted blood ♪
♪ Malevolence running up
the spine of the world ♪
♪ Ready for the bastard child ♪
♪ There ablaze
in the veins of man ♪
♪ Down in misery ♪
♪ There ablaze
in the veins of man ♪
♪ Left for God to see ♪
♪ Do you want to take a life? ♪
♪ Do you want to
cross that line? ♪
♪ 'Cause it's a long
way back from Hell ♪
♪ And you don't want to go there ♪
♪ With me ♪
♪ Do you want to take a life? ♪
♪ Do you want to
cross that line? ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Wanna cross that line ♪
♪ Oh, sold
into slavery in New Orleans ♪
♪ Swamp Goddess of Light ♪
♪ Black dog head
on death bed ♪
♪ Cut and left to bleed ♪
♪ There in flames
in the corner of the world ♪
♪ Down in misery ♪
♪ Lucifer's face in the
mirror when you look ♪
♪ Left for God to see ♪
♪ Do you want to take a life? ♪
♪ Do you want to
cross that line? ♪
♪ 'Cause it's a long
way back from Hell ♪
♪ And you don't want to go there ♪
♪ With me ♪
♪ Oh, poisonous father
of the human race ♪
♪ God of tainted blood ♪
♪ Malevolence running up
the spine of the world ♪
♪ Ready for the bastard child ♪
♪ There ablaze
in the veins of man ♪
♪ There is misery ♪
♪ There ablaze
in the veins of man ♪
♪ Left for God to see ♪
♪ Do you want to take a life? ♪
♪ Do you want to
cross that line? ♪
♪ 'Cause it's a long
way back from Hell ♪
♪ And you don't want to go with me ♪
♪ Hey, it's a long way
back from Hell ♪
♪ And you don't want to go... ♪
We stick the needle
with your name and you
we pull to our
earth plane, Mabel.
- Mabel.
Mabel...
Vroom.
Translation: Fabiano M. Machado
(AFT Ash J. Williams)