[laser blasts]
Any sign of that bounty hunter?
The only vessel in our
scanners is Crosshair's
and he is right on top of us.
Don't let them get away.
It's getting hot back here!
Prepping to jump.
Not without Omega.
The bounty hunter who
took her is long gone.
We'll have no chance of finding
them if Crosshair shoots us down.
Rear deflector
shields are failing.
[sighs]
Make the jump.
[engine revs]
[groans]
- [door opens]
- [footsteps approaching]
Let me out of here!
Afraid not.
- Looking for your communication device?
- [grunts]
It has been confiscated and
placed in a secure compartment.
I said let me out of here.
I would advise you to cooperate.
Mr. Bane does not respond well
to prisoners who are difficult.
- How's my asset doing?
- My name is Omega.
Who are you?
Cad Bane at your service.
Where are you taking me?
You'll be sorry when
my friends come for me.
Your friends are long
gone. I made sure of that.
No one is coming for
you, little lady.
Now sit tight and don't
cause any trouble.
But when will you have
time to fix my leg?
It is quite inconvenient.
Bane, did you hear me?
Mr. Bane. Mr. Bane.
- I have the girl.
- What is her condition?
Alive, so I expect a premium.
See that she stays that way.
That depends on you.
I'll be at the rendezvous.
Bring my unmarked credits.
I will deliver the payment
and retrieve Omega.
Your personal interest in the young clone
has threatened our operation enough.
Taun We, you will go to our
abandoned facility on Bora Vio.
Bring the bounty hunter his
payment and recover our property.
Yes, Prime Minister.
When the clone is returned, confine
her to the sublevel facility.
Once you have retrieved the genetic
material needed, terminate her.
This is all that clone's
fault. He shot my leg off.
He was protecting me.
That's what friends do.
Why isn't yours helping you?
Well, Mr. Bane is very busy.
I could fix your
leg if you want.
I mean, it's a simple
booster adjustment.
I've done it a bunch of times
for AZI-3 back on Kamino.
[scoffs] I am a
techno service droid.
I am quite capable of
completing my own repairs.
You are a prisoner and
are not to be trusted.
Have it your way.
Your description of the bounty hunter is
a match to one from the Republic's files.
That's him.
Cad Bane.
He had multiple
run-ins with the Jedi
and was responsible for attempting
to abduct Chancellor Palpatine.
First the bounty hunter on
Pantora and now this guy?
Why are they after the kid?
Because she is more
valuable than we realized.
What do you mean?
I further analyzed
Omega's genetic profile
and discovered she has
pure, first-generation DNA.
Whoa!
Wait. W-W-What does that mean?
All clones were created from
a host named Jango Fett.
While our genetic structure was modified
for growth acceleration and obedience,
Omega is a pure
genetic replication.
How many clones like that exist?
To my knowledge
there's only one other.
A male clone code-named Alpha,
later referred to as Boba.
Since he disappeared at
the start of the war,
that makes Omega the sole living
source of Fett's raw genetic material.
If she's vital to the
Kaminoans' cloning operation,
they must have put
the bounty on her.
So how do we find
this bounty hunter?
Tech, check with Cid. See if
her contacts know anything.
We'll keep monitoring comms.
[sighs] No. Not
that way... [grunts]
- Look, you need to rewire…
- [sighs]
…the servos in your hip first.
That is what I am trying to do.
Will you just let me help you?
You are a prisoner.
Exactly.
It's not like I can
escape off this ship.
That is a valid point.
[sighs] I'm only a kid.
Oh, all right,
but make it quick.
And not a word of
this to anyone.
[whispering] Of course not.
[grunts]
- [beeping]
- [clattering]
Okay. Let's get to work.
Do not try anything funny.
Mr. Bane will be back shortly.
How long have you
been working for him?
Many years.
I am his trusted confidant.
We are a team.
Really? He's not
very nice to you.
On the contrary, my treatment
is perfectly adequate…
Most of the time.
There. How does your leg feel?
It is misaligned.
You will need to adjust the
calibration, but be careful.
Relax. I've done this before.
Oh, my. Yes. That's working.
It feels brand-new.
Sorry.
It's only temporary.
Now, where did you
hide my comm device?
[beeping]
Todo, get your chassis up here.
I can't see anything
in this chop.
[ship rattles]
[beeping]
Todo, get up here.
Todo?
[sighs] Come on, come
on, come on. Where is it?
Ah, yes!
[Cad Bane] Ya glitchy droid.
What's taking so long?
Todo? Where's the kid?
[scoffs] Mr. Bane, she's
quite obviously right there.
[gasps] Oh.
[Todo] Uh-oh.
Wait here.
Hello? Is anyone
there? Can you hear me?
Yeah. Cid knows all about
Bane but not how to find him.
She said we're on our own.
[Omega] Come in. Come in.
- [Omega] Anyone?
- Omega!
Omega, are you there? Omega!
It's long-range. I'll
try to boost the signal.
Is anyone there?
[Hunter] Omega, do you copy?
Hunter? [Gasps]
I'm here. I got away,
but you have to hurry.
[Hunter] Where are you?
I… I... I don't know where I am.
[Wrecker] Hang on, kid.
We're coming for ya!
[sighs] The signal's too weak to
establish a direct connection trace.
Omega, we need a relay
of your position.
Try to create a power surge.
Can you find a panel nearby?
There's one by a door.
It looks like the
ones on Tipoca City.
[Tech] That's good. First,
see if you can activate it.
[power panel charging up]
- [beeps]
- It worked. Now what should I do?
[Tech] Next you will need
to reroute the circuits
to overload the main grid.
[Cad Bane] By hook or by crook…
[gasps]
You're coming with me.
[Tech] Omega?
- Get off of...
- [Tech] Do you copy?
- [Omega] Let me go!
- I still can't get a good read.
[Omega] Hunter, I need you!
[Hunter] Omega!
- Omega...
- [Cad Bane groans]
It really does feel brand new.
[alarm blares]
Mr. Bane, an unidentified
ship is approaching.
[Cad Bane] Check it out.
No.
I am not going with you.
You're lucky they
want you alive.
Who wants me?
You'll soon find out.
- [gasps]
- [laser blasts]
I told you you'd be sorry
when my friends showed up.
Quiet.
Taun We?
She needs help!
None you can give.
[woman] He's right.
Fennec Shand.
Hello, Bane.
You got no business
messin' with my score.
You of all people know
it's all about the price.
Besides, she was my score first.
Omega and I go way back.
Don't we?
You lack the experience
to be goin' up against me.
Yet, I'm the one
who has the payment.
That's my case you're holdin'.
Hand it over and I'll
let you walk outta here.
How about a trade?
The case for the girl.
Sounds fair.
You first.
I have the case!
[beeping]
[explosion, glass shatters]
- My credits!
- [blasting]
Todo! Find the kid.
I am on it!
[gasps]
You should know
when to quit, Shand.
[beeping]
[gasps]
[screen beeps, powers up]
[screen beeping continues]
I think I've got her.
She's in the Lido system.
Where in the Lido system?
I'm pinpointing the
exact coordinates.
Hang on!
Mr. Bane!
Do not worry. I will recover
the target. I will not fail you!
[screen beeping continues]
[Fennec] They won't
get here in time.
The only person you can
rely on is yourself.
Why did you kill Taun We?
Part of the job.
You should thank me.
What their Prime Minister
has planned for you
is far worse than why I'm here.
What does he want me for?
You already know the answer.
Omega, I'm trying to help you.
You said the same
thing on Pantora.
There you are! You
are coming with.
- [Fennec grunts]
- [Todo grunts, groans]
It's too late for that.
It's time to go, Omega.
[grunts]
[grunts, groans]
Flight pods.
[footsteps]
Playtime's over, little lady.
[grunts]
- [Fennec grunts]
- [Omega grunts]
- [Fennec grunting]
- [Cad Bane grunting]
[groans, sighs]
- [gasps]
- [groans]
- [grunting, groaning]
- [Fennec grunts]
[Fennec grunts]
[Fennec grunts, groans]
[Fennec grunting]
[Todo approaching]
Going for the flight pod?
[gasps]
That will not get you very far.
- [Omega grunting]
- You are coming with me.
Let me go!
[grunts]
[both screaming]
[screams, grunts]
[Fennec grunts]
[groans]
- [grunts]
- [short circuiting]
[groans]
[grunts]
[Fennec grunting]
[bones break, groans]
- [grunting]
- [Fennec straining]
- Ah ah ah.
- [gasps]
Where do you think you're going?
[engine starts]
Oh, no!
[screams]
You'll be sorry for this…
[Fennec groaning]
[grunts]
[Todo] Bane, the
target is getting away!
Get to the ship!
- [Fennec grunts]
- [grunts]
[groans]
- [alarm blaring]
- [gasps]
Ugh! No!
- [alarm blaring continues]
- [screen beeps]
[engine failing]
[alarm blaring continues]
[thuds]
[engine dies, crashes]
[gas releases]
- Omega! Are you in there?
- Wrecker!
Aw! Good to have you back, kid.
[engine starts]
[crying]
Are you okay,
Omega? Are you hurt?
[sniffles]
Why is this happening? Why
are the Kaminoans after me?
Hunter, you have to tell her.
You're valuable to them.
More than all the other
clones. Even more than us.
You're different.
Different? How?
Get us in the air.
I am trying, but our
systems are not responding.
- They appear to have been sabotaged.
- [sighs]
[growls]
[beeping]
I require an update.
Omega was rescued by the same
clones I encountered on Pantora.
I can track them, but
that will cost extra.
No.
As long as she is not in the
hands of Lama Su, she is safe.
I will transfer your payment.
If you change your mind,
you know how to reach me.
[switch clicks]
[yawns]
[Tech snoring]
- [switch clicks]
- Can't sleep?
I keep thinking
about the Kaminoans.
Seeing that place.
I don't want to end up
an experiment in a tube.
That's not gonna happen.
If I'm as valuable as you say,
Lama Su will keep sending
bounty hunters after me.
He can send everyone
in the galaxy.
You have us.
You can't fight them all.
Omega, you don't have to worry.
You are never going
back to Kamino.
Promise?
I promise.